Chapter 391: Two Days

Zhao Hai dealt with the matters inside the Space while also handling the matters back at Iron Mountain Fort. Naturally, the information about the Space’s upgrades as well as the fact about detoxification was told to Green and the others.

Green was very excited that tears streamed down from his face. For him, there was no better news than this. As long as Zhao Hai recovers, they wouldn’t need to fear for the scenario where the Space would suddenly vanish. Green and the others were extremely glad, nothing was more important than Zhao Hai recovering.

…

Time passed as the Haven continued on travelling. It was already the tenth day after they met the Shrimp tribesmen. The things back in Iron Mountain Fort were almost taken care of, and some of the medicinal herbs were already collected. However, the quantity needed was still not enough, so they need wait for three days for the herbs to become fully collected. Zhao Hai could start processing the antidote by then.

At this time, the Fruit Trees as well as the Bread Trees were already planted. But they didn’t yield any fruit yet since their growth rate was the same as outside. So there wasn’t anything to see from them right now.

The Processing Factories also weren’t idling. They had already processed all of the rice and wheat. Now they were currently processing the fruit oil.

This time, a large number of animals could now be raised inside the Ranch so Zhao Hai placed his argalis inside the Space. At this time, Zhao Hai understood that the Ranch didn’t need to have feed anymore. This was because the animals could now graze from the ground as well as hunt other animals for meat. Herbivores would eat grass while carnivores would eat the herbivores.

Because of the recent upgrades, all the grass present in the Ranch could now be eaten. This also made the animals undergo migration from time to time. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried that the Ranch would get destroyed. Additionally, Mu’er was also present, so Zhao Hai didn’t need to worry about the animals.

Zhao Hai also noticed that the grasses inside the Ranch grew much faster than those outside. Although it was not as fast as the Farm, it was not that much slower either.

The reason why Zhao Hai allowed the carnivores to hunt the herbivores was so that the population of herbivores would be controlled. The small world needed to be balanced. If the herbivores were left to their own, they would incessantly multiply, eating all of the grasses in the world and destroying it in the process. Zhao Hai didn’t want this to happen, so he established a food chain inside the Ranch.

Obviously, this process certainly made Zhao Hai lose a lot of money. After all, these carnivores must eat meat. But Zhao Hai didn’t worry, as long as a stable food chain was created, the Ranch wouldn’t be destroyed.

The Ranch had enough food for the numerous herbivores that Zhao Hai released, but the carnivores present weren’t a lot; this made it an incomplete food chain. With the number of prey vastly outnumbering the predators, it was an inevitability that the Ranch would run out of food. However, this was Zhao Hai’s Ranch, not nature. Those herbivores would still be killed for meat, not many would be left.

Suddenly, Zhao Hai remembered that all of these considerations were of no importance. The Ranch indeed became a small world, but the situation still remained unchanged. Like before, the animals present here were all either digitally generated, or digitally raised, it was just the way they were raised that was different.

Zhao Hai regarded this situation as a serious matter, if he continues with the current model, sooner or later the number of beasts that he would raise could match those that were herded by the Beastmen. This was a terrifying thing, when this time comes, he wouldn’t be able to sell those beasts outside. Because if he does, the continent’s economy will certainly collapse, causing chaos all over the place.

But it was fortunate that he already had Mu’er to manage the Ranch. Zhao Hai could just give an order to control the number of beasts inside the Space so that they wouldn’t increase too quickly as well as decrease too quickly. All of these responsibilities were handed over to Mu’er.

Although the Ranch had all of those shortcomings, Zhao Hai still thought that it was very useful. With those carnivores constantly hunting inside the Space, their natural instincts would get sharper and sharper as time passed by. This made them true to their wild nature while inside the Space.

Their fighting strengths would be more formidable, moreover they were all completely obedient to Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai needed them to fight later on, he could just release them for battle.

At this moment, the beasts with the most population were the bulls, argali, and horses. Next in line were blood hawks, and moonlight lions. Bulls and argali were raised for their meat, horses for transportation, while the blood hawks and moonlight lions were for fighting strength.

Aside from these land magic beasts, the Ranch was also raising massive amounts of aquatic magic beasts. Also, the aquatic food chain was more complete than the land food chain. After all, Zhao Hai fully absorbed seawater into the Space, so naturally, he would be absorbing complete food chains along with it.

Zhao Hai now understood why it was still called a small world, it wasn’t a mature world since there were still some flaws here and there, thus the title small world.

But generally speaking, Zhao Hai was very satisfied regarding this small world of his. So long as he continues to upgrade the Space, then one day it will completely evolve into a complete world.

With the matters of the Space being good overall, Zhao Hai didn’t have much worries. He could just give instructions whenever he felt like changing something.

Looking at the Space’s changes day by day, Zhao Hai became very satisfied. After all, this place was his own personal domain.

…

Three days went by quickly, Rising Water City was already in sight. As long as they travel for half a day, Zhao Hai and the others would be able to enter Rising Water City’s harbor.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t paying any attention to the city right now. He was currently in the Space, in front of the Multipurpose Processing Machine. By his side was a pile of medicinal herbs.

Laura and the others were also right by his side, anxiously looking at the machine and waiting for Zhao Hai to press the button. Zhao Hai didn’t delay, he immediately pressed the button meant for depositing the materials.

When the button was pressed, a flash of white light came, then the pile of herbs by Zhao Hai’s side disappeared completely. Zhao Hai pressed the ‘Process’ button and selected the item that he wanted, the Detoxification Potion. Then finally he pressed the ‘Begin’ button. The Space deducted his balance by 10 thousand gold coins as the machine sprang into action. A projection popped up, showing Zhao Hai digits that were very important to him. The figure showed 48 hours.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be relieved, in two day’s time, he would be forever be cured of his affliction that was caused by the “Water of Nothingness”. He can finally go back to being an ordinary person.

Laura and the others looked at the numbers that were projected above. They also understood what those number represented. Laura sighed with relief as she said, “Brother Hai, in two days, two days! You can finally get rid of your poison.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he excitedly looked at Laura and Meg as he smiled, “Yes, in two days, I can finally restore my body to what it originally was.”

Meg shed tears as she hugged Zhao Hai. She didn’t realize that she was crying, she was too happy. Zhao Hai’s poison was always a heavy stone in their hearts. As long as Zhao Hai’s poison went unsolved, they wouldn’t be able to sleep comfortably. Now that in two days, Zhao Hai would be cured, the dark clouds plaguing the Buda Family would finally dissipate.

Zhao Hai patted Meg’s back gently as he smiled and said, “It’s okay, don’t cry. Everything will be alright after two days. Your young master can finally learn martial arts, we should be happy. We’ll show those people who looked down on us the fully revived Buda Clan.”

Meg was still tearing up while she nodded, she believed that Zhao Hai could achieve anything. From the beginning, she had unconditional trust towards Zhao Hai, this was because Zhao Hai was her world.

Laura’s tears were also flowing, she loved Zhao Hai. But his poison was a very big deal to her. This was because Zhao Hai’s poison could be inherited, if they had a child in the future, their children would also have this poison inside of them, making them unable to study martial arts as well as magic.

In Ark Continent, someone who couldn’t practice martial arts or magic was considered a waste. Laura was somewhat of an prideful person, how could she allow her children to be such wastes?

But she loved Zhao Hai very much, and she decided to marry him in the future. So she just hoped that Zhao Hai could cure his affliction. Now that the day had come, she was extremely happy.

Looking at Laura’s appearance, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He lifted his arm to create an empty space, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and immediately threw herself into Zhao Hai’s arms, still with tears flowing down her cheeks.

Green and the others weren’t with them today, so the only other people present were Shue and Shun. Regarding Zhao Hai’s development, the two of them were also quite happy. They had made a Blood Oath with Zhao Hai, so naturally they would hope that their master would have a bright future. After they knew Zhao Hai’s real identity, the also knew that he drank the Water of Nothingness, this was the matter that they worried very much about.

Ever since the two followed Zhao Hai, their lives had been very comfortable. Zhao Hai put their lives in order, provided them with delicious food, while at the same time taking the two of them away from their previous lives that were full of dangers. This made the two extremely grateful to their young master, so they regarded to matter of his poison very highly.

Now that the matter was close to being solved, with Zhao Hai being healthy again, they thought that things couldn’t get any better. The return of the Buda Clan was getting closer and closer.

After some time, the group calmed their emotions down and went out of the Space. The Haven was now entering the harbor, they had no choice but disembark from the ship.

Chapter 392: Call Them

Standing in front of the ship, Zhao Hai gazed at the distant Rising Water City. The size of the city wasn’t as large as Sky Water City, but the traffic of ships present were quite the same.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he turned his head, “Looking at the size of Rising Water City, it seems like it is worse than Sky Water City. But it looks like it is just as bustling here. It’ll be a good idea to have a shop at this place. Right, is there a Shelley Hotel here? Perhaps we can work together with them.”

Laura smiled, “It has, how could there be no Shelley Hotel in a city such as this? We should find them and get into contact, I believe that they would be happy. Brother Hai, how about we reduce the supply of fire fish and milk wine that we are giving to Brother Smith, to give the Calci Family a warning.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Consider that finished, I will still take into account Brother Smith’s face on this matter. But if the Calci Family continues to push me, then I will end my cooperation with them. Let’s see what they’re going to do about that.”

Laura nodded and said, “Very well, let’s give Brother Smith some face and have him speak to the family in our behalf. Let’s see Calci Family’s response, if they still go too far, hmph, then don’t blame me.”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura’s appearance and showed a faint smile and said, “This is the Laura that I know, looking like a very capable woman. Haha. Good, if they still dare try to deal with us, then we won’t be polite anymore.”

While they were talking, the ship slowly approached Rising Water City. The harbor of the city was much worse than Sky Water City. The dock looked very messy, ships could hardly find any place to dock in.

Zhao Hai knew that this should be the public pier. There was no need to pay in order to dock here, thus the numerous ships. But this was also the smallest and most chaotic ship terminal in the city.

There were other docks nearby. They were quite large, and they had good security as well. There were even porters present, but one needs to pay money in order to dock on those places.

This was Rosen Empire’s method, they would lower taxes on some areas to attract people. Upon arriving, one would get exempted from tax, but there were even more places to spend some money. In the end, if you calculate all of your expenses, they would come out to be even greater than what would be if you just paid your tax.

Zhao Hai looked at the public harbor and knew that there was no way that they could find their place there. So he had Jinan maneuver the ship towards those paid docks.

Paid docks were certainly a lot better, the water were very spacious, the pier was also very clean. There were even specialized people tasked in maintaining public security. All matters on these docks appeared to be in pristine order.

When Zhao Hai saw these docks, he couldn’t help but smile bitterly. He thought about those big companies back on Earth. The companies would willingly slash their product’s prices to the point of suffering losses just to make profits on the extra services. He didn’t expect that someone on the Ark Continent would actually think of the same method.

Zhao Hai’s group stopped on a place in the dock. They paid the supervisor for the fee and then got on the carriage to head towards the city.

Upon entering Rising Water City, Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but stare. They couldn’t say that the streets of the city were greater than those of Sky Water City, on the contrary, they were quite awful. However, the shops on both sides of the street were very numerous, they had the same liveliness as Sky Water City.

This was a port city, so businesses should be doing very well, Zhao Hai was already used to this fact. He looked at the shops on both sides of the street and turned his head to Shun, “Shun, go to those shops and see if there are any products worth noting, also, take note of the prices of the goods here. Shue, let’s go to the hotel and take a rest.”

The two complied, Shue ushered the carriage to head towards the direction of the Shelley Hotel while Shun went out to get some information. Back at the pier, Zhao Hai had already asked for the directions of the hotel, so they didn’t need to worry about getting lost.

Zhao Hai and the others quickly arrived at the Shelley Hotel. Although Rising Water City’s storefronts didn’t look very nice, the Shelley Hotel in this city was not the same. The outside of the hotel was extremely clean along with its front facade. There were also people dedicated to maintaining public security outside, fully exhibiting the quality of the hotel.

Just as Zhao Hai’s bull-pulled carriage stopped in front of the hotel,  a person wearing silk clothes immediately went out to greet them. The man looked over 50 years old with a long and skinny body. With his face full of smiles, one would be able to feel a very kind atmosphere around him.

When Zhao Hai disembarked from the carriage, the man went to Zhao Hai and greeted him, “This one is Ronaldo, the manager of Rising Water City’s Shelley Hotel. This one welcomes Mister Zhao Hai.“

Zhao Hai stared at Ronaldo and said, “You know me?”

Ronaldo smiled faintly and said, “I do. There is no Shelley Hotel Manager in the continent that doesn’t recognize Mister Zhao Hai. Mister, please come in, you’re always a distinguished guest in our hotels.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “I won’t be polite then.” Seeing the two talking and walking towards the hotel, the guests became quite alarmed. One should know that the hotel was not only for the rich, it was also quite expensive. Adding on to the fact that the Shelley Hotel had recently ousted Grand Duke Lionheart’s business, the managers of their hotels had became quite the personalities. They wouldn’t generally greet any ordinary person.

When the people saw that Ronaldo was extremely courteous towards Zhao Hai, they felt confused. This was because they didn’t know if Zhao Hai actually had any status.

During that time, when a noble looking person just went out of the hotel, he actually heard the exchange of dialog between Ronaldo and Zhao Hai. Upon hearing their words, the person’s eyes lit up, he immediately went toward his own carriage and rushed towards the direction of the City Lord’s Mansion.

…

After Zhao Hai entered the hotel’s reception hall, some people immediately went and served them some tea. Ronaldo and Zhao Hai drank a mouthful as the former said, “When I heard that mister came, I initially wanted to come greet mister at the pier. But I didn’t think that mister would actually arrive at the hotel too quickly, this is quite embarrassing.”

Zhao hai smiled and said, “Manager Ronaldo is too polite. I’m not  an influential person, coming to greet me personally is too much. I wouldn’t dare, I wouldn’t dare….”

Ronaldo smiled and said, “Mister is also too polite, mister offered quite a huge helping hand to the Shelley Family. It should be appropriate for me to personally greet mister. Anyway, why did mister come to Rising Water City? Is there anything we could help you with?”

Zhao Hai gave a smiled and replied, “There is actually a reason why I came. I want to set up a shop inside Rising Water City. The bigger the shop, the better. I hope the manager could help me with this.”

Ronaldo returned the smile and nodded, “Mister is too polite, this matter is no big deal. I’ll personally have someone inquire around. What price would be alright for mister?”

Zhao Hai replied, “The price isn’t an issue. I just want a shop right now and open as soon as possible. It’ll handle both wholesale and retail goods. Therefore, the shop’s location should be good, it also needed to be able to store goods. Transportation should also be convenient.”

Ronaldo nodded and said, “Very well, these things are quite easy to do, mister can be relieved. I’ll certainly go and find the best location as soon as possible. Right, if mister plans to set up shop here, you still have some formalities to do. I don’t know if mister is already prepared for this? If mister isn’t, the hotel could lend you a hand.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Thank you, Manager Ronaldo. To be honest, I really don’t understand about any of the matters inside Rising Water City. I’ll really have to rely on the manager here. How about this, I’ll give an additional 5,000 fire fishes to the Shelley Family each month. What does Manager think about this?”

Ronaldo stared, he was pleasantly surprised as he said, “Mister is too generous. Even if mister didn’t reward the hotel, we would still help you with this matter. Also, mister, these fire fire fishes wouldn’t be taken away from the Calci Family’s share right? Won’t mister feel awkward?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not awkward. I reckon you have already heard about the Calci Family. Now I’m just waiting for the family’s next move, if they become too overbearing, then I can only find other people to cooperate with.”

Ronaldo’s eyes lit up brightly, just like what Zhao Hai said, he already knew about the matter between Zhao Hai and the Calci Family. Because of this, he acted very enthusiastic towards Zhao Hai. Since if the Calci Family manages to make the wrong move, there would be some excess of fire fishes on Zhao Hai’s hands. If the Shelley Family could get their hands on these fishes, the family could surely make a ton of money.

The Shelley Family didn’t fear the Calci Family. Although the Calci Family aws fierce, it was impossible for them to fully uproot the Shelley Family. After all, outside of Rosen Empire, the Shelley Family had more influence than the Calci family.

However, merchant clans always wanted to hold onto wealth. So if they could prevent falling out with the Calci Family, they would. After all, compared to the entire business of the Shelley Family, the fire fishes were still a small business.

But Ronaldo also understood what Zhao Hai was implying. It was just like what Marriott reported, this Zhao Hai wasn’t a simple person.

At the thought of this, Ronaldo stood up and bowed to Zhao Hai, “Well then, this one will have to busy himself, mister. Your rooms have already been prepared as well as your meals. Mister can rest first while I handle the matters that you requested.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I thank the manager for his troubles.” Then he walked with Ronaldo outside as the latter arranged someone to lead Zhao Hai’s group to their accommodations.

Ronaldo had arranged for Zhao Hai’s group to have the best rooms of the hotel. He also instructed the attendants to give Zhao Hai the highest level of hospitality. If somebody dared to cause problems, Ronaldo wouldn’t express mercy.

Just after Zhao Hai and the others were settled inside their room, a knock was suddenly heard on the door. Shue immediately went to the door and opened it, revealing the meal that Ronaldo had prepared for them. The dishes looked very delicious and appetizing, it clearly showed how well regarded they were by the hotel.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t become polite, they immediately went and enjoyed the dishes that the hotel prepared for them. At this time, another knock was heard, when Shue went and opened it to take a look, what he saw was Shun.

After passing through the door, Shun gave Zhao Hai a bow and said, “Young Master, I have asked around, there are quite a lot of goods here. But compared to Sky Water City, there are more low-quality good present. Because of this, the goods sold in this city are much cheaper than those at Sky Water City.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, let’s eat first. After the meal, we’ll go around and scout for good shop locations as well as products that the Merpeople wanted. Then we’ll go back out at sea as soon as possible to trade with them.”

Shun gave a nod, then joined the others in the table to eat a meal. Laura who was sitting gave a frown and asked, “Brother Hai, did you think about the people that we’ll have to hand the shop’s management to? The slaves back at Iron Mountain Fort wouldn’t do, we can manage them back at the fort but not here. I think we need to recruit a few trustworthy people.”

Hearing what Laura just said. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smiled and say, “What? Didn’t you have some good people we can make us of? This is also good since we don’t need to worry about their loyalty. Those people you have back at the Purcell Duchy aren’t doing anything anyway, we should call them over.”

Laura‘s face lit up, “Right, if we don’t get in contact with them for quite some time, they would certainly feel strange. Since we cannot return to Purcell Duchy and happen to open a shop, we should bring them over here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “After our meal, you should write a letter for them and have it sent via blood hawks from Stony Mountain. Go make them head outside Casa City to gather and I’ll go and meet them.”

Laura nodded and said, “Brother Hai, I think you should also send a letter to Uncle Evan and tell him about this matter and have him prepare.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Be relieved, I’ll go arrange it. I think Uncle Evan couldn’t wait to get rid of your people. This way, Magic Lily Store would be completely under his control.”

Hearing this, Laura sighed. Magic Lily Store was something she established. It was just a pity that she had to hand it over to someone else.

Looking at her appearance, Zhao Hai gave a smile, “Don’t be sad, the Magic Lily stores that you built aren’t your largest assets anyway, it was those people who were nurtured under your influence. Those people are good resources, we must provide them with a stage to exhibit their talents to the limit. By the way, don’t forget to tell them to bring their entire families.”

Laura gave a smile and replied, “Don’t worry, I’ll tell them. I shall also inform them that this wouldn’t be the only store that we’ll open. If the matter back at Sky Water City gets resolved, we would need people to manage our shop there as well. Right, Brother Hai, don’t you think that Iron Mountain Fort needs a bit more managing staff? How about we send some of my people over there as well?”

Zhao Hai nodded, but at this time, another knock was heard on the door.

Chapter 393: Charlie

Zhao Hai stared blankly when he heard the knock. It was because he already told the hotel attendants to not disturb him if there’s nothing important going on. He believed that the hotel attendants wouldn’t dare disregard his instructions.

When someone knocked on the door the first time, Zhao Hai expected it to be Shun, and it turned out the be him. But who would knock on the door this time? Zhao Hai waved his hand as the monitor appeared. The group immediately saw a man dressed in gorgeous clothes standing outside. What was bizarre about this man was the fact that even though he wore  good quality and well-made clothes, the appearance of his garments seem to be those worn by servants.

The clothes of a servant were actually more magnificent than most nobles? When Zhao Hai and the others analyzed the man’s clothes, they couldn’t help but feel confused.

However, Zhao Hai knew that for a servant to be able to dress like this, his master should be anything but simple. Zhao Hai gestured to Shun, Shun gave a nod as he opened the door.

Right outside the door was the servant. Although he had magnificent clothes, the servant still acted very humble. When he saw Shun open the door, the man politely gave a small bow and said, “Hello, this one seeks an audience with Mister Zhao Hai.”

Looking at the man’s very polite attitude, Shun didn’t decrease his vigilance even by a bit, he looked at the man and said, “Can I ask why you are here? Why do you need to meet the young master?”

The servant showed a faint smile and said, “This one is just a servant, here to convey a message from my master. It’s just that the identity of my master is quite special, so this servant was the only one that came to see mister Zhao Hai.”

Just as Shun was facing a dilemma, Zhao Hai’s voice came, “Shun, make him enter.”

After listening to Zhao Hai’s instruction, Shun immediately complied then turned and gave a gesture towards the man. Then the well-dressed servant entered the room.

Zhao Hai was now sitting inside the living room. Naturally, the servant recognized Zhao Hai, so he immediately went towards him and gave a bow, “Little Liru has seen Mister Zhao Hai. My master is currently at his accommodation and is inviting mister Zhao Hai over.”

Although his tone of voice was very polite, the atmosphere around the servant revealed a sort of pressure that seems to don’t accept refusal. This made Zhao Hai quite confused, he didn’t know what this servant was planning to do.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t affected too much. He just looked at the servant and said, “Can you tell me the identity of your master? You should know that I have a lot of enemies in the continent, I wouldn’t just accept casual invitations.”

Liru froze for a moment, but he still continued to look at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, I really can’t just say the name of my master. Just know that my master is very sincere this time. I ask you to please accept his invitation.”

Zhao Hai frowned as he stared at the servant, “The people in this room can certainly be trusted, I’ll vouch for it. If you really don’t intend to tell me, then I’m sorry, I don’t like meeting with people who likes to hide things from me.”

After listening to Zhao Hai, Liru;s expression couldn’t help but sink. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, since you really wanted to know. My master who wanted to meet you is His Highness Rosen Empire’s Third Prince.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly, with a puzzled look he asked, “If His Highness the Third Prince wanted to meet me, then why does he have to be quite mysterious? Is something wrong?”

Looking that Zhao Hai seemed to be confused, the servant said with a light tone, “I didn’t realize that mister wasn’t informed, I have misunderstood mister. Rising Water City is under the control of the Second Prince while Jade Water City belonged to the Third Prince. His highness’ trip this time is a secret matter. He couldn’t just go out into the city since he is afraid of alerting the Second Prince. So this time when His Highness wanted to meet Mister Zhao Hai, he could only request for a secret meeting.”

Zhao Hai understood, so he didn’t have any more worried. He turned to the servant and said, “Good, lead the way.” He stood as he said that.

Seeing at Zhao Hai accepted to come with him, Liru finally relaxed. He feared that Zhao Hai would change his mind, so Liru immediately led him out.

Zhao Hai and Liru went to the back of the hotel where a carriage was already waiting for them, inside one of the courtyards. Without being polite, Zhao Hai immediately sat inside the vehicle.

The carriage looked extremely ordinary, it lacked even a smidgen of special quality material. It was only quite big, can fit about five or six people. Zhao Hai took Shun and Shue with him, Liru was driving the carriage at front.

Zhao Hai initially thought that Liru was just having unnecessary caution. What was the point in being too serious? However, he changed his mind when he thought more deeply about Liru’s words and actions. Liru might be afraid because the battle between the princes may have reached quite a heated period. If this was so, there was enough reason for the Third Prince to be very careful.

But Zhao Hai was even more confused when he recalled that the Rosen Empire’s King was still quite healthy. Under such circumstance, it was quite confusing for the princes to be this vigorous in their battle.

The carriage went out of the hotel and into the busy street outside. They went around quite a few times before stopping at a house. Although this was the back side of the house, the light coming from the door made it look quite unordinary. The look on the door was more intricate than what most people would use.

The carriage didn’t stop and directly entered the house before completely stopping on a parking space. Liru asked Zhao Hai to disembark, Zhao Hai became curious, he wanted to know why the Third Prince called him over.

Under Liru’s guidance, the group passed through several courtyards before arriving at a small courtyard. This courtyard wasn’t that large, about the same size as Sweet Plum Courtyard. However, this place didn’t have any plum blossoms, instead, it had some ornamental trees. Zhao Hai couldn’t name them, but this made this place even more distinctive.

When the group arrived at the courtyard, there were two people already standing at the front door. One looked about 50 years old and wore a magnificent merchant’s garment on his fatty body. The fellow looked very big, just like a meat mountain that was standing there. What made Zhao Hai surprised was that even though the man was a literal meatball, he didn’t look like he was exerting any effort in staying up. This certainly showed that the man had quite the strength.

The other person wore a very ordinary noble’s clothing, not looking very magnificent. He was about 30 years old and had a very gentle look. The person was very well groomed, although he was just standing there, the atmosphere around him commanded respect and superiority.

Liru went towards the 30-year old man and said, “Your Highness, this is Mister Zhao Hai.” The man nodded and smiled at Zhao Hai, “Please forgive Charlie for the disrespect, mister. The situation  didn’t leave me with enough choices.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “This one has seen Prince Charlie. His highness is too polite, it is my honor to be invited by Your Highness.”

Charlie smiled faintly and said, ‘Mister is too courteous. Let me introduce mister to Rising Water City’s famous sea merchant, Aonas.”

Zhao Hai bowed and said, “Zhao Hai pays his respects to Mister Aonas.”

Aona’s’ flabby face rippled as he smiled, “Mister is too kind. Your Highness, Mister, please.” Then he led the two men inside the living room of the house.

After settling in the living room, Liru immediately served the group with a cup of tea. When the group already had a few sips of the tea, Charlie opened his mouth, “This time when I came to handle some matters in Rising Water City, I came to hear about mister’s arrival. So I took the liberty of inviting mister over, I hope you could forgive my disrespect.”

Zhao Hai gave a smile and said, “You’re highness is too polite. Let’s forget about being disrespectful, what did Your Highness look for me for?”

Charlie stared, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be so direct. He could only show a faint smile as he replied, “Mister is really a straightforward person, not beating around the bush. This time, I asked mister to come to discuss whether I could have the honor of having a partnership with mister or not.”

Zhao Hai had already expected this point. Except for the products that he had, there were no other qualities of him that other people could remember. So when Charlie got to the point, Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised. He just looked at Charlie and said, “May I know which business Your Highness wanted to cooperate with me?”

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “I know that mister is  currently working with the Shelley Family and the Calci Family for some business. I’m also interested about your fire fishes and milk wine. I just don’t know if mister can also cooperate with me?”

Zhao Hai looked at Charlie and said, “Your Highness, to tell you the truth, it isn’t impossible to work with you. The products that I supply the Calci Family and the Shelley Family which were 55 thousand jin of fire fish and 50 thousand jin of milk wine aren’t my limit. I can provide you with 45 thousand jin of fire fishes as well as 50 thousand jin of milk wine per month. Is Your Highness satisfied with this?”

Zhao Hai’s words were actually a probe towards Charlie. He wanted to see whether the prince wanted to snatch both the Calci’s and the Shelley’s share of milk wine and fire fish. If he did, then that meant that he didn’t care about offending the two families. Zhao Hai also wanted to see whether he would acquiesce if there was a way of avoiding to offend the families. If Charlie really wanted the shares of the two families, then Zhao Hai would have to think twice about their cooperation. This was because it meant that the prince most likely held a grievance towards the two families.

When he heard what Zhao Hai just said, Charlie was dumbfounded, he wore a happy expression as he said, “Mister is really telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai nodded and replied, “I won’t dare deceive Your Highness, of course it is real.” Seeing Charlie’s reaction, Zhao Hai had found his answer.

Sure enough, Charlie smiled and said, “Good, good, that is good. Mister can rest assured that I’ll also accept the same price that you give the Calci and Shelley Families. I certainly wouldn’t let mister suffer a loss.”

Chapter 394: Sincerity

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I don’t have to worry about that, but where does your highness want the stuff delivered? I think you won’t find it comfortable in Sky Water City?”

Charlie smiled and said, “Naturally not in Sky Water City. I’d want mister to deliver to my domain, Jade Water City, I wonder if that is possible?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Of course it’s possible. I’ll supply you starting next month and pay me whenever the products arrive. How does your highness think about this?”

Charlie gave a smile and said, “Thanks for understanding, I really still have a lot to prepare. Does mister have any other products? I see that you have milk wine, so I reckoned mister should have a good relationship with the Beastmen.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s just like what your highness said, I actually have a good relationship with the Bull-Headed Race. Currently, I have some wool products on hand, is your highness interested in those?”

When Charlie heard Zhao Hai’s response, he secretly nodded to himself. He commended Zhao Hai for being tactful. He knew what Zhao Hai was getting at, Charlie smiled and responded, “A bit interested, how many blankets does mister have right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Counting both my blankets and carpets, there should be 10 thousand. This isn’t my max production, come spring they should increase.”

Charlie nodded, “Good, I’ll have those as well. Is mister okay with selling those in market price?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Of course. Next month when I deliver the fire fishes, I’ll have those blankets and carpets delivered as well. Is your highness satisfied with this?”

Charlie smiled, “Then we’re settled. And mister, if I may ask, what matter did you come to Rising Water City for? If you need any help, Aonas can lend you a hand.”

Aonas quickly added, “Yes, I could definitely provide mister with help inside Rising Water City. I have a bit of influence here.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Nothing big, I just want to buy some things as well as try to open up a shop in this city.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Charlie’s eyes lit up then he said, “How about mister open a shop at my Jade Water City? The goods and services in Jade Water City are about the same as Rising Water City. Additionally, I could give mister an exemption on taxes. What does mister think?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that Charlie would be surprisingly enthusiastic. He knew that he might offend Charlie if he refuses. He didn’t know what kind of person Charlie was, if the prince was a petty person, he might retaliate in the future.

Also, if he agrees and opened up a shop in Jade Water City, he may suffer some problems if Charlie hates him in the future. It would be a risk to his people if he chooses this option.

Looking at Zhao Hai who stayed quiet, Charlie didn’t want to be misunderstood so he immediately added, “Mister, please don’t misunderstand, I don’t mean to force you. If mister wants to go then its good, but if he disagrees then that’s fine as well. This matter wouldn’t affect our cooperation.”

Zhao Hai looked at Charlie and smiled, “Your highness has also misunderstood, you have given me such a good benefits, so of course I’ll have to head towards Jade Water City. This time, I only came to Rising Water City because it was closer. Tomorrow I’ll head to Jade Water City, I wonder when your highness will return to Jade Water City?”

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I also happen to return to Jade Water City tomorrow. I wonder if mister can give this one a ride in your ship?”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he gave a smile and nodded, “Having your highness as my guest would certainly be an honor. Then we’re good, tomorrow me and my group will be waiting for your highness in my ship. Just head to the docks of the city and look for my ship. It’s named Haven.”

Charlie smiled, “Alright. Then I won’t be bothering mister anymore. Mister should rest when you head back. Tomorrow, we still need to leave the city unnoticed.”

Zhao Hai stood up while he gave a faint smile, “Then Zhao Hai will ask to be excused, your highness.” Then he bowed to Charlie before being led away from the living room by Liru.

Charlie also accompanied Zhao Hai to the entrance. Then left Liru to guide Zhao Hai to the carriage. Charlie then returned to the living room.

Aonas looked at Charlie and said, “Your Highness, why were you too polite to him? Also, why exempt him from tax? Is it because of the fire fish and milk wine?”

Charlie gave a smile and shook his head, “No, Aonas, you must understand. When I first heard about Zhao Hai, I didn’t think much of him. But after seeing him just now, I suddenly had the inkling to pull this person to my side. This is because this person is terrifying, not because of his schemes nor his temptations. Everything he does is all straightforward, you can clearly see what he is thinking about. This is why I value him too much, for him to refrain from using schemes means that he is confident in his own strength, he disdains beating around the bush. You can also see from his actions and expressions the look of sincerity, something that I rarely see in other people.”

Aonas looked at Charlie, still confused. Charlie smiled as he added, “There are all sorts of plots and schemes in this world that it is very hard to see a sincere person. Why did I cooperate with him? This is because for people like Zhao Hai, if you are good to him and not betray him, he will never ever betray you for the sake of higher benefits.”

Aonas was still not convinced, he looked at Charlie and said, “How did your highness deduce this? How come I am unable to see it?”

Charlie gave a smile and said, “Remember when I offered him a partnership? Most people would immediately agree, after all, as a third prince I have a much higher position than either the Calci Family or the Shelley Family. But instead, he implicitly told me the shares of the two families as he revealed how much supply he can provide. This is a probe, he wanted to see my attitude towards this matter. If I wanted the shares of the two families, then he would definitely not cooperate with me. Aonas, you should know about the recent matter of the Calci Family, yes? That waste of a fifth child of the family had his eyes on Zhao Hai, and may have even suffered a loss in Zhao Hai’s hands. Despite this, Zhao Hai still didn’t give me the share of the Calci Family. This showed that he is a man of sentiment, if such a person were to join my side, then it would be a great boon for me.”

Aonas finally understood after hearing Charlie’s explanation, he gave a nod and said, “Your highness, when you invited him to Jade Water city, why did he seem to be hesitant?”

Charlie smiled and said, “This is another point that made me like him. Do you think that if he establishes a shop in Jade Water City, he will stay there for a long time? Of course not, he would send his people there. I gave him tax exemptions, average people will definitely agree, the reason why he hesitated was because if he does send his men to Jade Water City and we happen to fight in the future, he fears that I would act against his men. For someone who cares deeply about his own subordinates, that is a very desirable trait.”

Aonas looked at Charlie with an admiring look, “Your Highness, your eyes are really like blazing torches. But if Zhao Hai is really a person of sentiment, then why didn’t he give the Calci Family all of the shares? I remember that the Calci Family had helped him a lot.”

Charlie replied, “This is because he is cautious and wants to leave a leeway for himself. I think that Zhao Hai has a lot of subordinates that are counting on him for resources. If he gave all of his products to the Calci Family, he would certainly suffer big if the Family decides to stop cooperating with him. This is understandable, its basic human nature. I even believe that this overall supply of about 100 thousand fire fishes and 100 thousand jin of milk wine that he revealed isn’t his maximum supply. He will always give himself a way out.”

Aonas nodded, this point of having a back up plan is how things should be. Even he has prepared an escape route for himself, this isn’t a strange thing.

Charlie looked at Aonas and smiled faintly, “This Zhao Hai isn’t simple. Earlier, he had an enmity with Grand Duke Lionheart, but he still managed to be unscathed. Moreover, I heard that back in Aksu Empire, he had offended the Radiant Church as well as Southern King Boris, making him escape towards the Beastman Prairie. Then he used a false identity to escape to Rosen Empire. After which he lead the Empire’s anti-Radiant Church tide. He is too fierce, this is the most important point, he gave the Calci Family advice that would hit the Radiant Church in their most vital points. This made me decide to settle in recruiting him.”

Aonas frowned as he asked, “Your Highness, isn’t that idea from the Calci Family? What made you think that it was given by Zhao Hai?”

Charlie made a disdainful expression, “Hmph, if the Calci Family already had an idea that great, then they should have already used it a long time ago. They had been pressured by the Radiant Church all these years, and the idea only came out just as Zhao Hai arrived at Sky Water City, isn’t this too coincidental? Therefore, I judged that this should be Zhao Hai’s doing. Those antiques back at the Calci Family, hehe, it would be impossible for them to come up with this idea. It was good that Smith and his brothers are really talented, and they had good eyes. It was only that fifth child Juwan that is a complete waste. If you have the chance, try getting Smith’s favor, if we can get their support, then the throne wouldn’t be able to escape my grasp, haha.”

Aonas didn’t expect that Charlie would have such high view of Smith. But he didn’t get angry, he knew his capabilities, and he was also a merchant. When thinking about Charlie snatching the throne, these few tricks could also be considered good.

Charlie turned to Aonas, this man is very important to him. Aonas’ capabilities were formidable, and is loyal to him. It was this point that made Aonas incomparable to the other people. Thinking about this, Charlie faintly smiled and said, “Aonas, go help me prepare to leave with Zhao Hai’s ship tomorrow in returning to Jade Water City. The matters in Rising Water City will be handed over to you. Don’t forget, you are now a merchant, except for extremely important matters, don’t contact me. Just go and do you merchant duties.”

Aonas nodded.

Chapter 395: Buda Family’s Opportunity to Recover

Zhao Hai returned to the hotel. After saying goodbye to Liru, he immediately found Ronaldo and told him that opening the store would have to wait.

Ronaldo knew that Zhao Hai had went out earlier, but he didn’t know where he went. He also couldn’t ask Zhao Hai, in any case he already got the family an additional 5,000 fire fishes per month. So he didn’t probe further, he just accepted the decision fully.

Ronaldo had already been given orders by the family to not be greedy in cooperating with Zhao Hai. Otherwise, they would lose everything. This was the reason why Ronaldo didn’t request anything from Zhao Hai and just helped him with everything. He believed that Zhao Hai wouldn’t leave him unrewarded and sure enough, he was rewarded with an additional 5,000 fire fishes per month. Although not that much, the Shelley Family still regarded it as quite a bit of income.

And now that Zhao Hai wanted to leave, Ronaldo didn’t stop him. He also didn’t inquire Zhao Hai as to why. He knew that further inquiry would only make the other party dislike him.

…

Zhao Hai entered the room and then reiterated what happened with Charlie to Laura and the others. Laura didn’t oppose to the cooperation since she trusted the Space. If they have a falling out with Charlie in the future, they could just receive the staff and save them.

Seeing that Laura didn’t oppose to the partnership, Zhao Hai sighed in relief. Truthfully, he still held Laura’s opinion in high regards when it comes to business decisions. After all, Laura was a true Merchant in the past, this lovely girl’s reputation even reached Rosen Empire, she isn’t playing around.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and asked, “Why do you think Charlie wanted to go with us to Jade Water City? Is it to recruit me? I don’t think that I have any worth for him to be considering me.”

Laura gave a smile and said, “Who told you that you don’t have any worth? You’re very exceptional, it is normal for him to be pulling over to his side.”

Zhao Hai just smiled faintly and said, “In any case, let’s prepare ourselves. We’ll be leaving Rising Water City tomorrow. Also, Charlie will be coming along with us for cover. I initially didn’t want to involve myself in their matters since looking at Charlie’s actions today, it seems like the battle for the throne is more intense than I thought. Taking part in their struggle isn’t a good idea.”

Laura forced a smiled and said, “We’re already involved ever since you met Charlie, it’s too late to say anything at this point. From what I can see, we might as well lend Charlie a hand. Brother Hai, if we can help Charlie get the imperial throne, the Buda Family might see itself reemerging in the future.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, “I’m afraid that meeting him is the wrong decision. I’m also afraid that if we relocate the clan to Rosen Empire, the Aksu Empire would take away the Black Wasteland from us. In the end, that place is where we decided to take root.”

Laura smiled and said, “You think too much, Elder Brother Hai. No matter who wanted to take the Black Wasteland away, they still need to deal with the poisonous fog. Nobody would dare settle there. Rest assured, that place will still be our roots. Also, nobody would think that we stayed there anyway, they might have already thought that we had escaped to the sea or something.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile, he knew that what Laura said was the truth, there was nobody that would dare settle in the black wasteland aside from them. Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “I think it would be better for us to discuss this matter with Grandpa Green.”

Laura agreed, “I think that’s a good idea. We should tell Grandpa Green about this, but I think he wouldn’t agree.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t think so, Granpa Green would certainly agree, he wanted to revive the Buda Clan more than I do.”

…

“Agree! Of course I agree. Young Master, what are you afraid of? As long as the Black Wasteland is in our hands, we will have a place to return to. If an accident happens outside, the Buda Clan could still return here.”

Green immediately expressed his thoughts when Zhao Hai told him about the matter. Green continued, “Young master, all great families must start from the bottom and build themselves bit by bit. In the past, the Buda Clan fell into this situation since we didn’t have the Space, it was impossible for us to retreat immediately back then. But young master, you currently have the Space, we don’t need to fear about anything, you should grasp this opportunity.”

Zhao Hai didn’t think that Green would say this, but seeing that Green agreed to his plan, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and just nodded as he said, “Alright, when I get to the ship tomorrow, I’ll go and see Charlie’s attitude. If I like his bearing, then I’ll go help him.”

Green nodded, he looked at Zhao Hai with his eyes shining and said, “Young Master, tomorrow your poison will get cured. But what would happen in the ship?”

Zhao Hai smiles and said, “It doesn’t matter. When the time to detoxify comes tomorrow, I’ll just go to the Space, not a huge trouble.”

Green nodded, “You should be careful with the procedure. This is too important for us, as well as to the future of the Buda Clan.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “Grandpa Green, rest assured, there will be no problems. The Space has never failed me before, there’s no reason for it to fail this time.” Green nodded.

…

Next morning, Zhao Hai and the others went out of the hotel early. Then they headed straight to the Haven. The Haven was just moored to the dock without interference. It looks like the fee that they paid was quite worth it.

Zhao Hai paid the supervisor before boarding the boat and wait for Charlie. When they docked the ship here, they already paid, now that the wanted to depart, they need to pay again, this dock is really too black hearted.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t care, it was just a small charge. Currently, he wanted to know when Charlie would arrive. And just as he was thinking about this, a very ordinary carriage arrived and went right beside the Haven, then Liru came out of it.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he immediately gave the command to bring the carriage straight into the ship. Liru drove the carriage to the ship then Zhao Hai immediately set sail.

Only after they left the dock and entered the sea did Charlie get out of the carriage and smiled to Zhao Hai as he said, “I don’t have any choice in my actions this time, I hope mister can forgive me.”

Zhao Hai smiles and replied, “Not a problem. Your Highness, please.” Then he led Charlie to the cabin. After the Haven got modified, the cabin of the Haven wasn’t like those on the other ships anymore. Installed inside was a living room as well as a dining room.

When Charlie saw this part of the ship, he was startled, he didn’t think that such a scene was possible inside a ship. When he sat down, Meg immediately gave him a cup of tea. After drinking a mouthful, he smiled and said, “Mister’s ship is very nice. I have been on many ships before, it was only this time that I felt very comfortable.”

Zhao Hai replied as he gave a smile, “Your Highness praises too much. The ship was only modified like this because I have some undead crew on board. They don’t need to rest so there’s no need to have cabins for their use. With that, I had so much free space.”

Charlie stared blankly, he didn’t notice that those crew were unexpectedly undead. After hearing Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but be surprised and asked, “It seems like Mister’s Dark Magic has reached a high level. I actually thought that the crew on board were ordinary people.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The undead on the ship are previously the original crew of the ship. In fact, I only had this ship recently, back when Grand Duke Lionheart was still alive. It was because of him that I had acquired this ship.”

Charlie was puzzled, he asked, “Grand Duke Lionheart? But why do I see that this ship seems to have the workmanship of the Ocean Waves Dynasty? Did Lionheart have some relation to the dynasty?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “A little bit. When Lionheart ran away from his territory, he wanted to board this ship to run away. In the end, I caught up to him and he couldn’t escape anymore. I killed him and his group, naturally, the ship was turned over to me.”

Charlie’s eyes flashed, “Grand Duke’s demise was because of you? I thought that the Calci Family were the ones responsible for his execution. As it turns out, it was actually mister. May I know what rank Mister is right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “8th rank. I’m just an 8th rank Mage, hehe, I hope that your highness wouldn’t laugh at me.”

Charlie actually laughed, “Mister is too polite. I think that the continent hasn’t heard of a person as young as mister that has reached 8th rank before. Mister really brings a lot of surprises.”

Zhao Hai replied, “I’m not counting on that. At least I know of some people in the Radiant Church who had reached that level who aren’t older than me.”

Charlie stared  blankly, this was the first time that he had heard of this matter. He couldn’t help but change his expression as he asked, “Can mister tell me about it in detail? Mister should know that because of the current matter, my Rosen Empire and the Radiant Church is not very happy with each other. I’m afraid that something will happen soon.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your highness should have heard that I came from Aksu Empire. When I offended the Radiant Church and was forced to run to the Beastman Prairie. I didn’t expect that the Radiant Church would send someone to hunt me down, and it was surprisingly a 9th rank expert. Fortunately for me, they violated a beastman taboo, so the 9th rank was killed by another 9th rank beastman. After he died, I turned him into an Advanced Level Undead. From his own mouth, I heard of a thing called the Ultimate Weapon plan that the Radiant Church had been operating these past years.”

Charlie sternly listened to Zhao Hai’s words. Upon hearing Zhao Hai mention the Ultimate Weapon plan, his expression changed. He looked straight at Zhao Hai and said, “Ultimate Weapon Plan?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, the Ultimate Weapon plan. This plan selects innately talented children from the entire continent. They train these children as well as had the church’s potion masters and artisans experiment on them. They plan to develop way to mass produce 9th rank experts. Those who failed would be at least 7th or 8th rank. Majority of those who failed would end up as crippled, some would even die from the process.”

Charlies expression continued to worsen, he asked further, “Mister, are you really talking about the Radiant Church? Haven’t they always said that they are the servants of the Radiant God and thus would save people? Why would they do such a thing?”

Zhao Hai gave a bitter smile and answered, “This is only a pretense that they use. The talk about being the servant of the Radiant God and saving people is all nonsense. The bad things that they did are no less than what the Dark Mages did. I’ll be open to your highness, a lot of those notorious Dark Mages in the continent are all cultivated by the Radiant Church. They trained those Dark Mages and made them go out into the continent and perform heinous acts to dirty and corrupt the reputation of the other Dark Mages. With this, not only did they make the populace hate the Dark Mages, they also slowly reduced their numbers, and hoping to eventually reach their goal of fully exterminating them.”

Charlie’s eyes couldn’t help but shrink, he asked with a deep voice, “Are mister’s words serious?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “No statement from them is true. Your highness, do you know why I left the prairie and went straight to Rosen Empire?”

Charlie replied, “Isn’t it because of the Calci Family?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “That is one reason, the other reason is because compared to all the nations in the continent, the influence of the Radiant Church on the Rosen Empire is the weakest. Rosen Empire is the most powerful nation in the continent, their own nobles had their own pride, therefore there would only be a few of them that would join the Radiant Church. Not like other nations where their highest officials are all members of the Radiant Church. Southern King of Aksu Empire is one of the members of the Church’s Knight’s Congregation. He held a high status in the church and thus in other nations. It was because of this that I came to Rosen Empire.”

Charlie stood up and paced around the room as he muttered, “How could this be? This way, the Church would control the entire continent sooner or later. What fierce move by the Radiant Church.”

The empire’s anti-Radiant Church movement wasn’t taken seriously by Charlie previously. In his view, the Radiant Church can only do so much inside Rosen Empire. But now, it seems like it was a completely different matter. Luckily, they had been suppressing the Church. This thought brought a cold sweat to Charlie’s back.

Although it can be said that the empire had been suppressing the Church for many years, they didn’t investigate them thoroughly. They were so sure that the church wouldn’t be a threat. Charlie never imagined that the church had this hidden agenda going on.

After walking a few more paces, Charlie turned his head to Zhao Hai, “Mister, who else knows of this information?”

Zhao Hai gave a smile, “Your Highness, who do you think hates the Church the most inside the Rosen Empire ? Of course it is the Calci Family. Some of these matters were only known to them quite recently, but some was already known by the family for a long time.”

Chapter 396: Business

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai, he knew that Zhao Hai should have just acquired this information recently. He stared and asked, “Why are you telling me this?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “I have an enmity with the Radiant Church, they wanted me gone as soon as possible. In order to preserve my life, I have to pull more people into going against the Church. I’m telling these information to your highness in the hopes that you would also help me deal with the church.”

Charlie stared at Zhao Hai for a moment, then he gave a laugh and said, “Alright, haha, no big deal. Mister can rest assured, if the church is really as overbearing as what you just described, then it is naturally my duty to deal with them. But mister should know that I’m just a prince, the things that I can do are quite limited.”

Zhao Hai looked at Charlie while Charlie also looked at him, Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “Your highness, if you need my abilities, I’ll try my best to help.”

When two wise people talk to each other, less words were required to convey a message. Charlie knew what Zhao Hai meant, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Charlie thanks mister. Mister, you should know that I need quite a bit of money right now. Do you have any business opportunities that you could provide me?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Your highness is too polite. Haha, but I like your personality, direct and with no false pretenses. What business does your highness want? I’m thinking about cooperating on Merfolk products such as magic beasts, pearls and so on. What do you think about this?”

Charlie stared blankly before his eyes lit up. One could even see his eyes turn into gold coins. Nobody could blame him, merfolk products are too valuable in the continent.

The continent is very big, making its coastline quite long. However, one could easily forget that there were mages who could use their spells to harvest these marine products by the tons. This made these products as cheap as the price of cabbage.

But as time passed, those marine resources were all overfarmed to depletion. The only place that they were available belonged to the sea-dwellers, and humans wouldn’t dare to approach that part of the sea. Since nobody wanted to go, the scarcity of these marine products made their prices skyrocket. Presently, there were almost no cities in the continent that had a market for these products, people were too reluctant to sell their share.

Now that he heard Zhao Hai propose a partnership regarding these products, Charlie immediately understood the amount of wealth involved. But he quickly sobered up, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, these merfolk are not fond of playing jokes, you say you got it from the deep seas? You’ll scour them yourself? Sir, doing that isn’t wise, if you anger those merfolk, huge troubles will arise.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “It’ll be alright, be relieved, all of these are legit. You forgot that I’m a Dark Mage. Since my crew didn’t need to eat food, my food stockpile could last me for about a year and a half. In that time I can go to the deep seas and make my undead dive down for those resources. There’s no need for me to find them myself.”

When heard Zhao Hai, Charlie didn’t add more. In the past, those who were willing to scour the coastline for marine products were those weak mages or apprentices. Since they couldn’t do anything great with their magic, they would just go to the sea and make some money.

But for truly strong mages, they didn’t stoop so low. These mages were already invited by nobles to sponsor them.

Also, those weak mages would only get cheap products from the sea that weren’t that valuable, so they generally won’t go into the deep sea, their ships also couldn’t go there. After all, they could still earn some change with the fishes in the coastlines.

After a brief pause, Charlie opened his mouth, “Very well, I can cooperate with mister in this venture. How do you want our cooperation to be? Will you sell me the products? Or would we distribute them together? I think it’s better if you give me your supply while I sell it, then we divide the profits. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, let’s go with the latter, I’ll give you my supply then you sell it. How do we divide the profits, half?”

Charlie replied, “I thinks that’s no good. You are the one who got them, doing all the hard work. Me having half the profits wouldn’t be appropriate.”

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “It doesn’t matter, then we’re all set. Also, you highness, I wouldn’t be able to give you a lot of fire fishes, otherwise their value in the continent would drop. I suggest that you place this business on other people’s hands, I have a good deal for you in return.”

Charlie asked, “Other business? What?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Right now I have a lot of grains and vegetables on hand. If you want these, I can supply you. Of course, I’ll sell it in market price, and I swear that their quality is the highest in the continent.”

Charlie couldn’t help but smile faintly, “Mister, my business is mostly wholesale selling. Good quality wouldn’t make any difference, if I add my markup price, those merchants wouldn’t purchase it.”

Zhao Hai slapped his head, he actually forgot that the reputation of his high quality goods could only be used in Purcell Duchy. For the other people in the continent, they might not have heard of his Haven products. If he wanted to use his brand in Rosen Empire, it obviously wouldn’t work.

Zhao Hai could only smile bitterly and say, “Your highness, how about we brand my products with my Haven trademark? This way, the populace would know about my products.”

Charlie nodded, “I heard about mister’s Haven products when you are still in Purcell Duchy. If we start making the brand known, it would be good for both of us.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “Then I have no other good business at the moment. Although I have some rations, they are low-end products. They wouldn’t be able to make much money.”

Charlie smiled and said, “That’s fine. I heard that rations are quite popular with the mercenaries. How about giving me some?”

Zhao Hai looked at Charlie. Seeing the enthusiastic man in front of him, Zhao Hai could only give a forced smile and said, “Your Highness, you’ve got to be kidding. Rations are very easily produced, soon the continent would have loads of suppliers, we wouldn’t be able to make much profits in them. You won’t be able to have good benefits. Don’t worry, I won’t hide from you the fact that I’m currently developing a new type of liquor. If the development succeeds, then it will definitely be huge, all hotels in the continent would have it. The price isn’t very expensive, it is also very suitable for everyone. When that time comes, I’ll have this as an exclusive business with you, what do you think?”

Charlie’s eyes widened as he said, “Really? You have this kind of liquor?”

Zhao Hai smiles, “Of course I do. This liquor is just as fragrant as Milk Wine, but has a higher yield; this makes it quite cheap. If we make this, it would certainly be popular. Laura, please get a glass of beer for his highness.”

Laura calmly nodded as she prepared a glass of beer for Charlie. Charlie looked at the glass in front of him, the color was so bizarre that he had the thought of not drinking it. But to show that he trusts Zhao Hai, he could only lift the glass and took a sip with his eyes closed.

When the beer reached his mouth, Charlie felt a strange sour taste. He didn’t want to swallow it, but for the sake of politeness, he gulped the liquid down.

After the beer was drank, Charlie noticed a strange smell. The smell was quite peculiar, it wasn’t a good smell, but it definitely made you want to take a second drink.

WIthout thinking about it, Charlie took another sip, then the smell came again. Charlie could only stop himself as he placed the glass down and said, “It really has a special taste, but I’m afraid that common people wouldn’t like it.”

Zhao Hai only smiles and said, “This is because it is still in development, the acidic flavor is still there. Upon completion, that flavor would not be there anymore.”

When Charlie heard Zhao Hai’s assurance, he became more interested, “If that is so, then this business would definitely be very good. But I seem to feel that this liquor wouldn’t survive long times in storage.”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “Your majesty is half wrong. Preserving this liquor is both easy and difficult. If this is stored in a tightly sealed container, then it could be preserved for a long time. If the seal is faulty, then the flavor wouldn’t be good.”

Charlie nodded, “So that’s how it is. Then that’s good. Sealing a container isn’t a difficult thing. Then I will be anticipating mister’s good news.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, if the research succeeds, I will immediately supply you.”

Charlie smiled, “I’ll have to thank mister for today. All these money making businesses will be very helpful to me.”

Zhao Hai gave a slight chuckle and said, “It’s no big deal, after all, I still have to sell them somewhere right? Haha.”

Charlie returned the smile and said, “No matter what, mister has my gratitude.”

Zhao Hai laughed as he said, “I could also supply your highness with some bulls and argali, but those still have to wait until spring.”

Charlie smiled, “Good. Although bulls and argali aren’t in very high demand, their sales are still very good. As long as we have supply, we won’t worry about selling them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “These businesses are enough for some people to be green with envy. I advise your highness to be careful. Make sure that people wouldn’t group up against you, or else you’ll going to be in deep trouble.”

Charlie frowned, but he couldn’t help but agree to Zhao Hai’s suggestion. That situation can be very easily reached. .

Chapter 397: Second Prince

What Zhao Hai said was true, all of those businesses that he proposed were indeed subject to envy. At present, all of the candidates for the throne had the same strengths and position. Nobody was particularly superior to the others. But if Charlie were to start these businesses, his position would certainly surpass his other brothers. This may force the others to group up to keep him in check, it would be troublesome.

However, Zhao Hai’s businesses were really lucrative. Letting these benefits go would truly be a waste, this placed Charlie in a dilemma.

Zhao Hai looked at Charlie and smiled, “Your highness doesn’t need to think about it too much. In the end, the final result isn’t up to you, you should just go about your own matters.”

Charlie nodded then sighed, he understood what Zhao Hai meant. The outcome of the struggle for the throne was indeed not up to the candidates. His father was still not old, he could still continue to become emperor for 20 years. In 20 years, nobody can really know what will happen, so there’s no particular forecast that can be made.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You highness, when we reach Jade Water City, I might need your help in opening my shop.”

Charlie smiled, “Mister can rest assured, I got you covered.”

As he said this, an alarm could be heard outside. Zhao Hai turned his head to his side as Shun immediately ran out.

Charlie just calmly sat there. After a short while Shun came back and reported, “Young Master, there are several ships from the harbor approaching as. They look to be pursuing our ship, possibly wanting to surround it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So the alarm was for us. Let’s go see who it is.”

After he stood up, Charlie followed suit and also stood up. Zhao hai turned his head and said, “Your Highness, you should stay in the cabin this time. This may not be necessarily because of you. You will get exposed if you show yourself.”

Charlie nodded as he sat back down. Then Zhao Hai led Laura and the others outside, leaving Charlie behind.

Liru frowned and asked, “Your Highness, do you think we’re in danger?”

Charlie shook his head, “I’m not sure, we could only know later. I believe that mister’s strength is enough to ensure our safety.”

Although Liru was worried, he didn’t talk anymore and just nodded. He didn’t know that because of the upgrades in the Space, a lot of Zhao Hai’s undead already had the strength of 8th rank. Also, Zhao Hai still had Cai’er and Zhao Wen. With all of these added together, there weren’t a lot of people that could deal with Zhao Hai in this world.

When Zhao Hai came out of the living room, he calmly stared at the ships that had encircled the Haven. The ships weren’t battleships, just five-masted ironclad cargo ships, like Zhao Hai’s Haven. For someone to be able to mobilize this number of ships made Zhao Hai quite surprised.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid, even if these ships were armed, they were useless. Zhao Hai’s undead had already reached 8th rank because of the Space, with these undead on hand, Zhao Hai could even destroy a small kingdom, not to say these ships.

Zhao Hai didn’t move, he waited the other party to approach him. He just stood calmly as he had the Haven’s sails taken down.

Before long, the closest ship in the encirclement went towards the Haven. Zhao Hai observed the vessel. On its deck were a group of people, the most noticeable person was 30-year old man with a face closely resembling Charlie. Their figures were very similar with each other, he had ordinary clothes on but feels very different when he wore it. And most importantly, the commanding aura that this person had wasn’t any less than Charlie’s.

Upon seeing this person, Zhao Hai knew that the man didn’t come for them, but instead for Charlie. This man was possibly Charlie’s second brother, the Rosen Empire’s Second Prince.

Zhao Hai took a deep breath and bowed towards the man who he suspected to be the second prince, “May I know who mister is? Why did you surround my ship? Didn’t you know that this is Rosen Empire’s waters?”

The supposedly second prince revealed a curious look when he heard Zhao Hai, after some time, he replied, “Are you Zhao Hai? You’re quite brave, nobody asks me for explanations while inside Rosen Empire. But feel relieved, I did not come for you today.”

When Zhao Hai heard the other party’s words, his suspicions were confirmed. He couldn’t help but smile faintly and say, “I really don’t know why I need to be relieved, I’m just an ordinary merchant doing proper business. I didn’t skip on taxes, nor have I become a spy, I didn’t kill people and burn places. I really don’t understand what merits me to be afraid.”

The Second Prince looked at Zhao Hai’s eyes and said seriously, “Boy, I’m not here to find you today. Go and make Little Three come out immediately. He came to my Rising Water city without meeting me, isn’t he being impolite?”

Just as Zhao Hai was about to reply, Charlie walked out from the ship. He showed a faint smile and bowed, “I’ve seen second brother, I just went for a short visit in the city. I didn’t want to disturb you.

The Second Prince looked at Charlie and laughed, “Is it really just a short visit and nothing else? Then why did mister Zhao Hai immediately leave Rising Water City and head towards Jade Water City?”

Charlie gave a smile and said, “I just unintentionally met mister Zhao Hai and invited him to do business in my Jade Water City. For convenience, I rode on his ship. What’s wrong about that? Is it worth second brother dragging all of these people here?”

The Second Prince coldy snorted and retorted, “Little Three, your words are useless. Without even looking into mister Zhao Hai, I could tell at a glance that you just took him from me. This seems very insincere.”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but force a smile and said, “Mister should be the Second Prince right? Your highness, I am a merchant, and isn’t it up to me where I do my business? By your words, it seems like if I go to Rising Water city, then I am obligated to do business there, and not head to other places. With this logic, since I came to Sky Water City first, then should I do business there forever? Where did the second prince get the fact that I was stolen?”

The Second Prince looked at Zhao Hai, “Zhao Hai, there’s no use to keep speaking. Behave yourself and stay in Rising Water City, I promise to not take action then. Otherwise, you wouldn’t be able to do business in the Rosen Empire anymore, believe me.”

Zhao Hai just smiled slightly and replied, “i don’t believe you.” Very simple words, but they made the Second Highness’ heart explode with rage, he looked at Zhao Hai with a reddened face.

Charlie didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually go against the second prince, this moved him a bit. At the same time, he was scared. He knew that he wanted to get Zhao Hai’s support, he didn’t want him to suffer an accident.

Charlie immediately inserted, “Second Brother, speak straight, why did you come today? This matter had nothing to do with Zhao Hai, what do you really want from me?”

The Second Prince coldly replied, “Little Three, don’t be too complacent, I know that you’re the favorite. I won’t touch you, since if you let father know, I’m finished. But no matter what, Zhao Hai must go back to Rising Water City with me.”

Charlie replied, “Impossible. I don’t have a deep influence on mister Zhao Hai. Going with me is his own decision, I didn’t pressure him.”

The Second Prince snorted, “Hmph, if you’re not pressuring Zhao Hai, then why are you riding his ship towards Jade Water City? Why did he leave Rising Water City when he had just arrived there? Who doesn’t know that he just had a falling out with the Calci Family. This time, when he came to Rising Water City, it was definitely to establish business. But now you’re pulling him towards Jade Water City, who wouldn’t see that you’re in the wrong?”

Charlie just showed a faint smile, “There are a lot of people doing business between Rising Water City and Jade Water City. Can’t you think that this is the situation this time, second brother? Also, you’re talking about being wrong? I don’t know why Mister Zhao Hai wanted to leave Rising Water City, but you stopping him is something that you shouldn’t be doing.”

The Second Prince looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, do you really want to side with Little Three?”

Zhao Hai looked at the Second Prince and smiled, “Your highness, I’m just a merchant. Chasing benefits is my job. When I looked at Rising Water City’s atmosphere, I decided that it isn’t suitable for my business, therefore I want to head towards Jade Water City to take a look. Why am I unable to do this? Also, what’s wrong with the Third Prince riding my ship?”

The Second Prince clenched his teeth when he heard Zhao Hai, “Good, Zhao Hai, good. You actually said that my Rising Water City isn’t suitable for business? What benefits did Little Three give you? I can give you the same conditions.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head secretly, the second prince is much worse than Charlie. He just knew about Charlie when he embarked on the ship, only then did he give chase. This meant that he wasn’t Charlie’s match, such person wasn’t an opponent for Charlie.

Zhao Hai bowed to the Second Prince and said, “Your Highness Second Prince, I just want to look at Jade Water City. Just like you said, me and the Calci Family currently have problems with each other. Thus, I want to choose another place to do business. However, I have not been to both Rising Water City and Jade Water City. This time, I only came to Rising Water City because it was the closest location, I didn’t intend to do business there. There was no need for the Second Highness so amass such show of force.”

The Second Prince looked at Zhao Hai while having a pale expression. “Good, good. I’ll let you go Zhao Hai. But just know who’s territory Rosen Empire belongs to.” Then he waved his hand as he departed to his ship.

Seeing the Second Prince leave, Zhao Hai gave a sigh. He was utterly disappointed with the Second Prince.

Chapter 398: Attitude

After Zhao Hai and Charlie returned to the ship’s living room, Charlie smiled apologetically to Zhao Hai, “Mister, what you just did placed you on the opposite side of my second brother. Second brother isn’t that broad minded, you need to watch out in the future.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is how people are. Some of them you become friends with, while some become your enemies. A truly friendly person only exists in stories.”

Hearing Zhao Hai, Charlie understood that Zhao Hai was showing his faith on him. Although Zhao Hai promised to help him, he wouldn’t be the same as his other people. Zhao Hai wants to have a degree of freedom in his actions as well as weight to his words. He wanted to be treated like equals.

Charlie also knew that people with Zhao Hai’s capabilities have their own pride. They will not accept being slaves that will be on other people’s beck and call. It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai said those words.

Charlie nodded, “Mister can feel relieved. I will guarantee mister’s safety. My second brother has underestimated by strength, mister can rest assured.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’m not that worried, to be honest. With the second prince’s current strength, he wouldn’t be able to do anything that could harm me. Your highness need not worry himself over my well-being

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Charlie couldn’t help but knit his brows, “Mister, you need to be careful in not underestimating my second brother too much. The cards on his hand aren’t weak, he isn’t any weaker than Grand Duke Lionheart.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “It doesn’t matter. As long as he doesn’t send a 9th rank expert to deal with me, then there’s no problem. Your highness shouldn’t worry.”

When Charlie heard Zhao Hai, he nodded. In truth, it wasn’t easy to request something from a 9th rank expert. When Grand Duke Lionheart was being hunted, the Calci and Shelley Families sent four 9th rank experts to kill Lionheart’s two 9th rank experts. Naturally, the two families paid a huge price.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s confidence, Charlie didn’t say anything more, he could see Zhao Hai’s strength with this point. Actually, by looking at the undead on the ship, Charlie wanted to gauge Zhao Hai’s strength. Unfortunately, the undead didn’t have any chance to exhibit their capabilities. But judging by their outer appearance, Charlie decided to not underestimate Zhao Hai.

Looking at the skies, it seems like lunchtime has arrived, so Zhao Hai invited Charlie to the dining area for a meal. Naturally, what they ate were nice meals; beef, mutton, fire fishes and various vegetables.

Charlie looked at the table and saw some dishes that he hadn’t eaten before, this made him curious. Rosen Empire was the largest nation in the continent, so there were a lot of dishes that was served at the capital. But now, seeing that there were unique dishes in front of him, it touched the third prince’s curiosity.

Of course, there were also fruit wine and milk wine served. On the other hand, the staple food was replaced with bread fruit. Zhao Hai wanted Charlie to taste food he hadn’t tasted before.

Charlie was very curious of the bread fruit. When he started eating the delicacies, he was very startled since they were actually quite delicious.

It was especially so for the bread fruit. Charlie saw that this was from a fruit tree, but for the specific tree, Charlie didn’t know.

After eating some fruit, Charlie placed it down and looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, what is this fruit? Why does it change like this?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “This thing is called a Bread Fruit, I named it myself, hehe. Currently, only I have these on hand. However, I don’t have enough output for now so I cannot sell these wholesale. What is more important about the fruit is that it is the main component for the beer that I am fermenting. This is also the reason why I am not preparing to push this product on the continent.”

Charlie didn’t expect that the bread fruit was actually a component for brewing beer. He nodded and said, “It really can’t be sold, it would be more valuable if made into beer.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, “Actually, the tree’s yield is very high, not slightly inferior to bamboo rice. But the tree is very demanding in regards to climate. It couldn’t just be grown anywhere, this makes its output very hard to increase.”

Charlie gave a nod then frowned, “Mister, wouldn’t this affect the beer’s output?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and replied, “It shouldn’t. I’m also researching about alternative materials to replace the bread fruit. And if we manage to do so, the bread fruit wouldn’t be wasted, we could just sell it since it is also quite a good product.”

Charlie nodded, “Truly a pity, this thing would be a fantastic thing to be made into army provisions. Not only could it increase the marching pace, it also tastes good.”

Zhai Hai smiled but didn’t agree, people’s mindsets are truly quite different. He didn’t think of using the bread fruit as army provision, and thinking of its advantages to the army, but Charlie did.

After finishing their lunch, Zhao Hai returned to his own room. Naturally, he gave Charlie a good room, one of the best rooms in the ship.

Upon entering his room, Zhao Hai immediately returned to the Space and went to the Processing Factory. He surveyed the situation and felt good, in a dozen or so hours, the Detoxification potion would finally be done.

Zhao Hai sat in the villa’s living room with Laura and the others by his side. When Zhao Hai took a sip from his cup of tea, Laura looked at him and said, “Brother Hai, we have already sided ourselves with Charlie, wouldn’t he be angry with your actions today?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I just did that to judge his attitude. I want to see what would make him angry. If he became angry because of my intentions, then it meant that he isn’t that broad minded. Even if I volunteered to help him, I would only do so sparingly. But if he was fine by it, then I’ll fully support him in ascending the throne.

Zhao Hai placed his teacup and sighed, “A superior person who isn’t broad-minded is no good, this also applies for those who always strive for control. I could only gauge him because of this.”

Laura nodded and didn’t say anything. What Zhao Hai said was reasonable, if Charlie as a higher up didn’t have a broad mind, like the Second Prince, then supporting him was not a good idea.

At this time, Meg stared towards the Processing Factory and sighed, “It is too slow, still more than 10 hours left. Why does time seem to flow too slowly, a minute feels like 10 years.”

Zhao Hai can only smile faintly as he said, “You’re over exaggerating, it’s fine. We have the afternoon, then dinner, then sleep. After waking up, the potion should be ready.”

Meg pouted her mouth, “That’s easy to say. Young master, go look at what the third prince is talking about.” Zhao Hai smiled and opened the monitor. The screen immediately turned to the Third Prince’s room. Charlie was sitting inside while drinking, Liru was beside him.

Charlie looked somewhat thirsty, at the same time, he relaxed himself. He didn’t think that the Second Prince would be alerted to his presence in Rising Water City. This was not good news for him.

Looking at Charlie’s appearance, Liru knew what he was thinking, he couldn’t help but whispered, “Your highness, now that the Second Prince has found out about us, we should inform Aonas, he may be in a dangerous situation.”

Charlie placed his cup down and shook his head, “No, this time we went to the city to do about ten actions. Second brother shouldn’t have known about Aonas.”

Liru nodded then looked at Charlie, “Your Highness, wasn’t Zhao Hai being too unreasonable today? He clearly expressed his intent to side with you, but his tone seems to be negotiating. He didn’t put himself into a subordinate’s position, it seems like he sees himself as your partner.”

At this point, Charlie showed a faint smile, “Isn’t this quite good? Liru, remember that people with ability would certainly hold a degree of pride. I couldn’t do anything to mister Zhao hai’s arrogance, he didn’t need me to survive in the first place. Although he is currently in a sort of conflict with the Calci Family, I am quite sure that they wouldn’t let go of him. the benefits that Zhao Hai brings are certainly too good. Also, even if he loses the Calci Family’s backing, the Shelley Family is still extremely friendly with him. With such a continent spanning family in good relationship with him, why would Zhao Hai care about a nation’s prince like me?’

Liru thought for a moment and had to agree with Charlie. The Shelley Family was a powerhouse whose influence has reached the entire continent. The family was quite formidable. If Zhao Hai maintains his friendly ties with the Shelley Family, even if he were to be ousted from the Rosen Empire, he wouldn’t worry about surviving on other nations. So long as he has the Shelley family on his back, he wouldn’t have any problems.

No matter how powerful the Radiant Church was, it would be impossible for them to exterminate all Dark Mages. Additionally, they were currently going after famous and notorious Dark Mages, they didn’t have the time to deal with the mysterious Zhao Hai.

Charlie breathed out a sigh and leaned his body on the chair. “Having Zhao Hai help me should be the most correct decision I could make. Have you seen second brother’s attitude? This meant that he has some people supporting his back. Poor brother, why couldn’t you realize that father is still very much alive and kicking? You will only get farther and farther away from the throne.”

After he said that, he slowly closed his eyes. Before long, a windy sound could be heard, Charlie surprisingly fell asleep. Liru immediately placed a blanket over the third prince’s body.

After Zhao Hai saw the scene, he immediately turned off the monitor. He took a deep breath and turned to Laura, “I didn’t think that Charlie would have such high view of me. But Laura, why did he say that that if the second prince had a faction behind him, the emperor would see him as a threat? Aren’t they father and son?”

Laura gave a stiff smile and said, “So what if they are father and son? Fathers and sons killing each other is very common in royal clans. Not to mention royal clans, even noble houses have these situations happening all the time. People would go crazy for a high position. Even if the Rosen Emperor is a father, he wouldn’t forgive those who threaten his position, no matter they be his brothers or sons, all of them would be dealt with.”

Zhao Hai sighed, then nodded, “It really is very stressful when one is a ruler. I believe that there are a lot of monarchs that hadn’t left their castle for their entire life. Their subordinates would just report about the happenings outside, not requiring them to check for it themselves. Who would’ve expected that the most pitiable people in the continent were actually the rulers?”

Laura smiled and said, “If others were to hear you, they would die laughing. Even if the king couldn’t go out of his palace, don’t forget that the entire kingdom belongs to him. Every single life inside it is in his hands. He gives life as well as takes it. Having the authority over a person’s life would make anyone intoxicated. Otherwise, why do you think a lot of people wanted to be a monarch?”

Zhao hai chuckled and said, “Who knows? I don’t want to be like that anyway. I want my future situation to be just like now, free to walk around and wander about. We can just drink wine and sit while chatting. Isn’t this a better situation?”

Laura smiles, “Only you would think about this kind of life. There are a lot of people in the continent that don’t want that. But, this is also good, I used to be busy with my business everyday in the past, but now, I didn’t need to worry about a lot of things.”

Zhao Hai gave a forced smile and replied, “That may not be true for long, we already strive to have our own kingdom. My head couldn’t help but ache when thinking about the day that will be realized. Sigh. Anyway, Laura, when can your subordinates gather so that we could fetch them?”

Laura thought for moment then said, “I have given them ten days to prepare. This time, I had almost all of them come. Some are very far while some are just nearby, they still need some time to gather. Right, how is Uncle Evan doing?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “He told me that he didn’t want those people to leave. But he is still the Purcell Family’s Patriarch, he needed to take the family into account. Thus, he had no choice put call the elder’s assembly, and they agreed on letting your people go. I reckon Uncle Evan isn’t very happy right now.”

Laura could only smile, “Of course he is not happy, Uncle Evan’s temperament is just like a warrior. He wanted to place loyalty first, but he is currently shackled by the family’s interests which completely contradicts his character. It would be strange if he would be happy. On the other hand, when will he take Ruyen away?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile, “Ruyen is already on a ship. I really find Ruyen’s situation quite funny. Back when I was Adam, she ruthlessly wanted to end her engagement with me. Now that I’m Zhao Hai, she did her best to avoid me. It really is interesting.”

Chapter 399: Waiting

Upon listening to Zhao Hai, Laura and the others laughed. They knew that Zhao Hai was just talking casually and didn’t express that he had any interest in Ruyen. Just like what Zhao Hai told them before, Ruyen wasn’t worth Zhao Hai’s attention.

However, Laura asked, “Who did Uncle Evan send to get her? We still need to take care of her well-being, she should arrive in perfect condition. If anything happens to her, it wouldn’t be good for us.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It’ll be fine. I will send some Blood Hawks to follow her. If there’s anything wrong, we can immediately help.”

Laura smiled, “I think there’s no need for Elder Brother Hai to go, we can just send the Swordfish. Swordfish ships were even used to escort the emperor, I think there won’t be any problems with it. This way we can sort of help with their situation. Having blood hawks carry your ghost staff around is very inconvenient for us. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai agreed, “This is a good idea. We have a lot of ships in our hands, and some of them would be rarely used. It should be a good idea to use them this time around.”

Laura smiled and said, “If you send that many ships, the Aksu Empire would get nervous. They might think that a princess from Rosen Empire had come to visit Aksu Empire.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, they couldn’t blame him. Currently, he has 11 three masted ships and 4 five-masted ships on hand. This number is too astonishing.

Although the three-masted battleships were only the most common type, they were still battleships. Also, the five-masted ironclad merchant ships aren’t easily bought and used by just anyone.

The cost of iron armor is too high, moreover they needed to be serviced every year. It was the same scenario if they underwent a battle, they would have to be serviced again. Because of this, no average person can take care of these ironclad ships. Even if you didn’t use your ship, the maintenance cost of the ship was still very high.

Therefore, most five-masted ironclad ships are in the possessions of Great Families. Even Zhao Hai’s Haven ship once belonged to a Great Family in Ocean Waves Dynasty before it changed hands.

If he sent all these ships to escort Ruyen, the Aksu Empire would certainly think that a princess had just come for a visit, and this is not an exaggeration.

After speaking of this, Zhao Hai immediately called over a blood hawk and released it to find Ruyen’s ship. The hawk was very fast, they didn’t need to wait for the evening to find Ruyen’s vessel.

Although Ruyen rode on a ship, the vessel was just an ordinary three-masted cargo ship. It didn’t have any special features. Aside from Ruyen, there were also some guards and servants that came along to meet her. When Zhao Hai looked closely, he could notice some Purcell Family elders that were 8th rank, all of them were warriors.

Such strength wasn’t bad, 8th ranks were already considered to be experts on the continent. Only an anomaly like Zhao Hai would consider them as subpar.

Now that they spotted Ruyen, Zhao Hai didn’t make his move immediately. He would wait until dark before he’ll release the Swordfish to catch up to Ruyen’s ship so nobody would notice.

Seeing that it was already late, Zhao Hai and the others came out of the Space. Not long after Zhao Hai went out, Charlie also came out of his room looking very well rested.

Zhao Hai immediately had the some chairs brought to the deck. The group sat on down and chatted with each other while enjoying the seascape. At the same time, they also ate dinner.

After having their dinner, Charlie returned to his room to rest. Zhao Hai also returned to his room, and since it was currently dark, he needed to find an appropriate time to release the Swordfish that would escort Ruyen.

Since the skies were still turning dark, Zhao Hai didn’t hurry. He observed the situation on Ruyen’s ship. It may have been because of her recent experiences, but Ruyen had become more mature. Her change was too noticeable that the servants who came for her immediately felt it. She is much quieter than before, she also became more considerate. She was very polite to the servants, which made them quite flattered.

But Zhao Hai didn’t care about these changes, he only cared about Ruyen’s security. As long as Ruyen didn’t suffer an accident, then all is good.

After the skies turned pitch black, Zhao Hai looked for an area not too far from Ruyen’s ship and released the Swordfish.

He also called out a blood hawk and sent it towards Purcell Duchy. In a few days, Laura’s people would arrive and they needed to be transported using the ghost staff.

After doing all of these, Zhao Hai didn’t know what else to do. Even if it was already dark, he didn’t have the urge to sleep, this applied to Laura and the others as well. This was because they were waiting for the sun to rise in the morning, by then the detoxification potion would be finished.

While thinking of these, the group just sat on the living room and looked at each other. They couldn’t help but laugh.

Zhao Hai opened his mouth, “We shouldn’t be waiting for the result in here. Let’s go to our rooms and rest. When we wake up tomorrow morning, the detoxification potion should be finished.”

Laura nodded and stood up, “We cannot just sit here the entire evening, we need to rest. Also, Brother Hai, when you consume the potion tomorrow, you should call Grandpa Green’s group over, otherwise they wouldn’t forgive you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that Laura was speaking the truth. If he didn’t call Green and the others over, they would certainly complain to him for their entire lifetime.

The group returned to their respective rooms and the Space became peaceful. Zhao Hai was lying on his bed and thinking about all of what happened when he arrived at Ark Continent. Before long, he fell asleep.

…

For who knows how long, Zhao Hai suddenly woke up. He looked out of the window and saw a bright sky.

Zhao Hai went out of his room and turned the monitor on. The outside sky was also bright, but not that much, it seems like it was still very early morning.

He immediately went outside and walked towards the Processing Factory. Surprisingly, Shun was already standing there, looking at the digits that were constantly changing. It was obvious that the potion was still not ready.

Seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Shun immediately bowed and said, “Young Master.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and asked, “You didn’t rest?” He looked at the digits that showed 2 hours.

With an embarrassed face, Shun replied, “I couldn’t fall asleep, so I came out to have a look. I hope I didn’t disturb young masters rest.”

Zhao Hai shook his head with a smile. At this time, footsteps could be heard. Zhao Hai turned his head to see Laura and the others approaching. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile upon looking at their appearance. Laura and Meg also smiled towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai chuckled and said, “Well, we still have two hours. Let’s go to Iron Mountain Fort and wake up Grandpa Green and the others.” The group nodded and with a thought, Zhao Hai moved them to Iron Mountain Fort.

Upon arriving at the fort’s living room, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. Aside from Green and the two elders, Karen was also present. Seeing Zhao Hai and the others arrive, Karen stared before he opened his mouth, “Why did you just arrive now? We had been waiting for the whole evening.” [1]

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled, “It’s nothing, I just went to bed. I just happen to wake up early today. Grandma Merine, please whip up something to eat. After breakfast, we’ll head back to the Space.”

Merine nodded with a smile on her face. Then she called Meg and Laura over to the kitchen. Laura was currently studying how to prepare food. Even though she had no talent, and the food that she made were mostly inedible, she still studied diligently.

Looking at Merine and the others preparing the food, Zhao Hai turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, how is the beer’s progress doing?”

Green smiled and said, “The time is too short. The liquor needs to be fermented for a while. This time, we did a few experiments to find out which materials are useful. We tried bamboo rice, barley, bread fruit, spatial water, ordinary water, cold water, as well as warm water. I believe there should be at least one of those that will succeed.

Zhao Hai smiled, “That’s good. As long as we succeed, then it’s fine. Also, what container do you plan on storing the beer in? We should make sure to seal the beer properly, otherwise we would only be selling low quality beer.”

Little Jin wasn’t present at this time. Because of the transmission point on Ape Island, Zhao Hai would know what Little Jin was doing.

Green replied, “Rest assured, we will not have any issues with this. At first, we wanted to use a wooden barrel but there seems to be some issues with the lid. Now we’re currently finding ways to improve it, you don’t have to worry.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then sighed,. “As long as we make this beer properly, it could certainly be our Buda Clan’s biggest source of income . The future demand for this thing wouldn’t be any less than that of grain.”

Karen looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you really sure? I’ve tasted that thing, it is too acidic, not really tasty.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “When the beer ferments properly, you’ll be convinced. There are only a few people who could resist the temptation of beer.”

After the group chatted for a while, Merine brought the dishes. Zhao Hia and the others immediately went to the dining hall. Upon finishing their breakfast, they went to the Space and gathered around the Processing Factory.

In the Multipurpose Processing Machine, the digits shown had become 20 minutes. The group couldn’t sit well inside the villa, so they just stood inside the Processing Factory and waited, they waited for the countdown to reach zero.

* * *

Laura’s father

Chapter 400: Pleasantly Surprised

Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven. Six. Five. Four. Three. Two. One!

The heartbeat of all those present synchronized with the ticking down of the timer. When the number turned to zero, they even felt as though their hearts have stopped.

A white light flashed inside the Processing Factory, then a small bottle appeared on the ground. The bottle was quite small, about the size of a palm, it had a flat bottom. Seeing through its transparent body, one could see a blue liquid. At this time, a prompt was heard, “Special Purpose Detoxification Potion for the Water of Nothingness completed, administer orally, one time use. After ingestion, toxin shall be removed, impurities will be discharged. At the same time, Host’s body will be strengthened, advised to take the potion along with a Goldmetal Fruit, the effects will be better.”

Zhao Hai stared, but he immediately took the small bottle and gazed at the blue liquid inside it. Green and the others also stared at the liquid with bated breath, probably afraid that the bottle would disappear if they breathed strongly..

Zhao Hao turned his head to look at the others, he showed a faint smile, “I think that the Space wouldn’t deceive me, I should go buy a Goldmetal Fruit. Then I will go consume the two of them together, what does Grandpa Green think?”

Green looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, what are you planning on practicing, Magic or Battle Qi?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Battle Qi, of course. Now that I can use 8th rank Magic by using the Space, it would be redundant to learn Magic. I seem to remember about you saying that our family has the Wild Dragon Battle Qi being passed down, I hear that it’s very famous in the continent, I’ll train hard using that.”

Green’s eyes became wet as he laughed and said, “Good, good! Young Master is certainly worthy to be a Buda Clan member. I can teach you the true version of the Wild Dragon Battle Qi that our Buda Family has been secretly passing on.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he asked Green, “Grandpa Green, what did you say? What do you mean true version of the Wild Dragon Battle Qi? You mean that there’s another version that isn’t genuine?”

Green smiled faintly, “Right, our Buda Clan’s Battle Qi technique can be said to be one of the most famous techniques in the continent. Not only is the way it is practiced different, the attack strength of our technique is leagues better than most. Because of this, a lot of people became jealous. Thus, our Clan’s Wild Dragon Battle Qi has been divided into two versions. The first version is the simplified one, it has a weaker attack strength as well as a slow rate of practice. That version couldn’t compare to the true version of out Wild Dragon Battle Qi manual.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “That’s good to hear, but we still need to wait until my toxin gets removed. Teaching me when that time arrives wouldn’t be too late.” Then he took the bottle and headed to the villa’s living room along with the others following behind him.

Inside the living room, Zhao Hai placed the small bottle on the table first before opening the Spatial Store and buying a Goldmetal Fruit.

Now that the Goldmetal Fruit has been digitized, it could now be bought in the shop. However, it’s price wasn’t that cheap. At this moment, it was the most expensive thing in the shop, costing 10 thousand gold coins per fruit.

But Zhao Hai didn’t care about the price, he immediately bought the fruit and placed it beside bottle. He took the bottle and removed the cork. He looked at the liquid inside before raising his head and downing the liquid into his mouth.

It wasn’t until the bottle was empty before he placed it down. He flapped his lips but couldn’t taste any residual flavor. Then he took the Goldmetal fruit and took several bites one after another.

Every single person in the room looked at Zhao Hai eating the Goldmetal fruit. They just stayed in their place and stared at him.

Zhao Hai licked his lip, the fruit’s flavor was extremely good. It had a cool feeling as well as a sweet and sour flavor. This made Zhao Hai secretly want to eat another one.

Zhao Hai looked at the others’ appearance and couldn’t help but laugh, “I didn’t expect that the taste of this fruit would actually be very pleasant.” After he finished talking, he suddenly felt a rumbling sensation in his belly. Zhao Hai’s face changed before he charged towards the toilet while holding on to his stomach.

Inside the toilet, Zhao Hai immediately unbuttoned his pants and sat down. The stench that emanated from the toilet almost made Zhao Hai faint.

After ‘working hard’ for about 10 minutes, Zhao Hai was about to collapse, this wasn’t what he expected to happen. He immediately got some tissue paper from the Space and cleaned himself up. When he stared at what he just left behind, he felt very disgusted. What he saw was something black, akin to asphalt, it dispersed waves of gut retching odor. Zhao Hai could even swear that he just saw insects flying around the toilet.

Zhao Hai quickly covered the toilet and pressed the flush button. He also turned the exhaust fan on. When he felt that the air inside the restroom became better, he immediately walked out.

Although Zhao Hai felt that he was on the verge of collapsing, there was a sense of extreme relief that came about him. This weird feeling made him both uncomfortable and glad.

When he came out of the restroom, he saw Green and the others waiting for him. Seeing Zhao Hai come out, Green immediately inquired, “Young Master, how are you feeling? Are you alright?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m fine, I feel good, but I’m feeling very weak.” Meg immediately went forward to support Zhao Hai as they headed back to the living room. After Zhao Hai sat down, a glass of water was given to him.

After drinking the glass of water, Zhao Hai felt a bit better. Scratch that, it was a LOT better. He felt that he was full of strength, something he never felt before.

Green and the others stared at Zhao Hai. He placed his glass down and smiled, “I’m feeling so much better. That feeling earlier must have been the potion’s side effect. Now I feel that my body is overflowing in strength.”

Green’s heart was moved, he immediately said to Zhao Hai, “Young Master, I think the things that the Space produces are all very special. How about I impart the Wild Dragon Battle Qi Technique to you right now. Let’s see what results come up.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then Green quickly told Zhao Hai the instructions to practice the Wild Dragon Battle Qi Technique. Upon hearing the instructions, Zhao Hai was surprised, this was because this technique was unexpectedly quite the same as Earth’s Internal Strength techniques. Just like how it was described in martial arts novels, the technique practices the body through the various acupoints inside.

In Ark Continent, before one practices their Battle Qi through the acupoints, one needed to train their bodies first. Once their bodies have reached a certain rank, then they could train their Battle Qi. As long as they establish a minor cycle of qi within their bodies, then they would have reached minor mastery. This rank gives the person close to 5th rank in strength.

However, the Wild Dragon Battle Qi was different, this technique didn’t need you to train your body first. Everybody was able to practice this technique, naturally, those who had innate talent in cultivation would have much faster progress than those who had worse.

Zhao Hai had read a lot of Battle Qi techniques these past few days, so one could say that he had a bit of understanding about Battle Qi. Simultaneously, he had already memorized all of the acupoints inside a human’s body. This was because knowing those points were tantamount to cultivating Battle Qi.

Now that Green imparted the technique to him, he immediately understood it. He remembered the route according to the technique and started to try to probe for the sensation that one needed to feel.

In practicing Battle Qi, the most difficult part wasn’t advancement, but this sensation that one must acquire so that they could embark on their cultivation journey. This sensation was nothing but ethereal, it relied completely on your internal senses. After many years of experimentation on the continent, they had found out that those who had good body strength were able to achieve this feeling easier. This was also the reason why most train their bodies before starting to train in Battle Qi.

Zhao Hai expected to have difficulties in feeling out the sensation, but he didn’t think that when he just started the process, something like ants crawling in his meridians were immediately felt. It evolved into a torrential flow before completing the first rank of the Wild Dragon Battle Qi technique.

Then, the second rank was attained, then the third, the fourth, the fifth, and it stopped at the sixth rank. Zhao Hai felt that he was being excessive and stopped advancing, then he continued to operate the six ranks of the technique.

Every time the technique made a revolution, Zhao Hai felt that his body’s battle qi increase by a point. He slowly felt the Battle Qi in his body becoming like a river that rushed along his meridians. The river was golden in color, with a few black, blue, cyan, and red colors mixed in.

The movement of this river became quicker and quicker, and when Zhao Hai felt that the river could break through his meridian’s limitation, he immediately attacked the 7th rank. Looking as though the river had fount an exit, it immediately rushed into the meridians and immediately broke through the 7th rank. When he broke through the 7th rank, the river began to calm down. However, Zhao Hai still felt that there was still enough power to go on. So he continued to circulate his Battle Qi along the 7th rank and slowly accumulated the quantity of qi inside his body.

Before long, when he felt like his limits were about to be broken through, Zhao Hai immediately started to attack the 8th rank.

The operation was very smooth as he quickly broke through to the 8th rank. Then the river of Battle Qi calmed down. Zhao Hai felt his own veins become sturdy, his skeleton hard, his muscles powerful, and his skin durable. However, this time, he felt that he could no longer continue on.

Zhao Hai was very confused, he didn’t know why all of these happened. Then suddenly, he thought about the Magic brought by the Space. The Magic of the Space had already reached 8th rank. Now, his Battle Qi has also reached the 8th rank, it seems like all of these were linked to the Space.

Upon thinking about this, Zhao Hai stopped his cultivation. He slowly opened his eyes and saw Green and the group looking at him anxiously. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but show a faint smile and said, “What happened? I’m fine, I just circulated by Battle Qi, everyone doesn’t need to be so nervous.”

Green forced a smile and asked, “Young Master, you didn’t JUST practice Battle Qi. You’ve been doing it for a full day and night. Young master, what Battle Qi rank have you reached?”

Chapter 401: Methods

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that he actually practiced for a full day and night. Upon hearing Green’s question, he smiled and said, “Grandpa Green, my Battle Qi has reached 8th rank.”

When Zhao Hai said his answer, everybody present were shocked. Each and every one of them stared blankly at Zhao Hai. After quite some time, Green’s two eyes lit up as he said, “Young Master, did your Battle Qi really reach 8th rank? Operate it for me, let me take a look.”

Zhao Hai nodded, as an 8th rank Warrior, he was able to achieve Battle Qi manifestation. With a thought, Zhao Hai made his golden Battle Qi go out of from within his body, lighting the room up with a golden light. Zhao Hai looked like a small sun, but without the extreme heat.

Since he didn’t have much experience, Zhao Hai took quite some time before withdrawing his Battle Qi. Nevertheless, Green was still grinning from ear to ear. With Zhao Hai achieving 8th rank, he could already be considered as an expert in the continent.

An 8th rank Warrior that can also use 8th rank Magic of multiple elements. Everytime Green thought about Zhao Hai’s enemies, he couldn’t help but feel pity.

After Zhao Hai retrieved his battle Qi, Green laughed and said, “It’s really 8th rank, 8th rank! Fantastic! Young Master, I propose that 2 hours every evening, me and Kun will come to the Space and teach you about fighting with Battle Qi.”

When Zhao Hai heard what Green just proposed, he couldn’t help but complain inside. But he also knew that Green was doing this for his own good. The Space can turn him from nothing to 8th rank in an instant but it couldn’t help him with fighting skills. If Zhao Hai only had Battle Qi but didn’t have any fighting skills, then he will never become a true expert. In a battle between Warriors, Zhao Hai would get easily defeated by a 5th rank.

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, Granpa Green can feel relieved, I’ll go call you and Grandpa Kun every evening. Right, Laura, did you give an explanation to Charlie?”

Laura who was sitting nearby smiled, “Be relieved, that matter is already solved. But Brother Hai, do you notice something different in the living room?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he looked around the living room. However, he didn’t seem to notice something strange. He looked at Laura with a confused expression.

Laura smiled and said, “Didn’t you notice that there aren’t any metallic things here?”

Zhao Hai observed carefully, and indeed, there weren’t any items made of metal in the living room. Still with a puzzled look, he turned to Laura, “What happened? Why aren’t there any metallic objects in the room? Did they affect my cultivation?”

Laura responded, “We were afraid that you’ll get battered to death by those metallic objects. You didn’t notice but when you practiced your Battle Qi, all the metallic things in the room came flying towards you as though are a huge human shaped magnet. Brother Hai, I think you should also train this new ability along with your Battle Qi. I suspect that you had acquired a Divergent Ability, one that can manipulate metals.”

Upon hearing Laura’s description, Zhao Hai’s mind couldn’t help but think of a certain white haired old man wearing a cloak on his whole body along with a strange helmet, a man that was named Magneto.

Back on Earth, Zhao Hai was enamoured with the X-men series. The main villain Magneto had left a deep impression on Zhao Hai. It was no wonder why Magneto was the first thing to pop into his mind when Laura told  him that he may have developed a metal manipulation Divergent Ability,

Magneto’s ability had always been envied by Zhao Hai, so when he found that he had the Marvel villain’s power, he was very excited.

At this time, Green said, “Young Master, I think you should head outside the Space and see the situation. Laura said that you were cultivating yesterday, if you don’t go out today, Charlie may find it suspicious.”

Zhao Hai immediately turned on the monitor and looked at outside. Seeing that it was already time for breakfast, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll return to the Space this evening for Fighting Practice and training for Metal Manipulation.”

Green smiled, “Don’t worry too much, you’re now 8th rank, an expert in the continent. As long as you train diligently in your fighting techniques, you won’t need to be anxious. I’m also hoping that the young master will practice his metal manipulation well, and don’t use it in front of people too much. Make that ability a secret weapon.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I already have a lot of methods right now, keeping one hidden won’t be a problem. Grandpa Green, you should also go back to Iron Mountain Fort. That place won’t function well without you people there.”

Green nodded, then Zhao Hai delivered the group back to Iron Mountain Fort. After doing so, he lead Laura and the others back to their room in the Haven, before heading towards the living room.

At this time, Charlie was also there. When he saw Zhao Hai, he immediately expressed his greetings, “How was mister’s practice? Did you gain some improvements?”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “A little bit. I have unknowingly neglected your highness yesterday, I hope you’ll accept my forgiveness.”

Charlie smiled and said, “It’s normal for a Mage to train closed-door for a day or two, mister doesn’t need to apologize. In a few days we will arrive at Jade Water City, mister coming out this time made me quite glad.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I just felt something, so I went for a short one day retreat. Your highness also knows that we’re currently at sea, so it wouldn’t be practical to close-up for a long time. Right, your highness, we should have breakfast together. How about we do some fishing after our meal?”

Charlie laughed, “Good, there should be quite a few fish at this part of the sea. I haven’t fished for a while, I wonder what mister’s fishing level is?”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “I can’t really fish. I just do it to kill some time. Hehe.” Afterwards, him and Charlie went to the dining room.

After having their breakfast, Zhao Hai and Charlie sat down by the ship’s stern to fish. Laura and the others were chatting at the side, while Shue and Shun were quietly serving them.

Now that the ship was continuously moving, it was naturally impossible for the group to catch anything. However, they were able to kill some time while doing so.

Looking at the blue sky, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but let out a long breath as he leaned on the chair and said, “Sometimes, I really feel tired when going around like this, not knowing where the future will take me. Your highness, do you think that this is how people should live?”

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and faintly smiled, “You can live how you want to live. But if you want to live a better life than others, then you need to work very hard for it. This is a truth of life.”

Zhao Hai smiled and didn’t add anything. Then suddenly, Zhao Hai saw something on the distance. It seems like there were several ships approaching, originally Zhao Hai didn’t worry for even a bit. They were currently sailing near the coastlines, seeing these number of ships were quite normal. However, Zhao Hai felt that something wasn’t right about these ships, they were heading directly towards the Haven without even slowing down.

Zhao Hai stared at the ships, constantly feeling that those ships weren’t up to something good. At this time, a sound came, warning the group that they have become the target of those ships.

Zhao Hai turned his head towards Charlie and said helplessly, “Your highness, it seems like our travel itinerary has become quite eventful. Let’s head to the cabin’s living room, let’s see who we’re dealing with here.”

Charlie didn’t object, he just faintly smiled and followed ZHao Hai towards the cabin. A moment later, a shot from a magic cannon was heard, then a ballista shot. Good thing that Zhao Hai’s ship was ironclad, quite strong against attacks, it should be quite fine for a few moments.

Before long, Jinan walked in from the outside and reported to Zhao Hai, “Young Master, the boats had hit us. What do we do?”

Zhao Hai’s complexion sank, “Hit us? And it also seems like we lost some undead. Your Highness, you sit here for a moment, I’ll go take a look.”

Charlie smiled, “I’ll go as well. This area is quite close to my Jade Water City’s domain, I want to take a look at the people who dared be so rampant.”

Zhao Hai didn’t object, both him and Charlie went to the deck outside. What met them was a scene where ships were surrounding and approaching Zhao Hai’s vessel. One of them were even heading towards their ship at a faster rate, intending to ram the Haven. On the opponent ship’s bow was a sharp conical point. One could see a glint of light upon the object, it was clearly made from metal.

On the ship was a Wind Mage, giving the ship added velocity. This made the ship move quickly.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation and wielded his staff. Immediately, their ship was surrounded by strong winds as it shifted it position. This made Charlie stare, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai was also able to use Wind element Magic, and it seemed like it wasn’t a weak spell either.

The exhibition didn’t end, after using Wind element Magic, Zhao Hai changed to using Water element Magic as he froze a big area of the sea’s surface. This gave the opponent’s ship difficulty in moving forward.

The other ship wasn’t that far from Zhao Hai’s Haven. Since they were at this distance, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to stop it. Zhao Hai’s magic only delayed its approach.

At this time, the opposing ship attacked with two water dragons. The dragons collided with the frozen sea, scattering frozen sludge all over the place.

Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. It seems like the opponent came prepared, there was actually a Water Mage along with the Wind Mage.

When it seems like the other party saw Zhao Hai’s group, they immediately directed the magic cannons and ballistas to his direction. Zhao Hai immediately waved his wand as it produced a blue-colored water shield. The other party’s cannons and ballistas were useless in the face of this protective shield.

The shield was made through the Space’s 8th rank magic. Shields made on this level weren’t that easily broken through.

After releasing the blue shield, Zhao Hai followed through by releasing his composite magic. Composite spells made by two elements were quite handy. For example, combining Wind element and Water element magic would create a tornado with icy blades inside it, this made the spell’s lethality increase.

Composite magics were very formidable. If two 4th rank spells were combined, then it wouldn’t be worse than a 6th rank spell. However, the difficulty of achieving such feat was very high. The user needs to be compatible with at least two elements of magic. Moreover, he also needed to have a high rank in both departments.

Obviously, these requirements were useless for Zhao Hai. It was the Space who provided the magic, so doing a composite spell was quite easy.

But one must know that Zhao Hai had been quite diligent in his study of magic. He tried out a lot of magics and even had them written down. All of Zhao Hai’s notes were compiled to the point that the contents could fit into a book.

Zhao Hai knew that magic was his main method of battle. Therefore, he was very meticulous in studying magic, he carefully recorded the effects and names of each spell. Then he came up with various composite magics using his findings.

This time, Zhao Hai released a Wind-Water composite magic. The tornado, along with its sharp icy blades, soared up into the skies and directly headed towards the opponent ships.

Zhao Hai didn’t use this spell in order to kill the people onboard the ships, but to deal with the ships’ sails. Once their sails were dealt with, then it would be impossible for the other party to outmaneuver them, much less hit them.

Naturally, the opponent hadn’t noticed Zhao Hai’s composite magic, they expected it to be just any ordinary tornado spell; used for stopping the advancement of their ships. But when the spell reached them, they realized how strong the spell actually was.

Crewmen who weren’t prepared to defend themselves were either injured or worse, killed, by the icy blades. The most annoying thing for these people was the fact that their sails were shredded by the composite spell.

Charlie had been watching Zhao Hai’s battle. Even without his undead, Zhao Hai was still a formidable figure. Without using his undead, he was still able to decommission the opponent ships.

But Zhao Hai didn’t plan on letting those people off. He wanted to know which power the other party belonged to and why they attacked him. After all, they damaged the Haven, it would cost a fortune to repair it.

After the sails of the ships were rendered useless, Zhao Hai immediately used his Water element magic in order to freeze the surface of the sea. Charlie didn’t understand what Zhao Hai wanted to do. At this time, Zhao Hai waved his staff as large quantities of undead appeared on the icy surface before they proceeded to overrun the opponents. Even though the ships were already close enough to place the undead there directly, Zhao Hai still deliberately did so since he didn’t want to show Charlie the full extent of his capabilities.

Seeing the present scene, Charlie couldn’t help but feel a cold sweat coming down his back. Zhao Hai’s method made him very startled. The method that Zhao Hai used was very effective in sea battles.

At the same time, Charlie thought that if Zhao Hai was this formidable at sea, then what would he be on land? It would be a nightmare to face Zhao Hai as an enemy. Now, Charlie was praising his intuition. He had already become a friend to Zhao Hai, assistance from such a person would certainly be very valuable.

Chapter 402: Markey Family

Naturally, the other party also saw Zhao Hai’s actions, they didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have this much methods in combat. The only information that they obtained about him before was that he was a Dark Mage. Today, they were made aware that he was surprisingly able to use spells of other departments.

However, Zhao Hai’s opponents were also experienced in battles. As soon as they saw Zhao Hai’s undead army, they immediately acted accordingly. The two water dragons that were previously used to break the ice once again emerged and began to crash towards the approaching undead army,

Unfortunately for them, Zhao Hai’s undead were surprisingly high-level, these kinds of attacks were not able to affect them.

When the undead saw the magic attack heading their direction, two of them went forward, cyan light flashed from their bodies as they wielded their weapons. When the two dragons went in contact with the two undead, two Sword Qi met them, slicing them into halves before the water splashed back to the sea.

Charlie who was standing on the Haven had his eyes turn blank upon seeing the scene. He was speechless. An undead using Battle Qi, this was the first time he saw such a thing. This was an eye opening experience.

The opponent was also unprepared for such an outcome that they forgot to make a move. The undead used this opportunity to quickly board their ships.

When the undead came onboard, the crew was unable to fight them off. This was because the Undead were very strong right now, they were not inferior to 8th rank Warriors.

An 8th rank warrior, when placed on any ordinary clan, would immediately become its ancestor, supporting the family singlehandedly. But Zhao Hai just released a lot of those experts casually, making those not part of his group quite startled.

His attack didn’t end here, after releasing waves of undeads warriors, he also added a lot of Jackal Race Cavalry to the mix.

The Jackals were quite small, but they were very fast. Before the people on the ships came to notice them, they were already on their boats.

Zhao Hai considered the matter finished. The enemy had six five-master ironclad battleships overall, he released 12 thousand undead just now, 2 thousand undead pero ship should be able to deal with the opposite party.

Zhao Hai stopped his actions and just stared at the several ships. Although those who were on the ships continued to resist, they weren’t able to do so for longer since they were a lot weaker.

Seeing the situation, Zhao Hai relaxed and turned to smile at Charlie, “Your highness, it seems like my fleet of ships has increased. How about it, do you want two ships to play around with? With a boat like mine, you would be able to fish whenever you want at sea.”

Charlie recovered from his daze, he made a complex expression when he looked at the ships that came to attack them. He shook his head and said, “Forget it, I don’t have that much free time to wander about in the sea. Mister should keep these ships. However, I think that those who wanted to deal with us aren’t simple people. Sending six five-masted ironclad ships isn’t something ordinary powers could do.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It think these people didn’t come for your highness, but instead for me. Your Highness, I’m afraid that I had unexpectedly implicated you.”

Charlie smiled and said, “What implicated? Since you decided to lend me a hand, naturally your enemies are now also my enemies. Thus, their attacks on you should also mean an attack on me, no need to say that you implicated me.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t add anything. He knows that Charlie was saying this in order to win him over. However, seeing someone want to win him over was also something he enjoyed a lot.

He wielded his staff as six clumps of black gas flew and encircled the six ships. Before long, people inside the ship became quite busy. Charlie noticed that there were some undead that proceeded to change the sails on the ships.

It was common for ships to have spare sails. They sail the seas all year round, what would they do if a storm suddenly hits them? If the storms blow the sails away or just rips them apart, what would they do? Since they couldn’t just wait for their deaths or until some other ship saved them, they naturally would carry along spare sails.

At this time, the undead that Zhao Hai released came back while walking along the icy surface. Zhao Hai stored them, leaving only three Mages behind.

Charlie looked at the three Mages and knew that were the Mages on board the enemy ships. Moreover, looking from their appearances, it seems like they were turned into undead by Zhao Hai.

At this point, Charlie’s mind went numb. Although he wasn’t a Dark Mage, he knew that it wasn’t easy for a Dark Mage to turn people into Advanced level undead. But it seems like this law didn’t apply to Zhao Hai, so long as he waved his staff, he can turn anyone into an undead, an Advanced Level undead.

Zhao Hai observed his new undead Mages, one was a Wind Mage, one was a Water Mage, while the last one was unexpectedly a Light Mage.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, it seems like those who wanted to deal with him had been quite thoughtful. They sent a Wind Mage to deal with his ship, a Water Mage to combat better at sea, and a Light Mage to counter him being a Dark Mage. It was clear that the opponent specifically sent them do deal with Zhao Hai.

What made Zhao Hai surprised was the fact that the Mages didn’t bring any sort of emblem on their bodies. Obviously to make their identities unknown.

Zhao Hai looked at the Light Mage and said, “Are you a person of the Radiant Church?”

The Light Mage bowed and said, “Yes, Young Master. I am indeed a Radiant Church person, current assignment is a Priest.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he asked again, “Did the Radiant Church send you this time to deal with me?” Zhao Hai knew that a Priest is a level lower than a Radiant Church’s White-clothed Bishop.

The Priest shook his head and said, “They didn’t, this time I had received an invitation from the Markey Family to deal with Young Master. This isn’t an assignment given by the Church.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he frowned, “It surprisingly the Markey Family, I didn’t expect that. You two as well?”

The other Mages nodded, “Yes, Young Master, we are Markey family’s foreign elders. We received the order to deal with you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Except for dealing with me, did the Markey Family have any other plans?”

Tho two mages shook their heads as one of them answered, “We don’t know, the family only told us about this assignment, they didn’t tell us about any other actions.”

Zhao Hai looked at the two mages and said, “Aside from the two of you, who else was on the ship?”

The mages immediately said, “We have Captain Gauter, he is a trusted aide of the family. Everything on the fleet is under his control, we listen to him.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then with an intention, a person ran towards them from one of the attacking ships. This man was quite good, although the ice was starting to melt, making it quite slippery, he was still able to run on it without much issue. Before long, the man arrived in front of Zhao Hai and bowed, “Gauter meets Young Master Zhao Hai, what does the young master need?”

Zhao Hai looks at this person, he looked about 40 years old, very ordinary looking and had a thick brown skin; obviously from the constant sea travel. Zhao Hai immediately responded, “Did the Markey Family have any other moves other than sending you to deal with me?”

Gauter shook his head, “Nothing else, young master. In order to deal with you, the family had spend quite a bit of money. Along with the six five-masted ironclad ships, they also invited two 8th rank mages, a priest, and five 8th rank warriors. The family told me that losing the six ships didn’t matter as long as young master is dealt with.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good, you go back and fix the sails as soon as possible. Follow us afterwards.” Gauter complied and turned to head back to his ship. Zhao Hai waved his staff and received the three Mages into the Space.

Charlie stood still at the side, observing. He was now made aware of the best way to interrogate someone, it was to turn them into an Advanced Level undead. This way, even if you ask the person when he stopped wetting his bed, he will immediately tell you.

Zhao Hai turned to Charlie and said, “Your highness, we should continue on. No need to manage them, they will catch up soon.”

Charlie nodded, then along with Zhao Hai and the others, they returned to the ship’s living room. After sitting down, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Laura, it seems like the Markey Family had gone quite restless. What do you think we should do?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “No need to be anxious. This time, they dispatched six five-masted ships along with a few experts, which we just wiped out. Now, their ships and people belong to us. I believe that this is be quite a huge blow to the Markey Family, they should be staying their hand for quite some time. If they did plan to deal with us again, then we wouldn’t be polite, let’s just deal with them directly, ending everything. There should be a lot of people who also wants to deal with them, let’s see if they could handle that.”

Zhao Hai and Charlie laughed. Charlie knew about Laura, he just didn’t expect that she would be treating the Markey Family this way, it was not what he thought about.

Zhao Hai was not surprised. He already knew Laura’s view of the Markey Family, so it was normal for her reaction to be like this. In fact, if he also asked Karen about his input, he would without a doubt say the same thing. This pair of father and daughter had long lost their sense of belonging towards the Markey Family.

At this time, Jinan walked in and bowed to Zhao Hai, “Young master, after examining the ship, we have lost five magic cannons, 20 ballistas, and the ship’s hull became slightly damaged. However, this wouldn’t affect our navigation, we can immediately head out.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, then we’ll let Gauter change his sails by himself, let’s head out.” Jinan nodded, then turned away.

Chapter 403: Method of Improving Strength

After eating supper, Zhao Hai entered the space, and at the same time he also called Green and Kun. The two were to teach Zhao Hai fighting skills today.

When Zhao Hai told the two about what just happened earlier this day, the old men didn’t worry at all. Although the Markey Family was a strong power, they were still a merchant family, just like the Shelley Family. If they wanted to deal with a person, they needed to make a deal with the nation where that person was residing in, and they also need to spend a lot of resources to do so.

This time, the Markey family had overreached their boundaries. They didn’t do a good job at investigating. They weren’t even aware that Charlie was present inside Zhao Hai’s ship.

It didn’t matter if they were determined or just plain careless, their actions today had already been noted. As the third prince of the continent’s most powerful nation, there weren’t a lot of people who would dare take action against him, let alone a Merchant Family.

Merchant Families were rich, but for Rosen Empire, the continent’s most powerful nation, they were nothing. If the Rosen Empire wanted to deal with the Markey family, then it would be easy. As long as the family had its business spread out among a lot of nations, Rosen Empire could just form an alliance with them and they would certainly be willing to eat the businesses of the family.

The reason the Markey Family was feared was because of its vast resources, but these resources could also be the reason for their demise.

When Zhao Hai saw that the two elders weren’t very worried, he let go of the topic. He now began to train his fighting techniques with Green and Kun. The first thing he studied was naturally Sword techniques.

Zhao Hai’s Battle Qi has reached 8th rank, and with his body being strengthened by the Detoxification potion and the Goldmetal fruit, his strength had reached an absurd degree. The moment he learns how to use Battle Qi along with fighting techniques properly, his power would increase exponentially.

The first part of Zhao Hai’s Sword technique practice were the fundamental moves; the stab, cut, point, wipe, lock, stagger, and stick. These moves were the basic stances of any Sword technique. No matter how fierce a technique was, they would still be made up of these moves.

After practicing for two hours, Green made Zhao Hai take a rest. At this time, Zhao Hai thought that if the Detoxification and Goldmetal fruit could increase his capabilities, then wouldn’t that work for Laura and the others as well? If the group could use the Goldmetal fruit to increase their strength, then that would be a good thing for them overall.

Thinking of this, Zhao Hai immediately said, “Cai’er, come here.” Cai’er complied, she flew over to Zhao Hai and stared at him.

Zhao Hai smiled at her and said, “Cai’er, please go inspect whether Laura and the others could use the Detoxification potion as well as the Goldmetal fruit to improve their strengths.”

Cai’er nodded, then waved her hand as lights surrounded Green, Kun, Laura, Meg, Nier, Shue, Shun, Blockhead, and Rockhead. Before long, the light vanished.

Cai’er turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, Grandpa Green and Grandpa Kun couldn’t be scanned, the Space didn’t have enough levels to do so. Miss Laura may take the Goldmetal fruit, but it needs to be halved, taken in 10 day intervals. 10 days after the second round, she would have the same rank as the young master. Miss Meg’s aptitude is very good, but she isn’t suitable for the Goldmetal Fruit, she needs a special potion. However, since the Space doesn’t have enough levels, young master cannot purchase the components yet. The same condition applies to Shue and Shun. Blockhead and Rockhead can directly take in a Goldmetal fruit to reach the same level as young master, but since they aren’t the Space’s host, they wouldn’t get an ability.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then he made a happy expression, “Good! Fantastic! Immediately buy three Golmetal Fruits and give one of them to Laura. We’ll worry about Meg’s situation when the time comes. Right, you didn’t say anything about Nier, what’s her situation?”

Cai’er said, “Nier’s situation is special. She isn’t suitable for any current potions in the Space. She needs a special fruit to eat in order to enhance her skill in communicating with animals. This is her special ability.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows, “What fruit? Do you know?”

Cai’er shook her head, “I don’t know. There is no information about the fruit in the space currently. But from the materials that the Space had absorbed so far, there’s a 90% probability that the fruit exists.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. Let’s first buy a Goldmetal Fruit then.”

Cai’er responded, “Young Master, Cai’er proposes to buy a single Goldmetal fruit and plant it. Even though we need to wait for a few days, we can save 20 thousand gold coins.”

Zhao Hai patted his head and smiled, “Alright, good. Let’s go according to what you say. In any case, you have a strong computing power right now, you can see things more than me.”

After he said that, he turned to Laura, Blockhead, and Rockhead, “It looks like you need to wait for a few more days.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “We’re not in a hurry. We’ve already been at our ranks for a long time, waiting for a few more days wouldn’t be an issue. However, Brother Hai, I think we should upgrade the Space as soon as possible to help Meg and the others. The Space may even find ways to upgrade Grandpa Green and the others.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then sighed, “That’s easy to say. Now that the Farm has reached level 30, upgrading 1 level will be extremely difficult. It seems like it will take a long time. Meg, you shouldn’t get discouraged, continue training and maybe you may even rise to 8th rank by yourself.”

Meg looked at Zhao Hai and gave a sweet smile, “It’s alright, young master, don’t worry. Make Elder Sister Laura rank up first, her present level is too low.”

Laura made an offended expression and said, “Little girl, you dare tease me?” Then she ran off to chase Meg, who also ran while laughing. The two became quite jolly while teasing each other.

Looking at the two, Green smiled, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, let’s practice for a little bit more, then we’ll rest.” Zhao Hai nodded, then stood up and continued to do his boring exercises.

At this time, Zhao Hai didn’t know that Ruyen’s escorts were currently very nervous. This was because behind their vessel, a three-masted battleship was closely following. It was just there, leisurely sailing not far from their ship, it didn’t attack them nor did it try to contact them. They didn’t know if this ship was an enemy or a friend.

Hart, who was the ship captain that the Purcell Family had sent this time, was also quite anxious about this ship. He didn’t know what this ship intends to do, and why it followed them. If he were to say that it was a pirate ship, it wouldn’t fit either. Pirates would never attack their ship, this was because of nothing else than the fact that an experienced pirate would instantly know that their ship had nothing valuable in it.

Someone who sailed the seas all year round would see from water displaced by the ship that it didn’t have anything in its cargo. Attacking their ship wouldn’t be worth it.

In order to ensure Ruyen’s safety, Hart even chose to sail along the coastlines, opting to pay taxes in order to increase their security. Pirates wouldn’t generally raid along the coastlines in fear of being surrounded by a nation’s navy.

However, the other ship followed them closely that it made them uncomfortable. In the end, there was no other way for Hart to do but inform Ruyen about the situation.

Ruyen frowned as she listened to Hart’s report, “You mean there’s a three-master battleship following not far from us? It didn’t attack us nor got in touch with us? Is that right?”

Hart replied, “Yes, Miss. We don’t know what the other party wanted to do, it just followed uis. I’m really worried because there’s going to be an area between Rosen Empire and Aksu Empire that is under nobody’s jurisdiction. Pirates are present there, I’m afraid that the ship would act against us in that place.”

Ruyen nodded, “Come, let’s go out. I want to look at that ship with my own eyes.” She said as she went out of the cabin first.

After inspecting the boat closely, Ruyen suddenly smiled and turned to Hart, “Hart, you don’t have to worry, just leave them be and continue on. That boat holds no malice towards us, if I guessed it right, they might even be here to protect us.” Then she turned and went back to the cabin, leaving a very confused Hart behind.

Hart really couldn’t understand why Ruyen was so sure that the other party was protecting them, But if Ruyen said so, then he wouldn’t have any say in the matter. He just instructed his crew to be alert.

Ruyen can relax, but Hart can’t. So the only thing he could do was raise the alertness of the crew. No matter what, he couldn’t make Ruyen suffer an accident.

When Ruyen returned to her own room, Jill asked her, “Your highness, why did you tell Hart to not worry? Do you recognize that ship?”

Ruyen shook her head, “i don’t know that boat, but I know of its style. Couldn’t you see that the ship doesn’t look like a standard ship of the Rosen Empire? Its appearance had been changed a little. Think about that ship that we met on Law River.”

Jill stared at Ruyen for a moment before his eyes lit up, “Your highness, you think that ship was sent by Mister Zhao Hai to protect us?”

Ruyen smiled faintly and said, “It’s possible. But forget it, Hart would still be alert no matter what I say. This is also good, it would be best if the ship is our friend, but if it is an enemy, we wouldn’t be caught off guard.”

Chapter 404: Ruyen is Attacked

Taking the sea route, travelling from Rosen Empire to Aksu empire would take seven days. Upon arriving at Aksu Empire, it would need about three more days of travel before they can reach Buding City, the nearest port from Purcell Duchy. Ruyen would disembark there and transfer into a carriage. Then it would take 7 days or so for them to arrive at Casa City.

But Hart was aware that on the fifth day of their travel, they would be sailing inside non-governed waters. They would travel for two days inside this area.

In this place, both Rosen Empire and Aksu Empire ships were rarely seen. This was because this area is considered to be the buffer zone between the two empires. If either fleet comes inside, the other would feel anxious, thinking that they might get attacked. So for a long time, there were no empire ships sailing these waters. Unfortunately, this also made this area a pirate’s heaven.

Anybody sailing this area knew that they might get attacked at any time. So most sailors would be very alert while being here, preparing for a fight at all times.

After sailing for several days, they were finally about to entered the buffer zone along with the unknown ship. Hart became even more nervous since the ship was still following them.

In order to let the crew rest well and prepare them for the possible battles, Hart made the ship stop first and get a good rest before proceeding. Hart also wanted to know if the ship was really following or was just on the same path as them.

In the end, Hart finally found out that the other party was indeed following them. When they stopped to rest, the other ship also stopped. It just kept a safe distance from their ship.

After reporting to Ruyen, Hart understood that there was no use in further expressing his concerns. Thus, he just ordered his crew to always be prepared for battle.

After resting for a day, Hart officially entered the unregulated part of their route. All of the ships sailing here were keeping a safe distance between each other, mainly to avoid misunderstandings, another reason was to keep alert since any merchant ship could turn out to be a pirate ship.

Hart was also paying special attention to the ship that was constantly tailing them. Seeing the ship still keeping a safe distance away from them and didn’t express any intentions to attack, Hart started to believe Ruyen’s words.

The first day passed safely. When evening came, Hart released the anchor and after appointing some sentries, retreated to take some rest. Naturally, all of them had their own weapons placed in a convenient place.

The next day, Hart’s ship sailed early. Everyone’s nerves were tight, they were afraid of battles. Perhaps it was the heavens that helped them since they didn’t meet any attacks. This made Hart loosen up, and finally when they entered Aksu Empire waters in the evening, he finally breathed a sigh of relief.

However, what Hart didn’t think of was that they would actually suffer an attack the second day they entered the Aksu Empire’s territory. Moreover, this attack didn’t come from the ship behind them, but was actually from an Aksu Empire warship.

There was a three-master Aksu empire warship sailing on the waters. Hart originally thought that it was only a patrolling warship so he didn’t care. But he didn’t expect that when their ship reached the ship’s firing range, they were immediately met with a fierce attack. Hart’s ship suffered a huge loss, a lot of people in the ship were killed, a lot of ballistas were also destroyed.

Fortunately, Hart was well-experienced and immediately reacted. It didn’t matter why the other party attacked, but they immediately retaliated.

But in the end, their ship was only a Merchant ship while the other was a three-masted warship. Their firepower was inferior to the enemy, nor was their maneuverability. They were always in the state being defeated all the time.

At this time, the ship that had been following them came over and attacked the three-masted ship. The attack of the ship was also very fierce, its attacks weren’t something that a merchant ship like theirs were capable of doing. The main thing about the ship was that they seem to be unafraid of death, it just rushed towards the three-master ship as though it was willing to ram their ships together.

Seeing this, Hart fully believed that the other ship was escorting them. But Hart felt strange, if the ship was sent by the family to escort them , then why didn’t it contact Hart? If it wasn’t sent by the family, then who did?

The three-masted ship didn’t expect to face such a ship, it had been caught off guard. They also saw that the ship seemed to not care about life and death, it looks like it was willing to perish together.

The three-masted ship became afraid and immediately retreated. The escort ship didn’t go for pursuit, it returned to Hart’s ship and stayed at a safe distance away.

Hart performed some flag signals to get in contact, but the other ship didn’t respond. In the end, Hart could only continue on sailing. Three days later, they finally arrived at Buding City. The ship that followed them silently vanished.

That ship was obviously the Swordfish which was sent by Zhao Hai to escort Ruyen. The Swordfish was crewed by undead so of course they weren’t afraid of death. If they weren’t sent to escort Ruyen, they would’ve chased the three-masted ship and steal it away.

And when Ruyen’s ship was attacked, Zhao Hai was naturally informed. When he heard that Ruyen’s ship was attacked by a battleship, Zhao Hai had no idea who was responsible.

Upon further consideration, Zhao Hai reckoned that it must have been Southern King Boris.. Boris had suffered a great loss under Zhao Hai, so he must have hated the Purcell Family as well. Thus, when Hart entered Aksu Empire waters, which was Boris’ domain, he immediately had a warship attack Ruyen.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to deal with Boris right now since they had already arrived at Jade Water City. The size of the city was quite similar with RIsing Water City. Almost everything was similar except for the larger and much cleaner port.

Obviously, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to dock their ship at the public pier. After all, Charlie was on board, he also had his own private pier.

Under the guidance of Charlie, Zhao Hai’s ship arrived at the Third Prince’s private port. Naturally, the people on the pier were already informed that Charlie was inside the ship, so they didn’t block the Haven from entering. On the contrary, the pier was full of people.

When the Haven stopped at the pier, it immediately lowered its boarding plank. Charlie led Zhao Hai down the ship and handed the Haven over to Luri to perform some repairs. After all, the ship needed some good repairs since it suffered quite some damage from the previous battle.

Zhao Hai didn’t reject Charlie’s good intentions, so he ordered Jinan to go along with Liru’s instructions. Then he sat inside a carriage with Charlie as the two of them were escorted by Jade Water City’s Lord towards the mansion.

Jade Water City’s City Lord is named Trezebo, Charlie’s hardcore supporter. He helped Charlie take charge of his money purse. Trezebo looked very thin with a dry skin but Zhao Hai didn’t underestimate this man. Although this man didn’t have a single bit of Battle Qi fluctuation, Zhao Hai felt something in this person that he only felt with Shun.

What is Shun? He was an assassin. For this man to have the same temperament as Shun, then it meant that he was also an assassin himself. This made Zhao Hai surprised, he didn’t think that Charlie would actually leave Jade Water City in the hands of someone with that profession.

The carriage’s curtains were open while they were travelling inside the city. Charlie was pointing and introducing various famous buildings to Zhao Hai.

What made Zhao Hai surprised about Jade Water City was its difference from Rising Water City in managing businesses. In Jade Water City, selling of products were centralized in a certain section of the city. For example, if you are selling grain, they you’ll have to sell it in a specific area along with the other grain sellers; the same goes for other products such as commodities and etc.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that Charlie would govern the city like this. But it was actually a good idea, this made managing the city much easier.

Looking at Zhao Hai’s expression of approval with regards to his administration, Charlie felt proud since this method was suggested by himself.

…

The carriage quickly arrived at the City Lord’s Mansion. The mansion was very stylish, but compared to Smith’s mansion, it lacked a few things here and there.

Upon arriving at the mansion, the three immediately went inside. Trezebo lead Charlie and Zhao Hai to the Purple Bamboo Courtyard that was already been prepared. This courtyard was the largest, most attractive, and most refined courtyard of the mansion. It was a courtyard meant specifically for Charlie’s use.

Originally, Zhao Hai didn’t want to stay here. However, he couldn’t just decline Charlie’s hospitality. The third prince wanted him to reside in Purple Bamboo Courtyard, so Zhao Hai had no choice but to stay.

To be honest, Zhao Hai actually liked the atmosphere inside the courtyard. Zhao Hai found Purple Bamboos to be beautiful, so naturally he would be extremely fond of the place.

One could say that Bamboo rice is also a type of bamboo. But since it was too long and is used mainly for grain production, its ornamental use was very unpopular.

At the same time, Purple Bamboo was also not mainly used for decoration. Purple Bamboo was actually a very good material for weapons. This fine bamboo can be used as a shaft for spears as well as a body for a bow. The bamboo was very tough, making it one of the most popular material for weapons in the Continent.

However, the Purple Bamboo was also like the Bread Tree, it was very picky about where it could grow. It had very strict requirements about temperature, humidity and climate. If these special conditions weren’t meant then they wouldn’t be able to survive. This made its output quite scarce in the continent.

Fortunately for Jade Water City, its location was the Purple Bamboo’s largest habitat. The mountains around the city were full of these bamboos, making them the most popular export of the area.

Upon arriving at the Purple Bamboo Courtyard, Trezebo asked to be excused in order to prepare the banquet. He didn’t leave behind a lot of servants in the courtyard since he knew that Charlie dislikes it. Therefore, he only had the place cleaned and left behind four maids. This arrangement was just right for Charlie’s preferences, and it coincidentally matched with Zhao Hai’s as well.

Since everything here is complete, Zhao Hai didn’t need to do a lot, so he quickly finished his unpacking.

The Purple Bamboo courtyard had a total of 27 rooms. Naturally, Charlie resided in the main room. Zhao Hai, on the other hand, stayed at an independent building.

After Zhao Hai’s group was settled in, Trezebo came in and expressed Charlie’s invitation for a meal. While he left Charlie earlier, Trezebo took that time as a chance to investigate Zhao Hai further. He already had some information about Zhao Hai, but he didn’t put any emphasis on it. But now that he was going to help Charlie, he needed to be screened carefully by Trezebo, after all, the assassin cared a lot about his lord.

After the group arrived at the dining room and sat down, a maid immediately provided the meals. The dishes were very good, the things that Trezebo had prepared weren’t that luxurious, however, they had some special characteristics, they were also made using seasonal ingredients, they were fresh.

Charlie was surely satisfied with his subordinate’s meal. While they were eating, Charlie introduced Trezebo and Zhao Hai with each other.

After eating, the group sat inside the living room. Charlie drank some tea and turned to Trezebo and said, “Trezebo, go give mister Zhao Hai my badge tomorrow. Make sure to exempt him from taxes later as well. Also, allow his ship to use my own personal pier. Right, also look for a good store location for mister Zhao Hai, after tidying it up, hand it over to mister as a gift.”

Trezebo gave a nod. Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and smiled to Charlie, “I give my thanks to your highness. When my people gets settled down, we’ll immediately send you the things we agreed on. Right, I also need a bunch of daily necessities as well as some iron, I’ll have to ask for your highness’ help in this.”

Charlie replied, “Iron? What does mister need iron for? Weapons? That wouldn’t be good. Even if I want to produce a large number of weapons, I still need to report it to the capital. You know that my situations is quite complex, I think mister should hand this over to someone else.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I understand. Don’t worry, I don’t need a lot of iron. On the other hand, I need a ton of necessities, include ceramic products as well. I’ll need your highness’ assistance with this. I want a lot, enough to fully stock one ship.”

Hearing Zhao Hai, Charlie nodded, “If that is so, then it wouldn’t be a problem, mister can rest assured. Trezebo, prepare those things from mister as soon as possible. Also, go prepare means to store and transport 50 thousand fire fishes. How many days would you need?”

Trezebo thought for a moment then replied, “Your highness, the things can be prepared tomorrow. But the equipment for the fire fishes would take at least ten days.”

Chapter 405: Unexpected Benefit

Charlie nodded, “Good, prepare the things that mister wanted first. You can slowly prepare for the fire fishes later. Also, make some preparations, Mister Zhao Hai might bring back some aquatic magic beasts and marine products, be sure to receive them properly.”

Trezebo stared at Charlie, then his eyes lit up as he turned to Zhao Hai. He understood what merfolk products represented in the continent, they represent money, gold coins!

If Zhao Hai can get a large quantity of marine products from the merfolk, not making money off of it would be difficult. For them, this is very good information.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I don’t know how it will turn out, it depends on the heavens. If they give me something good, then that would be for the better.”

Charlie smiles and said, “Mister will certainly succeed, I have confidence in mister.” Not to say that Charlie had trust in Zhao Hai, per se, but in his undead. Through the battle previously, Charlie was made known of the formidability of Zhao Hai’s undead. Those undead were unbelievably strong.

Zhao Hai smiles and replies, “Your highness over praises me. But I still have to wait before Haven finishes its repairs. The ship only suffered a few damages during the attack, it shouldn’t take that long for it to be repaired. I also have a few more ships, they can act as the advance party, I’ll just follow them in the Haven.”

Charlie said, “Mister’s undead can be separated from you that far?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your highness had forgotten that they are Advanced level undead, naturally they can be separated from me for quite some distance. Your Highness, I just remembered a matter, I had a three-masted ship sent to escort a friend, but I didn’t expect that it would be attacked so it is quite damaged. After a period of time I’ll have to ask your highness for help regarding its repairs, what does your highness think?”

Charlie waved his hand and said, “This is a small matter, you don’t have to worry about it. Just let your ship come. Alright, mister should take a rest first. I’ll have them repair your ship as soon as possible so that it can be returned to you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then after giving Charlie a bow he returned to his room. One could say that his cooperation with Charlie went successfully, Zhao Hai was glad.

After returning to their building in Purple Bamboo Courtyard, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately take a rest. He first explored the courtyard’s bamboo grove along with Laura and others.

Zhao Hai didn’t just go around the grove to sightsee,  naturally he also wanted to get a couple of bamboo shoots. If those shoots were planted on the ground, they would grow and eventually turn into their own bamboo forest.

The Purple Bamboo had very strict requirements as to its habitat, but it wouldn’t need that inside the Space. Zhao Hai was very confident in raising some Purple Bamboo there.

Every since he was little, Zhao Hai always wanted to have a house with a big patch of bamboo around it. He sees that scenario to be quite beautiful.

The Chinese people loved bamboo. There were many ancient poems that were written about bamboo. Zhao Hai was a writer and even though writers can do almost anything, Zhao Hai had a particular preference for Ancient Chinese. Therefore, he also liked poems about the tall grass. He always imagined himself living in a house covered by bamboo. Unfortunately, he lived in the north, a place not suitable for growing the plant. In the end, he never was able to grow his own.

In addition to his preference for bamboo, the Purple Bamboo was also able to save Zhao Hai’s worries about the future. First, the Purple Bamboo is a unique plant that can give the Space some experience. When Zhao Hai establishes his nation in the Black Wasteland in the future, he would inevitably need some soldiers for protection. With the Purple Bamboo’s characteristics, the need for massive amounts of weapon materials should get fulfilled.

After collecting shome shoots about three feet long, Zhao Hai threw them into the Space. Sure enough, a prompt was transmitted. It stated that the Purple Bamboo had been evaluated with a Level of 35, however, it was unable to upgrade the Space.

This was what Zhao Hai expected, it was normal for the Space to not level up. After all, the Purple Bamboo’s level was only so-so, how would it be able to upgrade the Space?

Zhao Hai made Cai’er plant those bamboo shoots at the back of the villa and instructed her to take care of them carefully. Then the group continued exploring the grove to see whether this place had any other things of note.

For a bamboo grove that had not been cut for a long time, there should be some good things present here. No matter plant or animal, Zhao Hai would have a need for it. Currently, he had a lot of ecosystems present inside the Space, both marine and terrestrial. Zhao Hai wanted to find out if something on this grove would help those ecosystems.

Zhao Hai’s initial purpose of upgrading the Space was to cure his toxin. But even though he had already solved that problem and was now able to practice Battle Qi, there were still benefits in the Space just waiting for him to take. After upgrading the Space further, he may be able to help Meg and the others upgrade their ranks. This also applied to Grandpa Green’s group, they might even reach 9th rank. For Zhao Hai, this temptation is too great.

If Green and the others can become 9th rank experts, then that would be extremely fantastic. When the Buda Clan acquires a few 9th ranks in their pockets, nobody would say a word when they decide to resurface in the future.

Upon exploring, in addition to finding some mushrooms, Zhao Hai and the others also found a bamboo rat.

Zhao Hai had heard that this Bamboo Rat was quite the delicacy back on Earth. In Ark Continent, he wasn’t sure if the rodent had changed its flavor.

Zhao Hai was dumbfounded when the Space received the mushrooms, their evaluation were unexpectedly higher than the Purple Bamboo, it said that the mushroom was a special treasure, had a nice taste and were full of nutrition. Its level was also above level 40, this surprised Zhao Hai.

His surprise was even more so for the Bamboo Rat, when it entered the space, it was unexpectedly evaluated to be level 50. It was a mouse variation that is affected by some plant genes. Not only was it delicious, it could also help in growing some plants and eliminate pests in the soil. Also, its attack power wasn’t weak, a fully grown adult would reach 7th or 8th rank in strength. Apparently, the one Zhao Hai just seized was a young rat.

A pleasant surprise, a pleasant surprise indeed. Zhao Hai didn’t think that he would come across such valuable things. To be able to get some highly valued stuff just by taking a casual stroll in a bamboo grove was an extremely lucky situation.

Laura and the others were even more surprised than Zhao Hai. This was because there was no custom in the Ark Continent of eating mushrooms. Thus, when they saw Zhao Hai absorb the fungi into the Space, they were puzzled. And when they saw that it had a high evaluation, they were dumbfounded.

Hearing Laura talk about not eating mushrooms, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pat his head. When Green went to forage some food in the forest before, he probably didn’t look for some mushrooms. No wonder he felt that there were a lack of fungi inside the Space, it turned out to be this.

But it was not too late, they could correct that thought afterwards. After strolling for a few more minutes in the bamboo grove, Zhao Hai didn’t find any notable things to absorb aside from some insects, naturally he absorbed those too.

Although insects were common, they were also crucial to ecosystems. Thus, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and absorbed a bunch of those directly. But since the insects were very common, it didn’t make the Space level up, the Space didn’t even give any evaluations for them, it just ignored them. However, the Ranch was already a small world, so those insects were still placed there.

Afte walking around the grove, Zhao Hai’s group returned to their small building. Laura was interested in today’s harvest, although it wasn’t very big, they had gotten quite some interesting things.

Zhao Hai smiled at the group and immediately brought them to the Space. At this time, the Space had allocated a space of ten mu where the Goldmetal Fruit was planted. The Goldmetal tree had already grown quite a bit, but it still didn’t bear any fruit.

Ten mu of ground for such a little tree seemed very strange. But Laura and the others looked at the Goldmetal Fruit with a look full of hope. They knew that as soon as this tree bears fruit, they would be able to increase their rank.

After taking a rest inside the Space, they came out of the villa. Zhao Hai didn’t call Green, it was still daytime, his grandpa was still busy.

Zhao Hai also didn’t practice fighting techniques, he already learned the basic sword stances. Moreover, he also had a few spars with Blockhead and Rockhead, giving him adequate experience in battle. With his present strength, he wouldn’t be able to be defeated by a 6th rank.

Since he didn’t have anything else to do in the Space, there was only one thing left. He held an iron ball in his hand and felt its characteristics.

Zhao Hai understood that he really had the same ability as Magneto, metal manipulation. However, his present ability was much less than the Marvel villain. Magneto can control airplanes and even make a metal bridge fly into the sky while Zhao Hai can only control a small piece of iron ball.

But Zhao Hai was still satisfied, with such a piece of metal, he can change its form and control it within the Space monitor’s range. He can make this metal both attack and defend, this is already enough.

Chapter 406: Charlie’s Delight

Through this matter, Zhao Hai understood the massive benefits of being the Space’s host. The current range of the Space’s monitor is 10 thousand meters, 10 thousand! Even if this iron ball isn’t large, when it becomes a small sword its lethality would increase. This way, wouldn’t it be just like a flying sword?

Thinking about this made Zhao Hai excited. However, even if he wanted to play with this iron ball, he could only do so inside the Space, he wouldn’t be able to do so outside.

Chinese baoding balls aren’t known in the Ark Continent, if people saw Zhao Hai playing with iron balls, then they would definitely find him very strange.

When Zhao Hai went out of the space in the afternoon, he didn’t see Charlie. But he knew that Jade Water City is Charlie’s domain, so he should have a lot of work to do upon arriving here. Thus, Zhao Hai didn’t think much of it and just stayed inside Purple Bamboo courtyard, drinking tea and chatting with Laura and the others.

When evening came, Charlie invited Zhao Hai for dinner. He apologized to Zhao Hai for neglecting him for the rest of the day. For a prince to apologize to him for such a minor matter was already giving him a lot of face, so Zhao Hai naturally couldn’t get offended. He just drank a few cups of wine with Charlie, while talking about the past.

Charlie acting like he just did made Trezebo startled. One must know that Charlie is a Prince, and because of this, he is full of pride. Normally he shows a good natured attitude towards people, but being Charlie’s confidant, Trezebo clearly knew Charlie.

The Third Prince’s arrogance is very high, he wouldn’t even pay attention to the commoners. He’s only be polite to someone because he knew that you have been educated, and not because he thinks highly of him.

However, Trezebo could feel that this politeness that Charlie showed to Zhao Hai wasn’t fake. The prince actually thought highly of Zhao Hai. This made Trezebo quite surprised.

If one would say that Zhao Hai makes a lot of money, but that is just business in the end. Compared to the tax revenue brought by Jade Water City, it was inferior. Charlie shouldn’t think highly of Zhao Hai because of this.

If one would say that Zhao Hai is strong, having 8th rank in strength, but he isn’t a 9th rank expert. His current strength isn’t enough to merit Charlie’s respect. This made Trezebo even more confused about Charlie’s attitude.

After having dinner, Zhao Hai’s group returned to the Space to rest. But at this time, Trezebo was with Charlie in the living room.

In the afternoon, they didn’t have much time for idle talk since they were busy with official matters. Trezebo just talked to Charlie to report the income of the city as well as some things that he handled for Charlie when he was gone.

After serving Charlie a cup of tea, Trezebo looked at Charlie with a puzzled expression, “Your Highness, why do you look so highly on Zhao Hai? Is it because he is very strong?”

Charlie looked at Trezebo and smiled faintly, “Why? You’re not convinced?’

Trezebo shook his head and said, “That’s not it. I’ve been with your highness for so many years. How could I be unconvinced about this kind of thing? I just don’t know if mister Zhao Hai has enough capability for your highness to be so respectful.”

Charlie smiled and said, “His business, his strength, his connections, all of these I fancy. Liru, go tell Trezebo about Zhao Hai.” Liru nodded, then told Trezebo about things they experienced with Zhao Hai.

Trezebo didn’t think that this would be the case. He knew that Zhao Hai had a connection with the Cali and Shelley Families. He also knew that Zhao Hai had some sort of conflict with the Calci Family. What he didn’t expect was the fact that Zhao Hai was the one who actually dealt with Grand Duke Lionheart. He also didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be an Advanced multi-element Mage.

It is difficult for Multi-element Mages to reach a high level, this is because mastering each department wasn’t very easy. For Zhao Hai to be an advanced level Multi-element magician is very astonishing. Such identity is indeed worth Charlie’s admiration.

9th ranks would rarely join battles in the continent, it was generally 8th ranks who do. This made Advanced Multi-element mages priceless. A lot of powers wanted to get in touch with one.

Advanced Multi-element mages can use a lot of spells as well as Composite Magic. The attack power of Composite Magics were very terrifying. The combination between two spells of different departments can bring forth unique reactions, increasing its magical attacking power exponentially.

If Charlie can have a Multi-element Mage like Zhao Hai under his retinue, his strength would surely increase by several folds. Moreover, this was a Mage that could bring wealth, he had a lot of valuable products on hand.

After knowing these things about Zhao Hai, Trezebo understood why Charlie gave him full respects, he gave a nod and said, “Your highness is doing the right thing. Someone like Zhao Hai is truly worthy of respect. But why is the Calci Family in conflict with him? Do they want him to go to another person? Are they crazy?”

Charlie smiled faintly and said, “Trezebo, you forget. The one who currently wields the power within the Calci Family are still those elders. And the person who was mostly favored by the elders is the fifth child Juwan. Seeing Zhao Hai making a lot of money, it wouldn’t be strange for Juwan to feel envious. Moreover, Zhao Hai offended Souther King, driving him out of Aksu Empire. At the same time, he also offended the Radiant Church, so he went to Sky Water City. Looking at these facts, Juwan thought that he would be able to pressure Zhao Hai. There’s no other person responsible other than Juwan.”

Trezebo nodded, “Your highness is right, it would be impossible for Smith and the other brothers to do such a thing, only Juwan. I always thought that the patriarch of the Calci Family is an astute person, to actually favor Juwan is a wrong decision. Allowing his fifth son to actually drive a person like Zhao Hai away, he will surely regret it.”

Charlie smiled, “That wouldn’t be so easy, Zhao Hai is a smart and wise person. He wouldn’t just cut ties with the Calci Family about such a matter. Although the one who holds the power in the family are those elders, Smith and his brothers have also grown up, they also held some sort of influence of their own. For the brothers, they couldn’t just let go of Zhao Hai. If I guessed correctly, Smith should have given Zhao Hai some sort of assurance that he would be able to reverse this action of the Calci Family.”

Trezebo nodded, “That is quite possible. It seems like Zhao Hai is really not that simple. Is your highness confident in getting him?”

Trezebo naturally had full confidence in his lord, but he asked Charlie if he was able to control Zhao Hai.

Charlie shook his head and smiled, “For a person like Zhao Hai, I wouldn’t dare exert my control. Just maintaining our present relationship is enough.  When we have some problems in the future, he surely wouldn’t just look the other way. Remember what he said earlier? That he had a ship that was quite damaged after escorting a friend?”

Trezebo nodded and said, “Of course, I remember that he wants us to repair it. What’s the issue with that?”

Charlie smiled, “You really didn’t recognize the issue? This is because of Zhao Hai and Purcell Family’s relationship. Zhao Hai had received some help from Purcell Family’s Grand Duke, thus Zhao Hai had been protecting Evan’s daughter all this time, I think she’s called Ruyen? I heard that this Ruyen had brought some trouble for Zhao Hai, but Zhao Hai still didn’t leave her to fend for herself. I received some information that Ruyen recently embarked on a sea route to return home. So along the way, they should’ve passed the ungoverned region, I believe Zhao Hai sent his other ship to escort her. For Zhao Hai to do this, it showed what kind of person he is. This kind of person isn’t someone that you would want to control, otherwise they would get offended, understood?”

Trezebo immediately nodded, “Your highness can feel relieved, I understand what must be done. I have already prepare a shop location for mister Zhao Hai. It is not very far from the east gate, the shop is quite big. Although its position isn’t that great, it has a huge warehouse, as well as two additional storages underground. It’s a good store. The things that mister Zhao Hai wanted has also been transported to the warehouse, he only needs pick them up.”

Charlie looked at Trezebo with a praising look, “Good work, Trezebo. You being here in Jade Water City these few years really made me feel relieved. If not for the family’s rules that Jade Water City couldn’t be owned permanently, I really would like to give this place to you. But rest assured, if I sit on a throne, I will certainly give you a good territory.”

Trezebo quickly responded, “I won’t dare, your highness. I’ve been following you since you are young, this Trezebo has also served you for quite long time. Your highness need not give me any territories, I can just serve by your side for my entire life.”

Charlie smiles, “Of course I know that, but with all that you’ve done for me, I cannot just let you go on unrewarded. It will make the others who follow me doubt whether I would reward them or not, so just accept my gift. As for your territory, I already have some idea. Grand Duke Lionheart’s Duchy still didn’t have an official owner, so father decided to just divide them to his successors. I plan to give my share to you.”

Trezebo’s heart couldn’t help but feel excited. He knew how good Lionheart’s territory was. A lot of people were lining up to get a piece of that land. So now that Charlie was giving him a piece, this was a very good reward.

Looking at Trezebo’s appearance, Charlie couldn’t help but smile, “This is the only thing that I can give you right now. If I get the imperial throne, I will give you Lionheart’s entire territory, when that time comes, you will be a Grand Duke.”

Chapter 407: Gift

The next morning, Zhao Hai was asked by Charlie to have some breakfast. After eating, the two of them went to the living room to drink come tea. At this point, Trezebo walked in and reported to Charlie, “Your Highness, the shop and the requested good are already prepared. Should we go check it out?”

Charlie turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “In any case, we don’t have anything else to do. Let’s go.”

Charlie smiled, “Good, let’s go and take a look. Your ships are almost repaired, they can start sailing tomorrow. The Haven has a bit of a problem so it may have to wait for a couple days more.”

Zhai Hai nodded, “This is already within my expectations. Let’s see the shop first.” Then the group went out of the living room and went to the already prepared carriage outside. The group sat in the carriage and immediately went straight to the shop under Trezebo’s guidance.

Today, they were riding inside Trezebo’s carriage. Riding his carriage was very useful when inside the city. As soon as people see it, they would immediately move out of the way, after all, this carriage belonged to the City Lord.

Before long, they stopped at a place near Jade Water City’s east gate. But there’s something strange, for a business area there were a few people here. Nevertheless, the shop is very large. Looking at its front, one could see that it has three stories, one could also see that it’s front design is beautiful. Behind the shop is a large courtyard, with a door at the side that could fit three carriages in parallel. The door looked very sturdy since it is made of thick wood.

At this time, there were two guards standing by the courtyard’s front door. When they saw Trezebo’s carriage, they immediately opened the door allowing the carriage to enter inside.

The courtyard was big, but there were no plants inside. At first sight, one could see that this place was used as a stockpile area for goods since the floor is covered with flat stone. There was also a stable and a warehouse inside. An owner’s room and servant’s quarters were present as well, all very simple in design, clearly specially designed for practical use.

After the group got down from the carriage, Zhao Hai and Charlie immediately inspected the place. After surveying the area, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It is very good, although the living section is ordinary, it has a very huge warehouse. This is very good, I give my thanks to City Lord Trezebo.”

Trezebo smiled and replied, “Mister Zhao Hai is too polite, come with me to see the warehouse, there’s a surprise in there.” Then he led Zhao Hai and Charlie towards the warehouse.

There were also people guarding the warehouse. When they saw Trezebo, they immediately gave a salute. Trezebo waved his hand and the guards quickly opened the door to the warehouse.

Zhao Hai looked at saw that the warehouse had been filled with all the things that he requested. The ceramics were carefully packed in wooden boxes, there were also living necessities inside. What’s more important was that this warehouse had a staircase heading downwards.

Trezebo took Zhao Hai to the basement of the warehouse. The basement was divided into two floors also filled with the things that Zhao Hai wanted.

The stairs in this basement are very wide, it could allow two carriages to go side by side. In fact, the stairs weren’t actually stairs, but instead an inclined surface that could allow carriages to run through, making transporting goods much more convenient. Moreover, the steepness of the stairs were very low, this made most carriages able to use it.

When Zhao Hai saw how large this basement warehouse was, he was afraid that the entire underground of the courtyard might have been hollowed out. Fortunately, the construction of this space was very sturdy. There were pillars here and there and they were made of full compact stone, a very strong material.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with this, although he didn’t have much use of such a large warehouse, it was better than nothing, also, it might provide them with a cover-up story in the future.

Looking at Zhao Hai satisfied expression, Trezebo felt relief, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are you satisfied with this? His highness has ordered me to gift you this yard as well as the things inside. I hope mister will not decline.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment, then nodded, “Them I won’t be polite. In exchange, I shall also give Your highness as well as the City lord a gift.” He turned his hand as two small bags appeared.

The two bags were naturally Spatial Bags. Charlie treated him well, so Zhao Hai couldn’t be stingy and decided to return the Third prince’s kindness, this Spatial Bag is one.

Charlie and Trezebo looked at Zhao Hai with confused expressions, they didn’t know what these two bags were. Zhao Hai handed the bags to them and said, “These two bags are Spatial Bags, inside is about ten cubic meters of space where you can store some things in. With Your highness’ power, naturally this thing wouldn’t be very valuable, just take it as a toy.”

Charlie and Trezebo were stunned, although Spatial equipment weren’t popular in the continent, they were very precious; even Charlie only had one such item. But Zhao Hai was just casually giving those away like they were worthless.

Charlie, still in shock, turned to Zhao Hai, “I didn’t think that Mister has such good things in his hands. I think that I owe mister now.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Your Highness is too polite, this is just an exchange of gifts. Your Highness doesn’t need to mind it too much.”

Hearing Zhao Hai, Charlie also laughed, “Very well, then we’ll receive mister’s gift. So are you satisfied with the place? When will you send people to take the goods?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “My people will come with the ship that I used to escort my friend. They’re heading here quickly, in about two days.”

Charlie nodded, “That is good, I’ll have Trezebo help you guard the place for two days, he’ll hand the place over when your people arrive.” Zhao Hai smiled and nodded.

The group returned to the City Lord’s Mansion, then Zhao Hai went to take a rest since he currently can’t take the goods from the warehouse yet. He plans to stock up those ships he stole from the Markey Family tomorrow, then make them sail towards Ape Island where they’ll wait for Zhao Hai. After the Haven gets fully repaired, then they’ll continue on to trade with the Shrimp Tribe.

He also wants to take advantage of this downtime to receive Laura’s people and settle them down. He’ll need to assign someone to manage the shop as well, after all, it was already ready to use.

Zhao Hai planned that he would just sell some daily groceries in this shop to not be too eye-catching. When the situation at the store gets more stabilized, then he’ll think about improving the products sold there.

Laura’s subordinates were all people who were talented managers. Their addition would surely help Iron Mountain Fort. They will also make it more convenient for Zhao Hai to open more stores in the continent.

Fortunately for Zhao Hai, the time of their arrival was approaching. At that time, they will be taken to the Space and then delivered to Iron Mountain Fort. For those who’ll be sent to Jade Water City, Zhao Hai would place them in the Swordfish.

The next day, the five-masted ships that Zhao Hai took from the Markey Family were now ready to set sail. Zhao Hai asked Charlie to help him store the goods onto the ships which the latter agreed and had sent people to place the cargo on the vessels. Even if the goods inside the warehouse were numerous, they weren’t enough to fill five of those ships. The ships were all half full when they set sail. Zhao Hai couldn’t tell Charlie that he wanted to trade with the merfolk this time, he only told the third prince that he’ll supply it to other people.

Charlie didn’t think too much about it. After all, those goods were all common in the continent, they weren’t treasures.

After releasing the five ships, Zhao Hai awaited the arrival of the Swordfish. Two days after the five ships left, Laura’s subordinates were all gathered and ready. All in all, there were 400 of them of which 80 were the Managers. The other people were their family members, all of which were also loyal to Laura.

Zhao Hai and Laura immediately entered the Space and took those people in and sent them to Iron Mountain Fort. One group was left behind and was sent to Jade Water City,.

When the Managers saw Laura, they were very glad. All of them had received some sort of grace from her, so they were all her devout followers; there were no problems in trusting them.

Zhao Hai also believed in them, so when they arrived at Iron Mountain Fort, they were handed over to Kun who was given the task of familiarizing them with the environment.

These people all had previous contact with Kun and were once directly managed by him. Now that they saw Kun receive them, they felt excites, it was better to be with those you were acquainted with after all.

The one who was chosen to stay in Jade Water City was one of Laura’s most talented subordinate. He is called Mu’en, over 40 years old and was a small merchant before he met Laura. Later on into his past career, he suffered bankruptcy and was forced to sell himself as a slave in order to save his family. In the end, Laura saved him and eventually became a Manager under Laura’s leadership. Him and his family were very grateful for Laura’s benevolence. Because of his previous experience as well as his tenacious attitude, he became a valued Manager in the eyes of Laura.

Although he was 40 years old, he was still very energetic and was still quite attractive. His wife was also smart. Besides him and his wife, he had two kids who were already in their 20s, also learning how to handle business from their parents.

Having such family be in charge of Jade Water City made Zhao Hai rest assured. He was very confident in Laura’s eye for people.

After settling the family inside the Swordfish, Zhao Hai returned to the City Lord’s Mansion. The Swordfish would arrive in two days which was also the time frame where the Haven would get fully repaired. After the Haven gets repaired, Zhao Hai can continue on and trade with the Shrimp Tribesmen.

Upon returning to the Mansion, Zhao Hai didn’t have anything to do. Because of this, he only stayed inside and continued to practice his fighting techniques and his control over metal. The more he practiced the better his control became. Right now, Zhao Hai can already control two fist-sized iron balls, with attacking force much stronger than before.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to meddle in Charlie’s matters. Even if he wanted to help Charlie, the Prince would still need to approach him first. After all, the two haven’t known each other for a long time. If Zhao Hai was too anxious in providing help, Charlie might misunderstand. So he didn’t inquire too much, he just lived his days leisurely, living a good life.

Zhao Hai’s actions actually brought relief to Charlie. For the Prince, Zhao Hai’s origins were too mysterious. If Zhao Hai wanted to intervene in his matters, then Charlie would’ve felt suspicion.

Two days went by fast and the Swordfish had arrived at Jade Water City. Zhao Hai already gave Charlie a heads up, so along with Laura and the others, they went to the pier to meet the vessel.

Naturally, Charlie didn’t’ go with them. Even if he fancied Zhao Hai, he couldn’t go, after all, he is a prince. For him to meet Zhao Hai’s people on the pier would be too excessive.

After receiving Mu’en’s family into the City Lord’s Mansion, the Swordfish was immediately sent to Charlie’s shipyard for repairs. At the same time, Zhao Hai also introduced Mu’en and Trezebo with each other. He wanted Mu’en to know Trezebo directly, so if he was given the opportunity, he could establish a close relationship with the Lord of the city.

One could praise Mu’en’s skills, he was truly born to be a Merchant. His way of speaking was very smooth, although it could be said that you wouldn’t instantly see him as a friend, it was impossible to dislike him.

Trezebo’s attitude towards Mu’en was also very good. The city lord knew how Charlie regarded Zhao Hai. For Zhao Hai to leave Mu’en in Jade Water City showed how Zhao Hai trusted this guy. Thus, Trezebo decided to form a good relationship with the manager.

When it was time for the evening meal, Charlie officially met Mu’en. This made Mu’en startled, he didn’t even see a Purcell Duchy prince before, much less a Prince of an empire. From his point of view, he could see that Charlie valued Zhao Hai a lot.

Mu’en wasn’t a fool, when he saw Zhao Hai and Charlie’s merry interactions, he knew that Zhao Hai’s position in Charlie’s heart wasn’t low. This made the Manager quite glad, this meant that Laura didn’t choose the wrong person.

The next morning, Zhao Hai brought Mu’en to the shop that Charlie gifted him. After seeing the shop, Zhao Hai handed its care over to Mu’en. Zhao Hai gave the store a name just like how he wanted to brand his goods, Haven.

Besides the shop, Zhao Hai also gave Mu’en a Spatial Bag as well as 100 thousand gold coins. At the same time, he also left behind some goods and vegetables, which would later be the shop’s main products.

Zhao Hai was honest with Mu’en, he told the Manager that he didn’t expect to make some profits from the shop. He just wanted someone to stay here and stay in contact with Trezebo, so Mu’en didn’t need to work too hard. Naturally, if the shop could do well, then that would be the best.

Chapter 408: Heading off to the Sea Once Again

Zhai Hai’s initial purpose in opening a shop in a major city was to get contacts for new businesses and establishing relationships with Nobles, essentially increasing his own web of connections.

However, that purpose was now made redundant because of Charlie. Who was Charlie? He is a prince with a possibility of becoming an emperor. It was much better to be connected with him rather than going for any other person.

Even if Charlie didn’t become the Emperor, he was still a prince, a influential one. Even if the new Emperor wanted to deal with him, Charlie already had a strong network of connections. If the Emperor wanted to make a move, he needs to think about it carefully.

The situation was like Aksu Empire’s Southern King. Although he was only a prince, his influence in the southern part of the Empire isn’t less than that of the ruling monarch. The Aksu Emperor couldn’t even enact his own decrees in the south, since all of the citizens there obey the Southern King.

And the reason why the Southern King has such influence was because of his connections to a lot of Nobles. The benefits that those people enjoy were closely interwoven with Southern King. Therefore, even if Boris didn’t become the Emperor, those Nobles would still protect his authority, or else their benefits would get affected.

However, Southern King’s situation was a special case in the continent. While Boris was competing with the current Emperor for the throne, the old king unexpectedly died. Although the current Emperor ascended the throne, there wasn’t enough damage to Southern King in order to remove his authority. He had no choice but to let Boris continue on ruling the south.

So if we look at the situation in Rosen Empire where Charlie was competing for the throne, when the current Emperor already decided on a successor, what he needs to do was suppress the other candidates while increasing the successor’s power. This way, fully establishing the successor’s influence across the empire, making it impossible for a second Southern King to appear.

On the other hand, established Nobles in the Ark Continent were also very formidable. There were times where an Emperor couldn’t make his moves easily. But the Emperor also had his own connections and interwoven benefits with them, so as long as the emperor don’t encroach on that, he can only damage a candidate minimally.

Zhao Hai also knew that he was only leaning on Charlie’s tree. Cooperating with old nobles was very difficult. He knew that established Nobles would refrain from taking a side in a successorship battle as much as possible. This was because if their candidate failed to take the throne, they would get suppressed by the new Ruler.  Although the nobles hold deep reserves, if they were continually suppressed, then they would slowly lose their power, this isn’t something that they would want.

If they didn’t participate in the battle, they could still keep their courtesies to whoever becomes the new Emperor. With this, why would they need to participate? Therefore, even if there were constant struggles between princes in all nations, only a few of those established nobles would be involved.

Zhao Hai was now connected with Charlie, this meant that he was essentially one of Charlie’s people. In this case, most established nobles wouldn’t get in contact with him. They were afraid that if they form a connections with Zhao Hai, then they would get grouped up with Charlie. This wasn’t in line with an established noble’s usual stance on the situation.

Since Zhao Hai was already clear about this, he didn’t make Mu’er make contacts with those Nobles. He just tasked the Manager to carefully look over the shop.

Zhao Hai also believed that having this shop wasn’t a bad idea. Even if those established Nobles didn’t want to get involved, this didn’t mean that nobody wanted to. In fact, general Noble participating was a common occurrence in these battles, especially Mid and Low rank Nobles. They wanted to increase their rank and influence, so as long as they see a possibility of succeeding, they would take a gamble.

So even though Zhao Hai didn’t have any reputation at the moment, Charlie would still introduce him to nobles belonging to his side. Those people would then go and inquire to Trezebo, and eventually approaching Zhao Hai for cooperation.

Zhao Hai was very confident about this, Charlie’s attitude towards him already provided enough proof. If those nobles in the Third Prince’s side knew how Charlie treated Zhao Hai, they will definitely approach Zhao Hai for a partnership. Zhao Hai also believed that Trezebo would spread Zhao Hai and Charlie’s relationship, after all, the man was one of Charlie’s closest confidants.

Trezebo would do everything to benefit Charlie, so he would naturally do his best to unite all of those under Charlie’s circle. After all, being united is the only way for their strength to stay strong. Trezebo promoting Zhao Hai to those Nobles would make them form a sense of respect for the new addition to the group.

With the matters in Jade Water City being completed, it was time for Zhao Hai’s group to leave. Aside from the Spatial Bag and essentials, Zhao Hai also left Mu’er with a Blood Hawk as well as 100 undead stored in the underground warehouse. Those undead were there to assist Mu’er if any situation comes up.

Now that he didn’t need to worry about Jade Water City, and along with the repairs on the Haven being finished, Zhao Hai was now hurrying along to trade with the Shrimp Tribe. He was worried that if he took too long, the Shrimp people might forget him.

He went to say goodbye to Charlie but didn’t expect the prince to actually deliver him to the Haven personally. This moved Zhao Hai, while at the same time startling Charlie’s subordinates.

Charlie was a prince, for him to be acting very close with Zhao Hai was a surprise. What’s most important was the fact that he wasn’t only intimate with Zhao Hai, he was also being respectful, which made them even more dumbfounded.

..

On the other hand, Zhao Hai didn’t know was that his situation with the Calci Family was currently going downhill. Smith wrote about his thoughts about the matter to his brothers so that they may support him. He wanted to convey that they musn’t offend Zhao Hai. He wanted the family to just partner up with Zhao Hai and not force him.

However, Smith didn’t expect that his brothers actually didn’t support him. Smith also understood why, his brothers didn’t get to meet Zhao Hai, moreover, Zhao Hai’s interaction with the family was very short. His brothers wanted more understanding of Zhao Hai to support Smith in this matter.

But while the brothers were taking their time in observing Zhao Hai, Juwan was not. Juwan hadn’t suffered such a huge loss of face since he was born. Zhao Hai snatching his ship, throwing him on a boat, and having Smith save him was the most humiliating thing that he experienced. Because of this, the only thing in his mind recently was revenge.

After returning to the clan, he immediately reported his interaction with Zhao Hai, of course with a few additions here and there. He expressed that Zhao Hai didn’t respect the family. Juwan was painting himself to be the good guy who was being bullied by an evil character.

As a result of this, the Calci Family’s view of Zhao Hai became worse and worse. Although Smith had written good reviews for Zhao Hai, the effect of a grieving man in comparison to some letters on a paper was very far.

Adding on to the fact that the family had massive interest for the products on Zhao Hai’s hands, they wanted to pressure Zhao Hai and see whether he would fold.

At this time, information came to the family that Zhao Hai had arrived at Jade Water City and was staying at the City Lord’s Mansion. They also found out about his relationship with Charlie and how the Third Prince was placing importance to him.  He even got into conflict with the Second Prince.

When this news came to the family, Smith became regretful, he wrote another letter to the family that Zhao Hai cannot become their enemy. If Zhao Hai forms an enmity with the family, they would certainly suffer huge setbacks.

But the family didn’t listen, for them Zhao Hai was being ungrateful. Not only did they not listen to Smith and restore their relationship with Zhao Hai, they instead decided to teach Zhao Hai a lesson. Therefore, these past few days, they mobilized their spies inside Jade Water City to gather information.

Unfortunately for them, Zhao Hai was very low-key inside Jade Water City. He rarely went out, just like how he was back in Sky Water City.

Zhao Hai’s actions left the Calci Family not knowing what to do. Even if the family was an established Noble family, they wouldn’t dare attack the City Lord’s Mansion, a place where the Third Prince Charlie resides in.

But when they found out about Zhao Hai’s shop inside the city, they were happy. They wanted to destroy Zhao Hai’s shop to teach him a lesson.

But again, they were disappointed. Upon further inquiries, they found out that the shop was a gift from Charlie to Zhao Hai. If the place was bought was Zhao Hai, they were free to destroy it, but with Charlie in the mix, it became another matter.

Even if Great Families didn’t care about Zhao Hai, they didn’t have a choice but give Charlie some face. Otherwise, not only would Charlie get offended, the Rosen Imperial clan would also get involved.

Don’t think that it was only Nobles who pay attention to their face, the Imperial Clan was also extremely protective of theirs, even more than those of established Nobles. No matter what, the Calci Family was residing inside Rosen Empire. If the family did decide to push things too far, then the Imperial Family wouldn’t be polite. If an established Noble and an Imperial Clan goes head to head, the one who would suffer more losses would certainly be the established Noble family.

Since the Calci Family was unable to make a move inside Jade Water City, they shifted their focus on Zhao Hai. They believed that Zhao Hai wouldn’t stay inside the city forever.

And at last, Zhao Hai was leaving Jade Water City. What the family didn’t expect was that Charlie would personally come and bade Zhao Hai farewell. This gesture was naturally understood by the family.

Regarding this scenario, the family was unprepared. They were hesitant in taking action against Zhao Hai. In the end, the man in charge of their operations in Jade Water City could only send word back to the headquarters and wait for their instruction.

Chapter 409: Rank Promotion

Zhao Hai didn’t know too much about the actions of the Calci Family. He thought that Smith already had the situation under control. He didn’t expect that Smith had yet to get the support of his other brothers. Being alone, Smith wasn’t able to deal with the problem

But it didn’t take too long before he was informed about the situation. The second day after he left Jade Water City, Zhao Hai received a letter from Smith sent via a Blood Hawk. In the letter were the recent and future actions that the Calci Family had planned. Smith didn’t urge Zhao Hai to be patient this time, instead he wanted Zhao Hai to teach the family a lesson.

This didn’t mean that Smith wanted to cut ties with the family. He just wanted to make Zhao Hai teach the stubborn elders of the family a lesson they wouldn’t forget. He wanted to make them understand that there were people in this world that cannot be touched. He wanted Zhao Hai to show the family how capable he is.

Zhao Hai didn’t think that Smith would actually urge him to do this. He handed Smith’s letter to Laura and smiled, “Look at this. I didn’t think that Big Brother Smith is actually a very radical person.”

Laura received the letter and looked at it, then she snorted and said, “This is nothing special, I can understand why Brother Smith did this. If the Markey family had people like Brother Smith, then we wouldn’t have experienced what we did. How about you, Brother Hai, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Why wouldn’t we agree? After all, we only have a good relationship with Brother Smith. It’s better if we teach them a lesson now in order to make them understand Brother Smith’s words. Right, in two days, the Goldmetal fruit will be ready. At that time, your rank will be improved. With what is going to occur, we happen to have a place to practice our skills.”

When Laura heard what Zhao Hai said, she smiled. It was indeed like what Zhao Hai said, now that the Goldmetal Tree is already mature, it was only a matter of time before it could bear some fruits. For the entire tree’s lifetime, Zhao Hai could get 80 Goldmetal Fruits.

The Goldmetal tree is a level 60 plant, it has 8 batches of its fruit period, it could produce 10 fruits each time, making it very precious. Even though the fruit had already been producing fruits, Laura and the others chose not eat it immediately. Everyday they would drink the Fluid of Life inside the Space before practicing, making their body in top shape for the time they will eat the Goldmetal Fruit.

Because of this preparation period, Zhao Hai spent a lot of gold coins letting the Multipurpose Processing Machine produce some low-level supplementary potions for Laura and the others to take in. Although it couldn’t improve their strengths directly, those potions could increase their body’s quality. When the last batch of fruits gets produced tomorrow, Zhao Hai decided to make Laura and the others eat the Goldmetal Fruit.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura, “Laura, what mount do you think is good to use? Now that Grandpa Kun has started teaching me how to ride, I think we should consider what mount we need to use in the future.”

Laura shook her head and said, “I think we shouldn’t be hasty in selecting a mount. I’ve seen that there are a lot of strange animals that is available in the Space’s store. When the time comes, we can just buy them and use them as our mounts.”

Zhao Hai didn’t oppose, inside the Space, there were even some mythological Chinese beasts recorded. These beast included some with a dragon’s bloodline, all of them equal to a 9th rank expert in strength. Having 9th rank beasts as mounts would certainly be very domineering.

Now that Zhao Hai had started to learn riding skills, he could now ride horses casually. But if he were to fight on horseback, he will fall behind. However, because of his rapid increase in strength, he could still contend against a 6th rank warrior.

A day quickly passed by. On the second day, Zhao Hai entered the Space early and waited for the last batch of Goldmetal Fruits to be matured.

Before long, Cai’er collected the last batch of fruits before using the land to plant another tree. Zhao Hai withdrew three Goldmetal Fruits and prepared to give one of them to Laura while the other two to Blockhead and Rockhead.

Although the strengths of Blockhead and Rockhead weren’t bad, their progress was too slow. This made the two very worried. But now that they finally found something that could aid them in improving their strengths, the two were naturally very happy.

According to Cai’er, Laura can only eat half of the fruit while Blockhead and Rockhead can eat them whole. Zhao Hai divided one fruit into two before handing the two halves to Laura. For Blockhead and Rockhead, he gave two full fruits.

The three people looked excitedly at the Goldmetal Fruit. In all honesty, Meg and the others were somewhat envious, but they knew that they weren’t compatible with the Goldmetal Fruit, it was quite a pity.

Zhao Hai looked at the three people and smiled faintly, “Go and eat it. After doing so, go stabilize your bodies, don’t forget that we may get into some battles in the next few days.”

The three nodded, then with their hearts beating fast, they ate the Goldmetal Fruit. Blockhead and Rockhead were the first to feel something, their stomachs rumbled as energy filled their bodies to the point of explosion. The two immediately sat down and circulated their Battle Qi.

Laura’s situation was also similar, but her reaction was much more mild since she only ate half of the fruit. But she also sat down and started to cultivate.

Zhao Hai looked anxiously at the three, he knew that this moment was very important to them. Although the Space said that they could tolerate the Goldmetal Fruit, it didn’t stop Zhao Hai and the others from worrying.

The trio took eight hours before they woke up one after the other. At this time, Kun and Green were also inside the Space. The two were also looking anxiously at the three.

The first one to wake up was Laura, she looked at the surrounding people and smiled faintly, “I’ve made everyone worry.”

Zhao Hai immediately replied, “Don’t worry about that, how are you? Did you rank up?” Looking at the nervous face of ZHao Hai, Laura’s heart warmed as she said, “I feel great, Now my strength has reached the peak of 6th rank. I believe that I’ll reach 8th rank when I eat the next half of the fruit.”

Zhao Hai relaxed and became happy. At this point, Kun happily laughed and said, “Fantastic! Young Lady, you have finally ranked up.”

All the people who were trying their best to cultivate didn’t only do so for their own safety, but also for their longevity. An ordinary person’s life could only reach 100 years old. But an 8th rank expert can reach 200. In order to live longer, everybody cultivated hard, this was especially true for Nobles.

This was because they didn’t need to worry about their livelihood, they had all the time to practice.

At this time, Blockhead and Rockhead also woke up. Both of them wore relieved expressions because they didn’t have any accidents. The duo’s level had also reached 8th rank.

Two more 8th ranks had been added to the group, this was good for them. Green took the two for a spar to see their new strengths.

Perhaps because they were still not accustomed to their new strength, Blockhead and Rockhead’s moves in the beginning were very stiff. But the two started to slowly adapt and began to block Green’s attacks. One must know that Green was a pinnacle expert among 8th ranks, ordinary 8th rank warriors could only survive for a few seconds under Green’s assault. For Blockhead and Rockhead to block his attacks at this point showed the innate strengths that the two possessed.

After some time, Green laughed and retrieved his Spirit Wind sword. He looked at the two happily and said, “Good, good! You boys have become strong. With the two of you working together, you already have the strength of the pinnacle of 8th rank. If an ordinary 8th rank meets the two of you, then he will certainly have a bad day. Hahaha. I can finally rest assured. You two listen to me, from now on you must wholeheartedly protect the young master. If even a single hair of the Young Master gets missing, I will have to scold the two of you myself.”

Blockhead and Rockhead were both orphans since their childhood. Although it was the Buda Clan who took them in, it was Green who took care of them. This made the two treat Green with the respect and admiration that a son might have for his father. Therefore, they would obey every instruction coming out of Green’s mouth.

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “Grandpa Green, it’s fine. Just make them assist you, there’s currently no need for them to protect me right now.”

Green laughed and said, “That’s true, but there’s nothing in Iron Mountain Fort that these two can help with. The school teachers back there are also undead, they didn’t need help. Young Master, just let them go with you to accumulate experience.”

Zhao Hai looked at Blockhead and Rockhead then nodded, “Alright, it’s good for them to come with me and get some experience. They might assume an important position in the future.”

Green and the others laughed. At this time, Zhao Hai remembered that they hadn’t been out of the Space for a day so he immediately went back to the Haven. Fortunately, there was nothing wrong on the ship, Zhao Hai felt relief.

When Zhao Hai went back to the Space, Laura was having a spar with Kun. It seems like Kun also wanted to see how strong Laura had become.

Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them and just did his own training. Since Zhao Hai didn’t train in fighting before, even if he has 8th rank strength,  his stances were still full of unnecessary movements. Compared to Laura who trained since childhood, Zhao Hai’s moves were very poor. This made him put in more effort in the hopes of bridging the gap between his and Laura’s strengths.

Chapter 410: Devilish Idea

The group trained rigorously inside the Space while the Haven peacefully sailed the seas. Although the ship was alone, other ships wouldn’t attack it as long as there wasn’t enmity between them. After all, it was not easy to attack an armored ship.

…

Smith’s situation was quite different from Zhao Hai’s idle life. The hair on Smith’s head had almost turned white, he couldn’t help but worry. Although he promised Zhao Hai that the matter with the family would get taken care of, Smith wasn’t sure whether Zhao Hai would still cooperate with the family. If Zhao Hai drops their partnership, the family would be losing big.

But no matter how hard he urged the family, nobody listened to him. Smith was almost convinced that the elders of the family had stones for their brains, seeing how stubborn they were regarding the situation.

He already knew that the family had sent some people to deal with Zhao Hai. Moreover, there were experts among them, 10 8th ranks, along with 20 armed cargo ships.

Such a force was quite formidable, but Smith was sure that this group wouldn’t be able to deal with Zhao Hai. Smith was clear that Zhao Hai was someone who didn’t show mountains nor seas. Nobody should look down on his strength.[1]

But Smith’s sentiments were useless, the family wouldn’t listen to him. Smith was afraid that they still wouldn’t stop even if the family suffers losses in dealing with Zhao Hai.

Smith knew that he and Zhao Hai would still be friends after these two conflicts. But Smith wasn’t sure how Zhao Hai would retaliate, would he go head to head against the family?

The more he thought about this, the more painful his head became. Smith just sat there, staring at the ceiling not knowing what to do.

At this time, a gentle voice can be heard, “Father, what’s wrong? Why are you unhappy?”

Smith looked up and saw Megan. Even if he was unhappy, he couldn’t stop himself from smiling upon seeing his lovable daughter, “Megan, aren’t you going outside to play? Don’t worry about me, just go and see your friends.”

Megan actually shook her head and said, “I don’t want to go with them. I like Sister Laura and Sister Meg. If I play around with them, I get to learn a lot of things. My friends look like they don’t have any goals aside from eating and chatting about marriage. There’s nothing else that they want to do, it’s too boring.”

Smith looked at Megan in shock. He didn’t expect Megan to say such a thing. Ever since she was young, Megan was the family’s princess. Everybody spoiled her and didn’t allow her to suffer some problems. All of the dark influences were also driven away from Smith. In the eyes of the people, Megan’s life was full of rainbows and sunshine.

Because of this, the Calci Family became too protective when Megan got attacked.

Moreover, Smith already prepared Megan’s right of inheritance. This way, when she marries, her dowry would be rich. Then she wouldn’t worry about her future, she can do what she wants, whether it be eating or playing, she can do everything.

But now, Megan told Smith that playing around became boring. This made Smith’s head dizzy, he didn’t know what to do.

Smith looked at Megan with a puzzled expression, “Megan, why did you suddenly think of that? Did someone tell you? You don’t need to worry about money, our Calci Family isn’t like those ordinary families. With the strength of our family, you don’t need to worry about anything.”

Megan shook her head and said, “I don’t mean money, I want to contribute to the family. I don’t want to be my friends who just live idly, eating and waiting for death. Look at Sister Laura and Sister Meg, they are travelling around with Mister Zhao Hai, that would be good.”

Smith stared blankly at Megan, he didn’t think that Megan would have these thoughts in her mind. Smith sighed as he looked at Megan, he knew that his darling daughter had finally grown up.

Smith looked at Megan and said, “Megan, why would you have such thoughts? You know that Laura didn’t do that because they chose to, it is because they have to. What they are doing should be very tiring.”

Megan grunted, “I know that such matters are tiring, but I find that kind of woman to be attractive, otherwise I think one could only be useless.”

Smith shook his head and sighed, he really didn’t know what to say. Looking at the slim and graceful Megan, Smith sighed again. In a blink of an eye, his daughter had finally arrived at the age of getting married. But on this continent, who was worthy of getting Megan?

For a doting father like Smith, he always thought that Megan was the best. In his mind, no man deserves her. Because of this, he didn’t have any marriage candidates in mind.

A Great Family like the Calcis didn’t need to marry for political reasons. Moreover, the proportion between male and female in the clan is very skewed. This made is so that males didn’t receive that much attention while Megan did.

Up until now, there had been no engagements that came to Megan. But when Smith thought about Laura, Zhao Hai’s face came up This made Smith startled, he hurriedly shook his head to get rid of this sudden idle thought.

But thoughts were sometimes akin to devils. It kept hovering around Smith’s mind, he couldn’t go for a time without considering Zhao Hai. He had to agree that Zhao Hai was a good man. He regarded sentiments heavily, knew when to advance or retreat, and was also quite formidable. Even if he had two fiances, it was common for a noble in the continent to have more than one wife. Moreover, there was a harmonious relationship between Laura and Meg.

Megan stood there and watched as Smith didn’t talk for quite some time. She asked, “Dad, Dad, what’s wrong? What are you thinking about?” Smith recovered and smiled at Megan, “Oh, it’s nothing. You go now. I’ll go ask Uncle Phil to arrange something for you tomorrow. Go see your mother, or else she would scold me.”

Megan nodded with an excited face, then she turned around and went off. Looking at Megan’s departing back, Smith sighed and muttered, “Maybe having her marry Zhao Hai wouldn’t be a bad idea.”

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t have any thought that Smith would have any idea of marrying Megan to him. In all honesty, Zhao Hai didn’t have much contact with Megan, he didn’t even know what he would do when interacting with her. He was now currently satisfied with his life, he was also satisfied with having Laura and Meg as his fiancees.

Zhao Hai was someone who gets easily contented. When he was back on Earth, even if he only had a few earnings from his royalties, he was still very happy. As long as he has food to eat ,a place to live, and can do all the things he liked, then he was satisfied.

When he arrived at Ark Continent, he was also quite contented. He had the Space to plant in, two beautiful fiancees, quite a number of loyal subordinates, and a ton of undead. His current life was good.

But he also felt that he shouldn’t get satisfied with his current situation. He knew that he could still do more. Just as what the famous Chinese Surgeon Qiu Fazu said: Cultivate the need to know what is not known, study hard, or just be content.[2]

This famous saying was Zhao Hai’s motto, even if he was a contented person, he would still do his best in handling matters. He always wanted to find out about his own deficiencies, and continue to improve himself, hoping that he can reach a higher level than he was before.

This was the same at the current time, he was satisfied with his life, but he knows that he wasn’t a writer anymore. He was a landed Noble, he needs to do business to improve his territory. Although he also thought that the territory is already doing good, he knew that it could do better. This was why he’s currently unsatisfied.

For his goals, he needed to overcome all obstacles, therefore he didn’t become afraid of challenges. He knew that difficulties are your enemies. If you turn away and flee from your problems, it will be like showing your back to the enemy. Your life and death will no longer be in your hands. So instead of running away, you should do your best to overcome your enemies. Even if you fail, at least you were the one who decided your fate and not others.

So Zhao Hai chose to confront Southern King, he chose to confront the Radiant Church. Although he hid in the Prairie, it was because he was pursued by the church, repelling him and making him leave. Choosing to leave is not equal to running away.

At this moment, Zhao Hai was training his martial arts in the Space. He wanted to improve his strength. Also, he actually enjoyed doing martial arts. As a Chinese man, he always had the martial dream, and for a novelist like Zhao Hai, even more so. Now that it was possible for him to do cultivate, he naturally would jump on the chance of being a master.

At the same time, Zhao Hai was also waiting for the Calci Family. Smith told him to teach the family a lesson, so Zhao Hai had to comply. Even if Smith didn’t say so, he would still do it. Zhao Hai believes that Smith knew this, this was why he sent the letter, to maintain the two’s relationship and leave a path of retreat for the future.

Zhao Hai didn’t object to this, after all, he was disgusted with the Calci Family. But he also has good feelings about Smith, he also wanted to keep their relationship. Thus, Zhao Hai sent a reply letter to Smith, though the content was ordinary, he knew that Smith will understand what it meant.

Regarding the coming attack from the Calci Family, Zhao Hai didn’t care. He knew that the Calci Family wouldn’t send a 9th rank after him. Otherwise, Smith wouldn’t tell him to teach the family a lesson, instead he would tell Zhao Hai to run away.

Zhao Hai attention was more inclined towards the Merfolk. This was his first time trading with the sea dwellers, in fact, this was the first for the continent. He didn’t know how the Merfolk would act.

He knew that the Humans and the Merfolk had been at odds for years. But haven’t they really traded with each other? For Zhao Hai, this was inconceivable.

But Zhao Hai also knew that the ships present around these parts are almost all Pirate ships. And on these pirate ships were people who weren’t that strong. If they go far into the deep sea, their ships would definitely suffer some accidents. So it wouldn’t be possible for them to trade with the sea-dwellers.

If Zhao Hai’s strength wasn’t enough, then he might’ve become food for the Shrimp Tribe. Moreover, the general outlook of the people from the continent regarding the Merfolk were mostly negative. Adding on to the mysterious nature of the Merfolk’s life at sea, Humans wouldn’t like to get in contact with them. Because of this, Human merchants cannot just do business like what they did with the Beastmen.

The reason why Zhao Hai was able to be welcomed by the Beastmen as well as the Merfolk was because he considered them as equals. Not aliens that were looked down upon.

But if an expert with the same strength as Zhao Hai meets those Shrimp Tribesmen, they would immediately kill them, much less talk about business.

Zhao Hai’s worry was how the Merfold would act during their trade. He didn’t know whether they would treat his as a normal partner would, or just take him as a fool and undervalue his goods.

Although this was a risky move, Zhao Hai still wanted to do it. This was because he was clear that if this business goes through successfully, his Buda Clan would get another ace up their sleeves.

The fifth day after leaving Jade Water City, Zhao Hai’s ship had left the waters governed by the Rosen Empire’s navy and officially entered international waters. However, Zhao Hai also knew that troubles would arrive, the Calci Family’s attack would arrive soon.

And just like what Zhao Hai expected, one the second day that he entered international waters, the Calci Family’s people came. All in all, they had 20 armed ships, 15 were three-masted ships, while 5 were five-masted ironclad ships. Such scene was domineering, only a Great Family like the Calci Family could afford to do such a thing.

Zhao Hai calmly observed from the monitor as he awaited the arrival of the other party. While doing so, he notice a familiar person in the monitor, and that person was none other than Juwan!

* * *

bù xiǎn shān bù lù shuǐ –  lit. to not show the mountain and to not reveal the water (idiom); fig. to hide the key facts

Qiu Fazu – a Chinese surgeon and a saviour of Jewish prisoners. In the People’s Republic of China, he is considered the father of modern Chinese surgery. Note: not sure about the exact saying, there’s nothing in the internet

Chapter 411: Face-off

Zhao Hai thought that Juwan wouldn’t appear, but when he saw him on the monitor, Zhao Hai understood why Juwan was so daring. On Juwan’s side were five people, two among them were Mages and three were Warriors, all of which were 8th ranks. When Zhao Hai looked at the other ships, there were also another two Mages and three Warriors spread out among them, also 8th ranks.

Seeing these people, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but shrink. Ten 8th rank experts, the Calci Family really went big this time, but will it be useful against him?

Zhao Hai surveyed the ships again. The ships were all good weaponized ships, and the people on board weren’t weak. At first glance, one could see that they were all elite troops. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but snort.

Looking at the ships and hearing Zhao Hai snort, Laura asked, “Brother Hai, what do we do? Will we kill these people?”

Zhao Hai replied with a serious tone, “If we don’t hurt them, they will never learn. We’ll leave the 8th ranks and Juwan’s group alone. Let’s take their ships since they did all the trouble of delivering them to us. Send the command to unarm our cannons, let their ship approach. Let’s play with them this time.”

Jinan immediately transmitted the orders, Laura didn’t oppose the decision. At this time, they only have the Haven. Naturally, they had more ships in the Space, but they couldn’t use them.

Zhao Hai had 20 ships currently on hand. The Haven that they were currently on, the Swordfish being repaired in Jade Water City, the five ships gotten from the Markey Family, and the rest are stored in the Space. If Zhao Hai suddenly released the other ships to fight the Calci Family, his secrets will be exposed; which he didn’t want to. Since it had come to this, Zhao Hai just had Jinan put the sails down while disallowing the gunners from firing in order to let the other party see. If they didn’t take the hint and opened fire, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of retaliating.

Zhao Hai also didn’t plan on firing because he placed some importance on the 20 ships of the Calci Family. If they somehow destroy one, Zhao Hai would certainly grieve.

Laura looked at the 20 ships that were slowly approaching with anticipation. Now that her strength had reached 8th rank, she was quite eager to test it. She had trained since an early age, Zhao Hai was not a match against her.

Since Laura was a knight, her footwork, spearplay and swordplay are all quite fierce. Just based on techniques, she wouldn’t lose against Blockhead and Rockhead. This was even more true for a newbie like Zhao Hai, he wasn’t her opponent.

Laura’s confidence was currently very high. Her spars with Kun were now useless, she wanted to have a real fight. Zhao Hai had no choice but to take some metal out from the warehouse and made the Processing Machine produce a Tang Blade for her.

It must be said that the weapons in the Ark Continent are very good. But Zhao Hai was somewhat partial towards the weapons from Earth. The Tang Blade was like a Japanese Warrior’s Katana, it was not only sharp, it’s killing potential was also very good. Because of these characteristics, Zhao Hai chose to give Laura one.

What he didn’t expect was that when Kun inspected the blade, he was attracted to it as well. So Zhao Hai could only create another blade for him. Now, Laura and Kun both kept their blades almost always at their sides.

Another thing he didn’t expect was that when Blockhead and Rockhead saw Kun’s new weapon, they wanted one for themselves as well. But the Tang Blade wasn’t a heavy weapon, it wasn’t like the two handed heavy sword that the two usually used. Since they weren’t compatible with the Blade, Zhao Hai gave them a large machete with a lengthened hilt. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile upon seeing the faces of the two.

Although blades and swords were different, people from the Ark Continent pay more attention to the weight of the weapons. Even if the weapon was considered heavy, women generally would take the lighter version of it. In Chinese martial arts, swords were meant to be swift while blades are for hard attacks. Obviously, it was impossible for a heavy sword to take the swift route. Zhao Hai observed that most moves in the Ark Continent involves chopping and swiping. This gave Zhao Hai the idea to hand his people blades which were more suitable for their moves than swords.

Upon receiving their new weapons, the group immediately went to familiarize themselves with it. Seeing the advantages brought by their new weapons, everybody was happy. They trained in the Space daily, and now that they have the opportunity to use it, they were naturally excited.

The Calci Family’s ships slowly surrounded Zhao Hai’s Haven. Juwan’s ship went forward while the others kept a safe distance while at the same time aiming their cannons towards Zhao Hai’s vessel.

Seeing the actions of the ships, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Good, they seemed to have learned something. But they were not smart enough since they came here.”

Laura smiled and said, “Juwan is certainly not smart. What Juwan wanted to see is your frightened face. This is the problem with young nobles, in his opinion, he had lost massive face because of you. So this time, he came with this force in order to make you lose face. Only after achieving this will his heart become comfortable.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “The attitude of an Idiot. If I just dealt with him properly before, he wouldn’t’ have come back here. I’ll make sure to take note of that.”

Laura and the others just listened to Zhao Hai and smiled. At this point, Juwan’s ship arrived and placed its walking plank. Juwan looked very smug as he boarded the Haven. At his side were several 8th rank warriors in addition to the Manager that the Family had sent.

.Besides these people, Juwan was also followed by more than 20 warriors. All of them were at 6th and 7th ranks. They all looked at Zhao Hai with an inquisitive gaze.

Zhao Hai just calmly looked at Juwan’s group. Juwan looked proudly at Zhao Hai and then turned his eyes to Laura and the others.

Looking at Juwan’s actions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but wrinkle his brows and said, “Juwan, why did you come? Do you intend to block me?”

Juwan stared at Zhao Hai, not expecting him to ask that question. He didn’t know why Zhao Hai said that, he stole more than ten ships from Juwan. Why would he ask that”

After some time, Juwan recovered, and with a red face he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, have you been scared silly? You really don’t know why I came today?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I really don’t know. How about you tell me?”

Juwan’s face was dark, his blood vessels were almost bursting. While gasping for breath he replied, “You snatched my ship and threw me on a boat, and now you ask why I came here? I told you, I will set our account straight one day. Today you must give me back my ships and the fire fishes as well for compensation. Also, make those beautiful women accompany me. Otherwise, you will become fish food today.”

Zhao Hai’s expression turned cold as he stared at Juwan, “Juwan, is this really what you want to say? Is this what a Calci Family member should say? Aren’t you afraid of shaming your Calci Family?”

Juwan’s expression changed, “You’re wasting your breath. Follow my orders immediately, or else I would be impolite.”

Zhao Hai looked at Juwan and laughed, “Good, Juwan, good. Does the Calci Family really think that these 8th ranks are enough to deal with me?”

Hearing Zhao Hai’s words, Juwan’s expression changed. It was also the same for the 8th ranks behind him. Zhao Hai just smiled at Juwan as he continued, “You really are naive if you think that these few experts on my ship can intimidate me. Today, let me show you my own method.” Then he waved his hand as large quantities of undead appeared on the sea’s surface.

Juwan and his companions didn’t know that the sea was already frozen. And just when their complexion changed color, Laura and the others went forward to fight them.

Juwan didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s companions would actually be experts. But what annoyed him more was the fact that Zhao Hai himself had taken up a weapon and fought against his subordinate with delight. And unexpectedly, he wasn’t a bad Warrior.

Although none of the undead under Zhao Hai touched Juwan, his face’s complexion was still pale. He knew that Zhao Hai’s subordinates didn’t attack him because they were afraid of Juwan, it was because they were putting the Calci Family into consideration. If Zhao Hai didn’t, all of them wouldn’t be alive right now.

His thoughts were correct, and while he was spaced out, Zhao Hai already assaulted the other ships. The experts on those ships were all seized under the command of Zhao Hai. Since he didn’t want to have a mortal enmity against the Calci Family, and he was just planning on teaching them a lesson, he just made his undead capture all of the key Calci Family people present.

Seeing his party being captured, Juwan paled even more. He knew that he wouldn’t’ be able to recover after this. At this time, the 8th ranks who fought Zhao Hai’s group were slowly getting captured one after the other. Only the one who fought Zhao Hai was holding on. Juwan could see that Zhao Hai’s fighting techniques weren’t strong, he was about the same level as a 6th rank warrior.

But Juwan didn’t underestimate Zhao Hai. This was because he knew that Zhao Hai didn’t focus on Battle Qi, he was a Mage.

A Mage that battles while carrying a weapon and was somewhat on par with a Warrior, this fact made Juwan think that the world had gone crazy.

Chapter 412: Recording Magic

Everybody knows that practicing Battle Qi and Magic at the same time wouldn’t yield good results, it was a waste of effort. But Zhao Hai wasn’t very different compared to a 6th rank Warrior. In fact, the was displaying strength that was superior to a 6th rank. If Zhao Hai didn’t use Magic before, Juwan might have believed that he was a Warrior.

Juwan also took note of Zhao Hai’s age. For him to reach 6th rank this young was already remarkable

However, Juwan eventually thought that his thinking was wrong. Zhao Hai was brandishing his sword and his moves were very ordinary. Juwan’s subordinate was actually gaining the upper hand.

Although Juwan wasn’t very learned when it came to martial arts, he could see that Zhao Hai was only like this because he was inexperienced, not because he was weak.

Juwan was too angry that he didn’t know what to say. He wasn’t a fool, when he looks at Zhao Hai’s situation, it was very clear that his subordinate was only used as a sparring partner. But Juwan couldn’t do anything about it, there was currently a large group of undead paying attention to him.

The undeads were each holding a sword, and it was evident that they were all high level. They were also quite close to him, casting magic at this point was useless.

Suddenly, Zhao Hai’s group drew back, leaving Juwan along with his experts. Juwan’s expression changed, he wants to tie down Zhao Hai’s group, but it was already too late. At this point, Juwan’s group was slowly being surrounded by the group of undead.

Zhao Hai touched his sword with his hand and looked at Juwan coldly, “Juwan, don’t think that I’m afraid of you. Your puny force isn’t enough for me to get frightened. I only chose to stop in consideration for Brother Smith’s face. I hope you understand that this Zhao Hai is not your Calci Family’s dog that you can just command whenever you want. If you want to cooperate with me, then show some sincerity. I’ll be confiscating these ships, I’ll take them as compensation. I hope you relay my message correctly to the family. I hope you won’t reach my bottom line.”

At this point, the only people left were the 8th ranks, Juwan, and the Clan’s housekeeper.

Juwan didn’t dare to make a move, Zhao Hai looked at him and smiled faintly, “I will not kill you, the same is true for those 8th ranks, rest assured. But I will have to take the ships, you know the rules, it’s the same as last time.”

Juwan’s complexion turned uglier, he understood, in his previous attack against Zhao Hai, they were still close to the shorelines and were aided by the Rosen Empire’s navy. Travelling to Sky Water City from that point would take three days. But this time, they weren’t with the Empire’s navy and were in international waters, the closest port from here would take seven days of sailing. For such a distance, it would be very troublesome if they were to get lost.

Zhao Hai didn’t care, he just retrieved the additional undead on the ships and stored them to the Space before he got Juwan on a lifeboat. When Juwan looked at the 8th ranks that he brought, they were actually crippled by Zhao Hai, not killed. Afterwards, Zhao Hai threw them all into Juwan’s boat.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s methods, Juwan’s face turned for the worse. He knew that for an 8th rank expert to lose their means of practicing Battle Qi and Magic, it meant a fate worse than death. Zhao Hai was really ruthless.

After looking at Zhao Hai’s departing ship, Juwan became gloomy. He stared at the pale faced and unconscious 8th ranks then turned to his housekeeper and said, “Throw them into the sea, then report to the Family that they were all killed by Zhao Hai.”

His housekeeper couldn’t help but stare upon hearing Juwan, then his complexion changed as he replied, “Fifth Young Master, that isn’t proper. It’s a rule of the Family to take care of an 8th rank when they get injured. If Young Master does this, you would be violating the Family’s laws.”

Juwan coldly snorted and said, “Don’t talk nonsense. Killing them will enrage the family. Bringing them home like this would just make the elders scared of Zhao Hai.”

Just after he said that, Zhao Hai’s voice was suddenly heard, “The Third Young Master is unexpectedly ruthless. Hahaha. But you seem to forget that there’s a magic spell that could record you. I’ve already saved what you said. Haha. If you dare abandon these people, then don’t blame me if this recording suddenly falls into the hands of the people from your family.”

When Juwan heard Zhao Hai’s voice, his face changed. He knew how difficult it was for a Mage to use Recording Magic. They first need to use three elements, namely earth, wind, and water. Then they would have to practice making Composite Magic with those three. If Zhao Hai or his subordinate can use Recording magic, this meant that Zhao Hai was or had someone that was an Advanced Level Multi-element Mage. And Juwan knew the family’s stance regarding those Mages.

Juwan also knew that Recording Magic wasn’t an attack magic, it belonged to a class called Truth Magics. These magics were unable to be falsified and are the most credible evidences that Mages could present. If Zhao Hai indeed recorded his words and actions today, then he would be out of luck.

Don’t underestimate the influence brought by 8th rank experts. Although the Calci Family wouldn’t care if they died, Zhao Hai’s recording of Juwan’s actions would be a very big deal.

8th rank experts were exalted in most clans, but their tasks would most often involve going into dangerous missions. They serve an important role to every group they belong to.

With these duties, some of them would unavoidably die while on duty.  Those 8th ranks also have their own families, so if they die, what would happen to them? Without a source of income, how could they survive?

8th ranks also knew about this, so before they associate themselves into a Noble Clan, they would make them promise that if they get killed while on a mission, the Noble Clan should give their families protection and compensation. And if they don’t die and instead get crippled, the Clan should support them for their entire lifetime, they must take care of them.

If the Clan couldn’t meet those expectations, then all 8th ranks would stay away from them. And that scenario would be fatal to any Clan.

If the elders from the Calci Family found out about Juwan’s plans for the 8th ranks, then he would certainly be punished. Moreover, if the 8th ranks of the family were to hear about Juwan’s actions, then Juwan could forget about getting the position of Patriarch.

Although those 8th ranks didn’t have much influence, it would be a different story if they form an alliance.

8th rank experts were the bread and butter of a Family’s strength. If the 8th ranks knew that they were actually treated that way, then he wouldn’t get their support. Juwan would then be very hopeless.

Juwan wasn’t sad about losing 20 ships. For the Calci Family, those 20 ships weren’t a big deal. But what is a big deal was Zhao Hai’s recording of Juwan. This would make Juwan unable to do anything to Zhao Hai. If he still did, then Zhao Hai can just hand his recording over to the family.

When the housekeeper saw Juwan’s appearance, he knew that it was the end for Juwan. Although he was just sent by the Clan to monitor the fifth son, their fates have already been bound together. Because of this, he didn’t report a lot of Juwan’s atrocities back to the family. He did so in the hopes that Juwan may succeed in being the Patriarch, making his position rise as well. But seeing this scenario, he understood that it was now impossible.

Zhao Hai naturally couldn’t just leave Juwan to fend for himself at sea. So he immediately sent word to Smith, telling him of the result. But Smith was already expecting this outcome, he already had his people patrol around the sea while waiting for Zhao Hai’s letter, so when the time comes, his men could quickly respond.

Although Juwan was a disappointment, he was still Smith’s blood brother. Therefore, he still had to go and save him. He also knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t take Juwan’s life.

When Smith received Zhao Hai’s letter, he immediately sent word to the family’s ships, making them pick up Juwan as soon as possible. Smith knew that unlike last time, where Juwan made his moves inside Rosen Empire’s region, this time his younger brother was on international waters. If they take too long in retrieving Juwan, he may come into danger.

Actually Smith also considered the fact that even though Zhao Hai disliked Juwan for the repeated attacks against him, Zhao Hai still highly regarded Smith’s face . Zhao Hai would certainly ensure Juwan’s safety, otherwise his ties with the Calci Family would wither away.

Chapter 413: Rock Shrimp Tribe

There are a lot of juniors inside a Great Clan, for bloodline juniors, there were also quite plenty. Some of them were far related, some were direct, some can become successors, some cannot.

Juwan was in good graces with the elders of the Calci Family, he was very dear to their hearts, even higher than Smith. Because of this, when Juwan told them to deal with Zhao Hai, they didn’t oppose.

For a Great Clan like the Calci Family, they didn’t place too much importance to their 8th ranks. Therefore, Juwan thought that throwing them overboard was fine as long as nobody else knew and that they would provide monetary support to their families afterwards. Nobody would care about this small loss of their 8th rank experts.

This was why it should still be fine if Zhao Hai gets to kill a few 8th rank experts of the family. Killing 8th ranks to teach the family a lesson shouldn’t merit being mortal enemies with the Calci Family.

But if Zhao Hai were to deal with Juwan, his enmity with the family would flare up. It was said that unless one party gets extinguished, it was impossible to resolve hatred if a direct descendant of a clan gets killed. This was because Great Nobles place great importance in saving their face.

Because of this consideration, Zhao Hai let Juwan go while at the same time sending people to protect his safety. Zhao Hai understood that so long as he had Juwan’s recording about the 8th ranks, there was no possibility of Juwan becoming the family Patriarch.

For Zhao Hai, the recording was worthless, but for Juwan, it was something of huge importance. If Smith were to get his hands on the recording, he would have Juwan on his hands, his chances of winning the succession would increase.

Juwan being a playboy wasn’t a lie, but his position inside the hearts of the elders of the family couldn’t be underestimated. With Juwan’s support, Smith’s name within the elders of the family would be more regarded, for Smith this was huge.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think about that for now. He made the undead on board Juwan’s ships to sail towards a place where nobody could spot them then Zhao Hai stored them into the space. Afterwards, Zhao Hai had the Haven go directly to where he initially met the Shrimp Tribesmen.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to enter other areas of the deeps seas. He could just pick a place and wait there, however, he wouldn’t be sure if that place belonged to the Shrimp Tribe. If the territory of the Shrimp Tribe was very small, then it would be very easy to stumble upon some other tribe’s place.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived at the area where he last met the merfolk. But he didn’t stop, he just slowly went further while taking caution. He prepared himself for the possibility of being attacked by sea-dwellers. The borderline between the coastline areas and the deep seas was quite blurred. But sailors knew that the area beyond Ape Island and its surrounding islands was the Merfolk region, so they came upon themselves to make that region the border. As long as you stay well behind that region, they should be relatively safe from Merfolk attacks. If you dare sail past that point, then you must be prepared to face the possibility of being attacked by a sea-dweller with the strength equal to the continent’s 9th rank expert. And nobody wanted to experience that.

Zhao Hai’s ship slowly sailed along the deep sea, but what surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that they didn’t receive any attacks. Everything seemed ordinary, as though they were just sailing on the continent’s coastlines.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor with his brows wrinkling, this was because he didn’t spot a single one of those Shrimp Tribesman. He didn’t’ even see a single Merfolk, this made him quite puzzled.

At this time, Zhao Hai noticed something moving on the seafloor. Zhao Hai carefully observed it and saw a fish in the mud. It was a strange fish, it had the same color as the seabed, this must be why Zhao Hai wasn’t able to spot it earlier.

But this fish wasn’t considered to be a sea dweller. And because of Zhao Hai’s worries about the Merfolk, he didn’t even take the chance to absorb the fish into the Space.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think that a moment later, a group of Shrimp Tribesmen could be spotted on the monitor. The group looked very menacing, as if they were coming to sink the Haven.

Seeing the situation, Zhao Hai immediately used Ice Magic and froze the waters surrounding the Haven. This made the approaching Shrimp Tribesmen stare blankly, they weren’t expecting this move from Zhao Hai.

These Shrimp Tribesmen understood that Zhao Hai wanted to make contact with them, otherwise he wouldn’t use Ice Magic. This made them stop and stare at the ice wall with confused expressions.

Zhao Hai saw their mouths move, but he couldn’t hear anything. This made him puzzled, but he immediately recovered as he gave his greeting, “Sea dwelling friend, hello. I have received an invitation by your tribesman Crag to do business with you. I’ll have to ask you to please call him to the surface and meet me.”

After Zhao Hai expressed his intentions, he observed the reactions of the Shrimp people. The Shrimp Tribesmen naturally understood Zhao Hai’s words, so they gave each other a quick glance before they exposing their heads out of the sea’s surface.

One of the Shrimp Tribesmen who surfaced looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Do you really intend to do business with us?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Hello, Shrimp Tribe friend, I told Crag before that I would do trade with you. If you don’t believe me, you can ask Crag.”

The Shrimp Tribesman replied with a happy tone, “You wait here. Although we already heard about this matter from Crag, we are not sure if you are the one. I’ll immediately go call him over.” After that, the group disappeared into the sea.

Looking at these Merfolk, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. For the Humans to call them an alien race is too funny. These Merfolk looked like they didn’t have the the extremely doubting mind of humans, if they see you as a friend then you are a friend, if they think that you are an enemy, then you are an enemy. Their thoughts were very simple, they were the type of people that Zhao Hai liked. [1]

Before long, another group of Shrimp Tribesmen appeared in front of Zhao Hai, possibly including Crag with them. Why possibly? This was because to Zhao Hai’s eyes, all of these Shrimp Tribesmen looked very similar. It was like in the eyes of the Chinese, foreigners looked very similar to each other. This was also true for Foreigners, they also find it hard to differentiate one Chinese person from another.[2]

After the Shrimp people appeared on the surface, one of them looked at Zhao Hai and said, “My human friend, you finally appeared!! Hahaha. These days, I’ve almost become a joke in the tribe, they thought I was lying. My friend, come with me to see the Chief immediately.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Alright, friend. Guide me, but stay on the surface, otherwise I wouldn’t’ be able to follow you.”

The man was naturally Crag. He looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “That’s not a problem, my friend, you can just follow my mount.” Then he sank into the sea before a large shrimp appeared. This shrimp was as large as those that were absorbed into Zhao Hai’s Space.

After the large shrimp appeared on the surface, it sank back down again, but before disappearing, it left its whiskers above the water. Zhao Hai smiled, it seems like these Merfolk were smarter than the Beastmen.

Zhao Hai followed the shrimp’s whiskers, although he can see the sea’s situation, he didn’t want to reveal that fact to the Merfolk.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that the place where Crag was taking him was actually quite far. His ship has been sailing for three days straight before the shrimp stopped. At this time, Zhao Hai was basking in the sun while on the ship’s top deck, he wasn’t paying attention to the monitor. Now that the ship had stopped, he immediately got up.

At this moment, Crag appeared and smiled as he bowed, “Friend, our Chief will be seeing you, please wait a bit.” Zhao Hai returned the bow hastily, he didn’t want to seem rude to these Merfolk.

Just as Crag left, Zhao Hai took two steps back into the ship before opening the monitor. Upon seeing the screen, Zhao Hai was stunned along with Laura and the others who were behind him. They didn’t think that they would be able to see such a scene.

Currently, there was a very large coral reef underneath the sea. One couldn’t just imagine how large this reef was. Seen on it were Shrimp Tribesmen swimming all around. He could also see marine products as well as all kinds of fish. This made Zhao Hai stared blankly.

Before long, Zhao Hai can see a curled up Shrimp man appearing on the monitor. This Shrimp man wasn’t hunched back because he was a shrimp, but because he was old. On his face were wrinkles, and his antennae were drooped on the sides of his head. Held on his hand was a wooden cane. This image gave Zhao Hai the impulse to laugh.

They could float on sea, why was this Shrimp Tribesman carrying a cane? At the same time, Zhao Hai was somewhat surprised, do canes have any use on the sea?

However, Zhao Hai just stayed on his ship and awaited the other party’s arrival. Soon after, a group emerged along with the old Shrimp. The elderly Shrimp man looked at Zhao Hai and coughed twice before talking, “Hello my young Human friend, I’m Libben, Chief of the Rock Shrimp Tribe.”

Zhao Hai quickly bowed and said, “I greet the Chief, I am the Human merchant Zhao Hai, I’m very glad to meet you.”

Libben looked very satisfied with Zhao Hai, he looked at him, smiled, then nodded, “Young man, you make me very surprised, I have never seen a Human who speak to us with a manner like you did.”

Zhao Hai replied, “To think that the Chief has met other humans, I didn’t expect that. I thought I was the first to come in contact with your Rock Shrimp Tribe.”

Libben smiled and said, “I just tried to interact with Humans, but in the end it all failed. When they see us, they yell, it made me feel uncomfortable. Young Human friend, I heard that you came to trade with us, what do you want?”

After hearing Libben, Zhao Hai immediately answered, “Respectable Chief, I am a businessman, naturally I would want some marine products. For example, aquatic Magic Beasts, marine plants, some pearls, unique corals, as well as some rare sea ores. If you have any special products, I want those too. For my side, I have grain, ceramics, and metalwares.

Libben looked at Zhao Hai, “Human friend, then come take a look at this and see how much this is worth.” Then the old Chief took out a clam shell that wasn’t that big and handed it over to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai received the shell and opened it gently, obviously he didn’t expect to see an actual clam inside, this should be the Merfolk version of a Human’s pouch.

The actual content of the shell was what made Zhao Hai startled, there was actually an exceptionally huge pearl inside.

The pearl was about the size of Zhao Hai’s fist. Zhao Hai couldn’t remember a time where he saw a pearl bigger than what he was currently holding. Moreover, this pearl had a pale yellow varnish, it looked very beautiful.

Laura, who was standing behind Zhao Hai, exclaimed as she took the pearl from Zhao Hai’s hands, “Brother Hai, this is a treasure! This pearl alone is worth all of the supplies that Charlie provided us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Lidden and said, “Chief, your pearl is very precious. It can be traded for four ships’ worth of cargo. Will you agree with this exchange?”

Lidden looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “You’re an honest young man, I agree to the trade. You should know that since I’ve been the Chief of the Rock Shrimp Tribe for so long, I have the intuition to tell a person’s thoughts. I know that you didn’t lie, alright, you can take the pearl.”

When Zhao Hai heard Lidden, he was startled. He didn’t think that Lidden would have an ability like that. He couldn’t help but wipe some sweat off his brow, although this pearl was precious, it could at only trade for four ships’ worth of cargo at most. If the Shrimp Tribe was unhappy with the that trade, it wouldn’t be good.

Zhao Hai wanted a long term partnership with the Rock Shrimp Tribe, so he didn’t plan on deceiving them. He knew that the Shrimp People can also look up the value of this pearl, and when they find out that they were duped, they wouldn’t work with Zhao Hai again. At that point, Zhao Hai’s gain wouldn’t be worth the losses.

Zhao Hai waved his hand as four ships suddenly appeared on the sea’s surface. This action scared the Shrimp people, they didn’t think that Zhao Hai was able to release these many ships. It was probable that the Merfolk didn’t have Space Mages and Spatial Items, thus when they saw Zhao Hai’s movement, they were terrified.

On the other hand, Lidden stayed calm, he looked at this tribesmen and snorted, ‘Why are you flustered? That is Human Magic, very mysterious. Well, human friend, please drop your goods off on the sea, my people will take them away.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright.” Then he waved his hand as the undead on the ships began to dump the goods overboard.

* * *

So basically, Beastmen of the sea? XD

That’s racist bruh. Cmon.

Chapter 414: The Trade is Concluded

Zhao Hai noticed that as the goods were dropped overboard, they were immediately caught by the Shrimp Tribesmen and brought to the coral reef.

Some of those Shrimp people had red eyes, they knew how valuable Human goods were to their fellow sea-dwellers.

Merfolk society was a hierarchical one. Just like the Beastmen, they valued strength highly. When you put the Shrimp tribe along with Beastmen, they would rank alongside the Pig and Cattle Clans, almost belonging to the lowest level of society, the slaves. Otherwise, the Shrimp Race wouldn’t be living this close to Humans.

For a tribe like them, they must provide tributes to those strong Merfolk tribes each year. Or else they would be demoted to being slaves, or worse being eaten.

When it came to ruthlessness, the Beastmen wouldn’t compare to the Merfolk. At the very least, Beastmen wouldn’t eat their fellow Beastman. But for the Merfolk, once someone becomes a slave, even if you are a fellow Merman, you would inevitably become food. This kind of race has a term, they weren’t called slave, they would be called meals, or in other cases, food.

The Shrimp Tribe were busy all year round, although there were a lot of treasures in the sea, the tribute they needed to pay each year was also a lot. Sometimes, their required tribute wouldn’t be met, so they had no choice but take them away from the Humans. They would raid and battle human ships near their territory, after all, they were superior on water.

For the Merfolk, Human products were very valuable. For a small tribe like the Rock Shrimps, a small amount of human goods would suffice for their yearly tribute. This made attacking Humans at sea even more appealing.

However, they wouldn’t be able to do that regularly since the Merfolk and the Humans had an agreement. If their raids were to cause a war with the Humans, the Rock Shrimp Tribe would surely become a Food Tribe.

Because of this little contact with Humans, Libben was able to have an understanding about what Humans find valuable. What he gave Zhao Hai was the most precious thing that they had. The production of this pearl was closely controlled by the Clam Shell Tribe, almost all of the pearl produced came from their hands. This one pearl that Libben presented was something he luckily acquired when he was young.

He showed this pearl in order to see if Zhao Hai was honest. If the price that Zhao Hai gave was acceptable, then he would be their Merchant. But if he didn’t, they would attacking him and sink his ship. They would rather do that than be deceived.

This reflected the attitude of their kind, the classification of good and evil was very simple. Being an enemy or a friend was decided by a few words.

Fortunately, Zhao Hai’s performance satisfied Libben, he decided that they would form a long time partnership with Zhao Hai. He immediately told this decision to his own tribesmen as they floated on the surface of the sea.

Zhao Hai took the pearl and closed it. After a short while, everything on the ships were emptied. Then Zhao Hai turned to Libben and said, “Chief, I still have some Human grains. Would you like some?”

Libben smiled and said, “Of course, we’ll be trading with these.” Then he waved his hand as his tribesmen took out a lot of things.

Zhao Hai looked at these things and smiled. These were his main purpose in coming here, aquatic magic beasts, marine plants, and special corals.

Zhao Hai said while looking at the aquatic magic beasts, “These things are very good, I’ll trade for them. Chief, I’ll be loading these things first.” Then the Shrimp Tribesmen carried the aquatic magic beasts along with their containers on board Zhao Hai’s ship.

Then Zhao Hai waved his hand as large quantities of grain appeared on the sea. As the tribesmen were transporting the grains, Zhao Hai turned to Libben and said, “Chief, I think today’s transaction has to end here. Can I know if the Chief wants to trade with me again next time?”

Libben smiled and said, “We will trade with mister whenever he comes, rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s great, then I’ll ask to be excused.” Afterwards, Zhao Hai made his ships turn around and sail slowly.

At this time, Crag arrived at Libben’s side with an excited face, “Chief, these things are more than enough for us to pay the tribute. It seems like the Human didn’t deceive us.”

Libben looked at Crag and smiled, “Little one, this time I’ll have to thank you for bringing this honest Human to us. Now he will keep trading with us, also, go inform the other tribes and make them join our trades with the Human.”

Crag looked puzzled, “Chief, I don’t understand? Are our products cheap?”

Libben sighed and said, “Little one, you are too naive. Although these products are very good, it wouldn’t be good if we are the only ones that get it. Out tribe cannot swallow a benefit this big. Only when we ally up with the surrounding tribes will have the security of not being exterminated. Moreover, we also need more things to be exchanged in order to preserve a long partnership with the Human.”

Crag gave a nod that seems to border within understanding and not understanding. Libben didn’t add any more and just waved his hand as he led his people back into the sea.

Zhao Hai was now inside the Space, he saw that the plants that the Shrimp Tribe had given him weren’t ordinary, they were edible; Zhao Hao even saw kelp among them. The various magic beasts were mostly shrimps, it seems like the Rock Shrimp Tribe was very capable in raising shrimp.

When Zhao Hai absorbed these things into the Space, nothing happened, it seems like their levels were too low.

However, Zhao Hai actually earned big this time since he got a pearl as big as his own fist. It wasn’t something he could just exchange for a few boats anywhere. Adding on the special corals that were also quite attractive, he really had earned a lot with this transaction.

This was because although the price that he traded with the Merfolk was fair, he could add a huge markup on top of those products due to their rarity in the continent.

Looking at the corals, even Laura had the feeling of taking them away. Those things were really beautiful.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura’s expression and faintly smiled, “If you like it, you can take some. We still have a lot, we won’t be losing much.”

When Laura heard Zhao Hai, she was first very happy, then she shook her head and said, “It’s alright, we need to hand these things over to Charlie. Even though we aren’t short of money, we can use them to further our relationship with him. Right, Brother Hai, what are your plans for these magic beasts? These shrimps aren’t small, they should also be quite rare in the Continent.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll get them to breed inside the Space first, then when they get to a certain number, I’ll take them out and freeze them.”

Laura nodded, “But we can’t head back immediately, or else Charlie would get suspicious. I think we might as well go and mine some stones on uninhabited islands. The last time when we planned to do it, we were interrupted with the Shrimp Tribe’s matter, so we weren’t able to continue.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “That’s also good, then let’s look for a small island and have the undead mine some stones. Let’s go and and see Little Jin as well, that kid had been too comfortable with his family nowadays.”

Even though Little Jin was still living on Ape Island, his life had been more comfortable than before. This was because he had a good relationship with Cai’er, so she kept a piece of land in the Space for the fruits that Little Jin liked. Zhao Hai didn’t oppose this decision since he was also fond of the little monkey.

Zhao Hai also didn’t want Little Jin to leave his tribe, after all a leader couldn’t just leave his group all the time. And since Ape Island now had a Transmission Point in it, they could just go visit him every time.

In the next few days, Zhao Hai found a small and uninhabited island according to the size they discussed before. The island had nothing else than some rocks and weeds, and it fortunately had the stones that Zhao Hai liked.

Zhao Hai stopped the ship at the side of the small island. Then he went to release the undead to mine the stones, and while those undead were mining, he went to Ape Island with Laura and the others.

Although the gorillas seemed very terrifying and weren’t as cute as Little Jin, they already were getting along with Zhao Hai’s group. The gorilla group had intelligence of a 5-6 year old child, they were happily playing around with Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai also wanted to find a safe place in the island to make a house in. So these past few days they were just strolling around the island.

Aside from finding a good place, they saw a cavern that had a water tunnel connecting to the cavern that the Goldmetal fruit was in. This cavern was very well hidden, even Little Jin didn’t know about it. This was because the entrance of this cavern was properly covered by a huge Bread Tree. The tree was placed on the outskirts of the island, this was why Little Jin rarely went there. The diameter of the tree was 50 meters, and half of it covered the entrance of the cavern, a 30 meter sized hole. In addition to the cavern entrance, it also had an opening towards the sea, also allowing a huge ship to come in from the outside. However, this entrance was underwater, Zhao Hai couldn’t do anything about that right now.

Although an entrance of the cavern was connected to the sea, it was actually very dry. Since the cavern was huge, it was no problem if several hundred individuals were to occupy it. This place was the best location for hiding  secret treasures.

Chapter 415: Returning to Jade Water City

Unfortunately, Zhao Hai had no great use for this cavern, he already had the Space for storing things. But for Little Jin, this cavern can be used as a storage area to preserve some Bread Fruits.

To be honest, there weren’t many things inside Ape Island. Apart from Little Jin’s tribe, the only other things were the Bread Trees. It was very strange that the only tree present on the island were Bread Trees, this made Zhao Hai very curious.

Although he was curious, there was no way for Zhao Hai to research this matter. The final conclusion that he reached was that it may be caused by the Goldmetal Tree.

Even if Zhao Hai was in Ape Island, he was also quite mindful of the stone mining operation. But Zhao Hai knew that there was no need to worry, making those undead do the mining was actually a good idea. This was because the undead can use their own bodies as their own tools, they didn’t need one at all. The situation went a lot better when Zhao Hai sent the Jie Li Shi twins to summon some stone golems. Summoning stone golems was the same as picking them and transporting them over, they were two tasks in one.

The group stayed on Ape Island for a whole month. Naturally, they didn’t stay there all the time, they also went back to Iron Mountain Fort from time to time, and on the other times, they just stayed inside the Space and trained.

Zhao Hai mainly practiced on his martial arts. And after one month of training, Zhao Hai’s present fighting capability can now rival an ordinary 7th rank Warrior.

These past few days, Zhao Hai had some good sparring partners, Little Jin’s tribe members. Those apes were very big, but they were also very flexible. Zhao Hai achieved great results when he sparred against them.

Besides martial arts, Zhao Hai also practiced his control over metal. Now he can control a metal ball the size of a soccer ball, allowing him the ability to change its form as well as make it fly all over the place. One day, Zhao Hai was able to transform the iron ball into armor and donned it on his body.

The current armor looks like a couple of ropes interlinked with each other. Because of this, he took quite a while in forming it. He wanted to make the ropes even more thin, but that would be very tiring. The more intricate the metal’s form is, the more difficult would it be for Zhao Hai to do it.

However, for Zhao Hai, he  thought that his progress was already good. He was quite satisfied with his armor right now.

One month quickly passed, now Zhao Hai and the gorillas on the island have become very familiar with each other. Zhao Hai even gave each of the gorillas their own names, making the apes like Zhao Hai even better.

For a whole month, under the endless effort of the undead, the entire island that they were on was more than levelled to the ground. The island now has a mountain sized depression making the middle of it hollow. The hole went below the sea level, only the area surrounding the island was abstained from being mined since if they get the stones there as well, the whole island would get flooded.

Although they were only mining for one month, the amount of stones that they got was a lot. Even if the stones weren’t enough to expand Iron Mountain Fort, it could still be able to build enough stone houses to accommodate 10,000 people.

Zhao Hai knew that it was time to set sail, so he retrieved all the undead back into the Space and then boarded the Haven to head back to Jade Water City.

These past few days, Zhao Hai hadn’t received any letter from Smith. He didn’t know what the Calci Family thought when he snatched 20 of their ships. Will they want to deal with him even more, or will they talk peace with him?

To be honest, Zhao Hai really wanted to be partners with the Calci Family. No matter what, the two of them had the same enemy. Even if Juwan disappointed him, he just let him go every time. He hopes that the Calci Family would put him in an equal position and just cooperate with him.

Another thing that worried Zhao Hai constantly was Southern King Boris. The attack on Ruyen’s ship was sent by him, this shows that he’s starting to take action against the Calci Family. Although Zhao Hai already warned Evan about this, he still couldn’t help but worry.

No matter what, Evan had been very helpful to him and was also a friend to the Buda Clan. Now that Zhao Hai had implicated him, he hoped that the Purcell Family could stay safe.

While the ship was sailing on the sea, Zhao Hai held on his hand two iron balls, playing with them as though they were baoding balls. This was a habit he had developed recently, additionally, it could also help him exercise his ability to control metal.

The Haven was quite calm as they spent the next few days sailing. He retrieved all of the boats he released before, he didn’t want Charlie to find out his total amount of ships. Zhao Hai currently believed that there was no other person that knew how many ships he actually had in hand.

Seeing that they were getting closer and closer to Jade Water City, Zhao Hai increasingly grew excited. No wonder Humans are social animals, it was much less stressful when having in contact with other Humans.

The ship slowly docked on Charlie’s private pier. The people in the pier already knew the Haven as well as Zhao Hai’s status.

The people at the pier knew that when Zhao Hai had set sail before, Charlie was there to bade him farewell himself. This gesture showed Zhao Hai’s exceptional identity. This made the personnel extremely careful when receiving him. In the end, this was Charlie’s special pier, all of those who were allowed to dock their ships here should be Charlie’s trusted people, nobody dared offend them.

Zhao Hai and the others got down from the Haven and sat on their carriage as they headed off to their shop in Jade Water City. From the pier, the shop was just a short distance away, so Zhao Hai chose to visit that place first.

While he was still quite a distance away from the shop, Zhao Hai noticed that there was a notable amount of traffic present. This made Zhao Hai stare blankly, he didn’t expect to see such a scene.

To him, the shop was mainly meant to be a contact point, its business quality didn’t matter. But now, it looks like the business here was doing very good.

Zhao Hai went around the crowd and arrived at a small entrance behind the shop. The entrance was meant for special people, average citizens wouldn’t be able to enter through here. Naturally, there were no people seen here.

The group went inside the courtyard and saw the busy atmosphere inside it. They could see a lot of people with slave marks on their heads moving things around the courtyard. This made Zhao Hai somewhat confused.

However, Zhao Hai quickly came to understand that these people must have been bought by Mu’en. He obviously needed a lot of helping hands here, so it was natural for him to buy some slaves. It seems like Mu’en’s methods are really good.

At this time, the slaves also took note of Zhao Hai. They were surprised since they knew that the courtyard had three gates, the front gate, the side gate used for unloading cargo, and a special gate at the back. That gate was guarded by Zhao Hai’s undead, only Mu’en’s family were able to pass through there and nobody else. Now that they saw a group inside the courtyard that didn’t enter from the front nor the side gate, the slaves reckoned that they must have passed through the back gate. And seeing that the group wasn’t coming to cause trouble, did these people know the Manager?”

At this time, Shun had already called Mu’en to the courtyard. When they arrived, Zhao Hai immediately sent Shun to fetch the shop’s Manager. When Mu’en saw Zhao Hai and Laura, he immediately gave a bow and said, “Young Lady, Young Master, you came back.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Mu’en, go arrange some people to unload some marine products from the Haven. Remember that the products are frozen into huge chunks, make sure to handle them carefully while avoiding injury to your people.”

Mu’en nodded and said, “Young Master, Prince Charlie isn’t currently in Jade Water City, it seems like he returned to the capital. Will you still be heading to the City Lord’s Mansion?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment then said, “I’ll have to go, these marine products that I’ve brought needed to be delivered to Charlie to be processed. But go and prepare some rooms for us here, we will come back to rest in the evening. We wouldn’t be staying at the City Lord’s Mansion.” Mu’en nodded, then Zhao Hai added a few more instructions before they headed to the mansion.

Just as they were halfway there, they were met by a group of city guards. When the group saw Zhao Hai’s unique bull-pulled carriage, they immediately stopped as their leader dismounted from his horse. He went forward to Zhao Hai’s carriage and said, “Is this mister Zhao Hai’s carriage?”

Zhao Hai opened his door and walked out. He looked at the person and said, “I am Zhao Hai, and you are?”

The person quickly replied, “Sir, I am the Guard Commander of the City’s garrison legion. Today I came to offer the City Lord’s invitation as well as to escort mister to the mansion. The City Lord has prepared a welcoming banquet for your group.”

Zhao Hai nodded then said, “Alright, lead the way.” The commander nodded, then jumped on his horse. The group then escorted Zhao Hai’s carriage as it headed to the City Lord’s Mansion.

At this time, the people on the streets also took note of Zhao Hai. Among them, there were those who knew about the person on the carriage. This was because of the uniqueness of Zhao Hai’s bull-pulled carriage. They knew that this person cannot be offended since even the Prince was very polite to him. The people immediately gave way and avoided the carriage.

They quickly arrived at the City Lord’s Mansion. Zhao Hai saw Trezebo surprisingly stood at the front gate to personally welcome him. When the carriage stopped, Trezebo went forward an laughed, “Mister Zhao Hai’s actions are really very quick. I didn’t even have the time to get notified, otherwise I would’ve had come and meet you at the pier.”

After he got down from the carriage, Zhao Hai smiled, “I wouldn’t dare tire the City Lord. City Lord is too polite, how could I just let you personally meet me, I think I don’t really deserve it.”

Trezebo laughed, “Mister is the one being too polite, how could I get exhausted. Right, I’m inviting mister for a meal. I’ve prepared some good food and wine to welcome mister and his group back to the city.” He said as he pulled Zhao Hai towards the interior af the mansion.

Chapter 416: Strength

When the group entered the City Lord’s Mansion, Trezebo turned to the housekeeper and said, “Go deliver mister’s stuff to Purple Bamboo Courtyard.”

Hearing this, Zhao Hai immediately said, “City Lord doesn’t need to be too polite. I now have a shop inside the city, there’s no need for me to live in Purple Bamboo Courtyard anymore. Also, that place is the Third Prince’s personal space, it wouldn’t be good if I stay there for long.”

Trezebo laughed and said, “Mister doesn’t need to worry. His highness wouldn’t be there for the majority of the year. Moreover, his highness already gave us order to allow you to keep staying in the courtyard. Mister can rest assured.”

Hearing this, Zhao Hai had no choice but to continue staying at Purple Bamboo courtyard. He had the others go to the courtyard to settle down first, then had Shun go inform Mu’en that it would be impossible for them to stay at the shop.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the dining hall, he saw that there were only seats enough for two people inside. This made Zhao Hai stared ot Trezebo puzzlingly, Trezebo smiled and said, “Let my wife accompany Laura and the others. Today let’s just eat with only the two of us  so that we can discuss matters.”

Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t say anything more. After the two sat down, the housekeeper immediately took action and served them liquor as well as had some people set up the dishes.

While they were sat down, Trezebo lifted his wine glass and said, “This glass is for mister. For enduring the tiresome sea travel, wading through salty sea breezes and sunburns.”

Zhao Hai also lifted his wine glass and said, “City Lord is very polite, actually I haven’t done anything, it was the captain who had all the troubles.” Then they bumped glasses and downed the liquor in one go.

After drinking the wine, Trezebo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Looking at mister’s appearance, I reckon your harvests aren’t small? What good things did you acquire this time?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The most precious ones are this.” He waved his hand as giant corals appeared on the room, the clam shell appeared on the table as well.

Zhao Hai opened the shell gently and revealed the giant pearl. Trezebo stared blankly at the treasure, even if he had seen a lot of good things, he hadn’t seen a pearl as large as this before.

This was because pearls and corals on the Ark Continent are very precious, not only because they are attractive, but also because they were Magical materials, very valuable Magical materials.

Naturally these pearls and corals were also loved by women. Presently, there were only a few people who would use these as Magical ingredients, most were used by Nobles to decorate their houses.

Seeing this magnificent display, Trezebo took deep breaths so calm down his mood as he turned his head to Zhao Hai, “I didn’t expect mister to have such a huge harvest, I really didn’t expect.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “These are the most valuable, I also have aquatic Magic Beasts, most of which were shrimps. I already froze them and is currently being transported to my shop’s warehouse. And last I also have some edible seaweeds and the like, not really worth a lot of money.”

Trezebo gave a nod and said, “That’s fine, the continent’s supply of those gets fewer and fewer every year due to the ruthless overharvesting of those Mages. They almost wiped out the entire coastline region of marine resources. Even if we are a port city, it has become more and more difficult for us to eat seafood. Your products should get very popular.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Good, as long as these things get sold. I was actually afraid that nobody would buy them. Right, you can take those in two days, after all, I already promised His Highness that I’ll only be acquiring those products. He can then decide how he wants to sell those.”

Trezebo laughed, “Rest assured, His Highness had already prepared, he’s now just waiting for you. Right, when will the fire fishes arrive? Everything on my side is fine, you can start sending them.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Be relieved, they should arrive in two days, you could get them then. Right, what happened to His Highness? Why did he return to Carson City? Did an accident happen?”

Trezebo smiled faintly, “Not really an accident, it was just that His Highness cannot leave Carson City for a long time. Carson City is the capital of the Rosen Empire, almost all of the big powers are centralized there. If His Highness left for a longtime, some people might start to loosen the ropes of his influence.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then gave a sigh, “His Highness really had rough. Right, did His Highness have any other tasks that he’s left to you?”

Trezebo smiled and said, “Rest assured, under normal circumstances, we who are on his side generally had nothing to do. We just continue doing our own thing.”

Zhao Hao nodded, “When the things get shipped in two days, have some people come and receive it. I think that His Highness should be needing a lot of money lately, we must make sure that His Highness gets the money he needs.”

Trezebo sighed, then with a serious voice, he said, “This is the only thing we can do right now. After all, the current Emperor’s body is still quite healthy. His Highness cannot overly try to win people over, therefore, we can only build our strengths at the moment.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “You go tell His Highness that if there is anything I need to do, don’t be polite to me, just go approach me directly. If he wants to make money, I can only provide these few products I have on hand. However, if there are other matters, tell him that I’ll do my best to deal with them.”

Trezebo smiled faintly and said, “Mister can rest assured, if there really is something, His Highness would surely be impolite. Right, will mister stay for long this time? It’s going to be God’s Grace Day, the whole continent will be celebrating.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Yes, it’s the day where the continent celebrates the greatest, but isn’t this the best time to do business? I’m going to return to the deeps seas in two days and get some more marine products. I believe that it’s the season best suited for selling those items.”

Trezebo gave a stiff smiled and said, “Mister is really a Merchant, still thinking about business when it’s God’s Grace Day. Hai, it would be impossible for people like you to not get rich.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, “I have no choice, I have my Clan to support. If I don’t think of more ways to get money, we wouldn’t have any income.”

Trezebo’s eyes showed a small glint in them as he looked at Zhao Hai, but he didn’t say anything about it and just smiled and said, “Who doesn’t?”

Zhao Hai just smiled and didn’t talk anymore, he just continued to drink wine. Since Zhao Hai didn’t want to talk anymore, Trezebo didn’t ask. He just talked about drinking more wine and tasting more dishes. He also talked to Zhao Hai about the other people on Charlie’s side.

Zhao Hai was mindful to everything that Trezebo said, he was now on Charlie’s side, naturally he would want to know all about Charlie’s group.

The rest of the meal was spent with casual conversation. After eating, Zhao Hai returned to Purple Bamboo Courtyard. Laura and the others were already there. When they saw Zhao Hai return, they immediately welcomed them. Laura then asked, “Brother Hai, what did you talk about with Trezebo?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Nothing really, we just casually conversed. Laura, God’s Grace Day is approaching, I’m afraid we won’t be staying still, I plan on returning to the sea in two days.”

Laura replied, “God’s Grace day is less than a month away. We should travel and maybe return to Iron Mountain Fort. What plans do you have when we go to the sea this time?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Naturally to trade with the Rock Shrimp Tribe again. In God’s Grace Day, people would be splurging their money everywhere. All Great Nobles would want to eat delicious dishes during that time. When we go back and trade with the Shrimp Tribe, we should get a lot of seafood ingredients, those things are surely very in demand nowadays.”

Laura thought for a moment and said, “That’s good, we will surely have big profits. We should get Trezebo to prepare good stuff for us in return.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, we should also get good things since we still need to return back to Iron Mountain Fort. Maybe I’ll also send a letter via Blood Hawk to Brother Wales along with some gifts.”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai, you seem to have forgotten. The Beastmen don’t celebrate God’s Grace Day. They’ll be attending the Ten Thousand Beasts Festival. Hehe.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly and patted his head, “Right, I forgot about that. Brother Wales is a Beastman, he doesn’t celebrate God’s Grace Day. Hahaha. Also, it’s something interesting to think about, when God’s Day passes, it should be about one year since we met.”

Currently, it was late winter. When Zhao Hao woke up last time, it was early spring. As long as God’s Grace Day passes, spring will arrive soon after. Time really passes by quickly.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Time really does come by fast, we actually know each other for nearly a year.” She and Zhao Hai had also met during spring season, since it was now winter, they will soon be knowing each other for one year.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “After this period of time, if we are not busy, we should ask Grandpa Green to prepare our matter, what do the two of you think?”

Meg and Laura’s face immediately turned red, they knew exactly what matter Zhao Hai was talking about, it was their wedding. The two of them were too embarrassed to answer, but they didn’t disagree.

Seeing the duo’s appearance, he couldn’t help but smile, “Don’t be embarrassed, I only held off our wedding up to this time because of some matters. First, it was because I was still under the effects of the Water of Nothingness. Second, I don’t want the two of you to marry me in secret. I must let the entire continent know about the women that I’m going to marry. I must let the continent know that the Buda Clan was once again standing on its feet, that the two of you are women of the Buda Clan. I will make all the people in the continent stop looking down on you.”

Laura and Meg looked at Zhao Hai with a gentle look. Laura spoe softly, “Brother Hai, we don’t really mind, as long as our Buda Clan is strong, it didn’t matter if nobody knows of our wedding.”

Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Marriage is a huge milestone of our lives, we cannot be careless about it. Alright, we’ll hold this matter until we discuss it with Grandpa Green and others. We should find a suitable time to reveal our Buda Clan’s might.”

At this point, Laura frowned and said, “Brother Hai, is this really a good idea? If we expose our identity, then wouldn’t trouble arrive at Iron Mountain Fort? If we show the secrets of the Fort, I think that it would be unfavorable for us.”

Zhao Hai replied with a serious voice, “I know that. But now that the poison fog on the Black Wastelands aren’t any less than those in the Carrion Swamp, even 9th ranks would think twice before entering. With the poison present being strengthened by the Space, ordinary 8th ranks have to chance of entering the area. If 8th ranks enter, they would be weakened, by that point they would become fodder before us. With the undead, Cai’er and the Blood Hawks, let’s see who would dare come and enter our territory.”

Laura thought for a moment, it was true. They have underestimated their current capabilities. At present, the Buda Clan is not weak. Now that the Black Wastelands have become pretty much like the Carrion Swamp, they could easily deal with those who dared enter it.

Meg, at this moment, chuckled and said, “Elder Brother Hai, you forgot to include the Blood Devouring Mosquitos. In the Space, we have large quantities of those mosquitos, there was no number that could describe it. Let’s see which expert can withstand a barrage of attacks coming from those. Also, if they really dared to wage a war with us, we can just repeat what we did back in Purcell Duchy. Just release pests in their territory, let’s see how well they’ll fare then.”

Hearing what Meg said, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. “I must say, Meg, you have quite some sinister ideas. Hahaha. But your idea is good. Before, I couldn’t just act recklessly because of my body, but now that I’ve been cured, we’ll see who will dare face us. Let’s just hope that the people in Aksu Empire wouldn’t dare mess with me. .”

Laura also smiled at Meg’s idea. At this point, Laura thought that their strength was already formidable, there was no enemy that they couldn’t deal with.

In all honesty, Zhao Hai had always neglected to take note of the strength of his undead creatures. One should know that Zhao Hai currently had a total of 700,000 undead on his hands. And these 700 thousand undead all have strength equal to 8th rank. If those 700 thousand undead were to be released by Zhao Hai in one go, then it wouldn’t be a problem even if they raze the entire Aksu Empire to the ground.

Although Zhao Hai also knew this, he just placed the idea on the back of his mind. This was because he knew that he couldn’t just release massive amounts of undead to wage war with other Humans, this was a one-way ticket to being public enemy number one and Zhao Hai didn’t want that to happen. He wasn’t a lunatic who wanted to take control of the whole world. He was just an average person who didn’t have any grudges on the entire Human race, he didn’t want to be embroiled in war all the time.

However, the heavens seem to think otherwise. It seems to dislike Zhao Hai being out of the limelight. When Zhao Hai and the others were chatting, a sound from a Blood Hawk was heard as it headed straight to Purple Bamboo Courtyard.

Chapter 417: Smith’s Worries

Drawing back time a couple of days ago, Smith sat inside his study with a blank look. Phil was at the side looking at him with a pained expression. Phil understood Smith’s current mood. This was because, just now, Smith received a letter from the family stating that they will still deal with Zhao Hai, and this time they would be bringing along some 9th rank experts.

Smith couldn’t fathom how wise and smart people like the elders of the family became dumb as a rock when it came to Zhao Hai’s matter. Smith felt like he was appealing to some cows.

And because of Smith’s constant messages, the Family was now quite dissatisfied with him. This brough Smith a huge headache. He knew that Zhao Hai was not alone anymore, he now has Charlie at his back. Moreover, the Prince came to think highly of his new friend. If the Family happened to kill Zhao Hai, they would form an enormous entity with Charlie. If the scenario where Charlie becomes the Emperor in the future comes true, then the family wouldn’t have any good days going forward.

He also knew that the Family didn’t care about Charlie since he was only the Third Prince, not the Crown Prince. Although Charlie has the right of inheriting the throne, he was always acting very low-key, this made the family’s disregard the Third Prince.

However, Smith knew that Charlie wasn’t that incompetent, otherwise why would the current emperor hand him Jade Water City.

Although the Imperial Clan had a huge influence, its truly high income cities only numbered three, Jade Water City, Rising Water City, and the Empire’s capital, Carson City.

Carson City, the Imperial Capital, was currently the residence of the Crown Prince. He was currently helping the Emperor manage the Empire, it can be said that Carson City is under the Crown Prince’s rule.

However, Carson City was a city full of dragons and tigers. In addition to the Crown Prince’s influence, the other prince’s center of power were also present in the city. There were even forces in the city that exceeded his influence. Even the Calci Family’s branch on Carson City wasn’t that less than the Crown Prince’s faction. With the addition to his Imperial Uncles, it was very difficult for the Crown Prince to fully control the city. Therefore, Smith wasn’t optimistic about the Crown Prince.

The Second Prince controls Rising Water City. It was a good place, geographically similar to Sky Water City. However, Smith was also not optimistic about the Second Prince. This was because this Prince was very shortsighted. He manages Rising Water City like how an abusive farmer overly milks his cows. Because of this, a lot of Merchants were forced to leave the city. If not because of its good location, Smith was afraid that Rising Water City would already be bankrupt.

The Third Prince Charlie manages Jade Water City. Even after being the Third Prince, the major forces of the empire didn’t seem to take note of him. This in itself made people feel very strange. The third successor of the continent’s most powerful nation was someone nobody paid any attention to, this matter was too mysterious.

This can only show that the prince had been acting very low-key recently that nobody paid him any attention. But Smith knew that someone was more terrifying when he was invisible. If you don’t take note of him, you wouldn’t be able to know the cards on his hand. This was a talent that made someone extremely frightening.

And this time, Zhao Hai chose to leave Rising Water City in order to transfer to Jade Water City, offending the Second Prince along the way, preferring a man no one paid any attention to. This in itself showed Zhao Hai’s nature, so why didn’t the family consider this?

Can the people in the family really not see the bigger picture? They might have forgotten about that aspect since they were too focused on dealing with Zhao Hai. Not only would they offend the Third Prince, they would also be harming the Calci Family’s prestige.

Zhao Hai’s status was very well-known in the continent. People knew that he is a Dark Mage. And when people heard that he went to Sky Water City, they should have faintly guessed that he ran away from the Radiant Church and Southern King Boris and reckoned that he might have hired himself to the Calci Family.

Even if the various forces in the continent were unaware of the existence of the League of Dark Mages, they should still be knowledgeable of the fact that the Calci Family was held the pinnacle influence regarding the Dark Mages in the continent. Because of this reputation, numerous Dark Mages would join the League of Dark Mages. This was because they could not only receive assistance, the organization was also quite loose.

In this case, the family’s action against Zhao Hai was improper. What would the other Dark Mages think when they hear of this? Will they still join the league? Can they still work hard for the league? Later on, Dark Mages would think twice about joining up with the Calci Family. They would fear that they might be treated like Zhao Hai, wherein the treasures they had on hand were seized by the family.

In the eyes of outsiders, this was the case. Zhao Hai had fire fishes on hand that the Calci Family fancied, so they wanted him to hand it over. But Zhao Hai refused, which caused this whole event.

Outsiders weren’t privy to the inside affairs of the family. In their minds, Juwan was just a member of the family, he didn’t have that much influence, so it was impossible for them to think that he was the root cause of the situation.

Smith was currently worried about this matter. He feared that the Calci Family’s image on other Dark Mages were now quite smudged. If this matters gets larger, then the League of Dark Mages might even disband.

What Smith didn’t understand was his brother Peter who had the most understanding with regards to the league. Why didn’t he prevent this? Not only did he not prevent it, he also disregarded Smith’s warnings. This made Smith very confused.

Phil, who was Smith’s housekeeper, naturally understood. But he didn’t have any other choice right now, Smith was only the 2nd successor to the Family. Above him were the Elders and the Patriarch, while at his surroundings were the other successors. The moves that Smith could do were quite limited.

Phil also thought that the family wouldn’t go too far in dealing with Zhao Hai. After all, this matter seems like the Family was stealing openly. Moreover, they were going against their own Mage. He didn’t think that this matter would reach this point.

Currently, Zhao Hai had already snatched more than 30 ships from the family. And although he didn’t kill 8th rank experts, he wasted their cultivation.

In all honesty, Phil was very angry when he heard about this, he didn’t expect that Zhao hai would be so ruthless, actually crippling those 8th ranks. But he also knew that Zhao Hai still kept the family’s face into consideration, otherwise Juwan would already be dead.

The one that Phil didn’t expect the most was the family sending a 9th rank to cope with Zhao Hai. This wasn’t a clever decision for the family.

Can a 9th rank really be mobilized that easily? But for of an uncooperative Dark Mage, the family actually planned to send a 9th rank, the resources they would use would be very huge. More importantly, they were going to send the 9th rank to deal with Zhao Hai, what would the members of the league think of this? Would they still support the family in the future?

Phil thought that the situation had become very troublesome. At this point, Smith suddenly talked to Phil, “Uncle Phil, what do you think is going on in the minds of the family? Why do they really want to deal with Zhao Hai? I think this decision shouldn’t be just because of Juwan.”

Phil nodded and said, “Mobilizing a 9th rank is a very huge matter, it wasn’t something the Fifth Young Master can decide on. The decision should have been made by either the Patriarch or the Elder’s Assembly, but as to why, I have absolutely no idea. Is it because they think that he might have become overconfident because of the previous matter that he dared to slap the family’s face? Or are there some ideas on the mind of the Patriarch?”

After listening to Phil, Smith’s eyes lit up, “Uncle Phil, are you implying that the family is scared of Zhao Hai?”

Phil looked confused at what Smith just said, “Scared? What do they need to fear about Zhao Hai? Even if he is quite talented, it was impossible for him to defeat a 9th rank expert. Why would the family be afraid of him?”

Smith let out a long sigh and said, “I think the Family didn’t fear Zhao Hai’s strength, but instead his ideas. In the past, didn’t the plan to suppress the Radiant Church came from Zhao Hai? They feared that through Zhao Hai’s understanding of the Radiant Church, he could influence other Dark Mages and slowly wrestle control of the League away from the Family. Therefore, they took this chance to eliminate Zhao Hai. Moreover then think that Dark Mages only think of themselves, they wouldn’t care about Zhao Hai. This made the Family decide on this action, since they didn’t fear Dark Mages would leave the league and form their own alliances on their own.”

Phil stared and muttered, “Is it really this? Even if those Dark Mages didn’t leave the league, they would still be afraid to share their information to the league. This would be a huge blow to the organization.”

Smith coldly said, “I’m afraid that it isn’t that simple. Zhao Hai’s idea made it possible to have more Dark Mages emerging from the empire, further increasing the family’s influence. In the future, it was highly probable that those young Dark Mages would hire themselves to the family. At this point, the family wasn’t worried about the Dark Mage’s inheritance anymore. For them, the leagues was no longer important, so they decided that it was fine to deal with Zhao Hai.”

Phil stared blankly at Smith, “Really? Can the family actually do that?” Although he was asking a question, he already agreed with Smith’s words. This may actually be the reason why the family didn’t hesitate in dealing with Zhao Hai.

Phil had served the family for his entire lifetime, so he already understood the mindset of the family. Although the Calci Family was very low-key recently, deep inside, they didn’t change their bearing as Great Nobles. They were still greedy, greedy for wealth and greedy for power.

A few years ago, because of the Radiant Church’s suppression of the Calci Family, they felt the need to establish the League of Dark Mages. Upon establishing the league, they treated all of the Dark Mages in it quite nicely. But in truth, the Calci Family were still looking down on those Dark Mages. There were even small Dark Mage clans that weren’t destroyed under the Radiant Church’s hands, but instead in the Calci Family’s. This was to ensure that the family stayed quite high up on the minds of the Dark Mages.

Chapter 418: The Devil Resurfaces

Now because of Zhao Hai’s plan, the family didn’t need to fear Radiant Church’s suppression anymore. Therefore, they shifted their focus towards the Dark Mages and proceeding to deal with those who pose a threat to the family. And Zhao Hai was without a doubt such a person.

From the family’s point of view, Zhao Hai’s strength was only 7-8th ranks, he wasn’t a threat regarding that area. However, the idea that Zhao Hai provided the family was too effective that the family came to fear him. For Zhao Hai to give that kind of idea meant that Zhao Hai’s capabilities are quite high. If given the opportunity, perhaps he can establish his own Great Clan, when that time comes, the Calci Family would have a hard time in getting the hearts of all Dark Mages.

Moreover, in their opinion, Zhao Hai’s body had all the conditions required to build a family. He is young and his strength isn’t that bad. He has a lot of good to not worry about money. He is smart as well, all of these combined together was enough for the Calci Family to make a move against him.

Phil didn’t agree with the family’s methods. It was because the family had caused huge damage to all the Dark Mages and ensured that they didn’t increase in power. With only the family facing against the Radiant Church, the profession was in fear of getting exterminated. Now that the family is doing better, they got back to their previous actions again, this was really a short-sighted behavior.

Smith didn’t replied to Phil’s words, but with a serious voice he added, “The Family’s brains is starting to rot again. Do they really really want to aid the Radiant Church? No, we cannot just allow it.”

At this time, Phil recovered from his thoughts, he looked at Smith and sighed, “Master, I’m afraid that wouldn’t’ be easy, how would we protect Zhao Hai? The family will send a 9th rank this time, don’t consider Zhao Hai, even the Third Prince Charlie couldn’t just casually mobilize a 9th rank.”

While Smith may have a calm face, his mind’s thoughts were continually spinning. He was trying to figure out ways in order to save Zhao Hai. In his opinion, Zhao Hao was a very talented man, one full of potential. He is a good blessing to all Dark Mages. Moreover, Smith wanted to preserve the mission of the League of Dark Mages, to be there for Dark Mages but not controlling them. They need to make the league keep its loose management.

It was precisely because that if the Family were to become strict in its management of the Dark Mages, they might kill those who were disobedient. When that time comes, Dark Mages would still respect the family, but not because of reverence, but because of fear. So when the league of Dark Mages became established, the family just supported it at the side and didn’t step in to rule it directly. The family knew that Dark Mages were mostly uncooperative.

The current practice of the family was very wrong. If their actions cause the Dark Mages to hold back on their contribution, this wouldn’t be very good for the overall situation of all Dark Mages. It would only make it easier for the Radiant Church to deal with the Calci Family, as well as slowly exterminating the Dark Mages in this world.

The advice that Zhao Hai offered, making Dark Mages proliferate in the Rosen Empire, requires time. For a child to study, become talented and assume a responsible position, it would take at least 20 years. Who knows what happens in 20 years? If the Rosen Empire feels like the Dark Mages were increasing their strengths rapidly, then they would start suppressing them. Adding that on top of the threat of the Radiant Church, the trouble to Calci Family would be huge.

Therefore, the League of Dark Mages cannot be disbanded. Zhao Hai cannot die, he must live, otherwise the will of the Dark Mages will wither away. Then the League of Dark Mages would only exist in name.

However, protecting Zhao Hai wasn’t easy, the family was determined to deal with Zhao Hai this time. And from what Smith understood from Zhao Hai’s disposition, he wouldn’t make any compromise, this would further the matter into a bad outcome.

But at this time, the devil suddenly resurfaced inside Smith’s head. It started to occupy his mind, moreover, its control got bigger and bigger.

This devil was of course the idea that has been brewing inside Smith’s mind these past several days, the idea of marrying Megan off to Zhao Hai. This idea existed inside the thoughts of Smith for a long time, but he didn’t have the courage to go through with it.

Wanting to protect Zhao Hai wasn’t easy, but if Zhao Hai weds Megan, then he would become a person from the Calci Family. This way, the family wouldn’t be able to act against him. Upon taking a further look, this really was the best way to avoid Zhao Hai’s conflict.

The thought was getting more and more intense, to the point where Smith couldn’t resist it anymore. Seeing Smith’s change in complexion, as though he had been convinced of a solution, Phil asked, “Did the City Lord find a way?”

Smith turned to Phil and nodded, “I have one, but it needs the agreement of a person to work. If she wouldn’t agree, then it will be useless.”

Phil was confused while he stared at Smith, “Who is it? Is it the eldest Young Master? But didn’t the eldest Young master agree to the family’s action?”

Smith shook his head and said, “It’s not Big Brother, it is Megan.”

When Phil heard Smith’s words, he immediately understood the idea. His expression couldn’t help but change. Since he was with Smith for a long time, he also watched Megan grow up, for Phil, the Calci Family’s Plum Blossom Princess was like his own granddaughter. When he heard Smith, he didn’t like it at first.

However, he was also a person that could see the bigger picture. Seeing him ruminate on his words, Smith looked at Phil, he knew how Phil felt for Megan, so he added, “Megan told me a few days ago that she didn’t just want to eat sleep and wait to die. She wanted to do something for the family and wouldn’t want to marry another noble who only knew how to eat and play. But if we marry her over to those legitimate successors of other Noble families, I’m afraid that she would get bullied. We protected her too much for all her life that now she is bored with her life. Uncle has also met Zhao Hai, that young man is very good, although he already has two fiancees, you can clearly see that their attitudes towards each other are very good, this is great news for Megan. And most importantly, Zhao Hai is also very strong. Even if his strength get bigger than us in the future, we have Megan on his side to monitor him. What do you think?”

Phil was still as he listened to Smith’s words, from what Phil heard, Smith shouldn’t have just thought this matter for one or two days. It seems like he already thought this out completely.

Phil’s impression of Zhao Hai is also very good. He was low-key, down to earth, and one who knows what the right thing to do. Although his origins are mysterious, it was undeniable that his future was limitless. If Megan were to marry Zhao Hai, that would be great as well.

However, Phil still said, “What we think is unimportant, only Megan’s opinion on this matter can be put into considerations. If Megan disagrees, then I will not make Zhao Hai marry her.”

As soon as Smith heard Phil, he knew that his housekeeper had already agreed. But as Phil said, everything hinges on Megan. If she agrees, then everything else would be very easy to handle. If she doesn’t then they wouldn’t force her. Smith was, after all, still protective of his daughter.

Smith nodded and said, “Uncle Phil can be relieved, if Megan disagrees, then we would find another solution. But I think that we should find another person to ask her, I’m afraid she wouldn’t be able to disagree if either you or me asks, that girl’s skin is too thin.”

Phil smiled faintly and said, “Oh, time indeed passes quite fast. In a blink of an eye, Megan reached marriageable age. Hehe, City Lord, I think you should discuss this with the madam, she would be the best person to ask this matter.”

Smith nodded, “Right, then I shall immediately go talk with the madam. I must make this clear to her first, otherwise she wouldn’t just agree.” Then he rushed off, Phil shook his head and followed right behind.

Smith’s wife was also quite influential, because of the family’s rule of not marrying off their daughters for benefit, naturally wives of the family were also held at high status.

However, even if Smith’s wife held some power, she had always been supporting Smith ever since the two of them married. She never intervened in family affairs. When she’s at home, she just raised some flowers and plants. And since she was also a Potion master, she spends majority of her time researching potion making. This made her quite distant to the matters of the family.

But because of this, Smith held a lot of affection towards his wife. Their feelings for each other never changed after dozens of years being together. Smith also didn’t have any other lover, the affection the two held for each other was the envy of everyone around them.

When Smith went to the courtyard where he lived, he didn’t find his wife. Soon, he went to his wife’s medical garden. This was where she researches medicine as well as prepare her husband’s medicines. Common people weren’t allowed here, even servants, this was the madam’s personal order.

Upon reaching the medical garden, Smith spotted his wife watering some herbs. The madam was wearing cotton garments, she held a canteen on one hand and was carefully dripping water on the plants. She looks very earnest and charming, Smith just stood there for a while.

Before long, the water inside the canteen was used up. When she looked up and saw Smith just standing there, she couldn’t help but smile, she stared at her husband and said, “Dear, what are you doing here? Is there something you need from me?”

Smith recovered as he quickly nodded, “I do, I have an important matter to discuss with you. Let’s return to the courtyard first.”

Seeing her husband seem so serious, the madam nodded gently. Then she placed her canteen down and walked with Smith towards their courtyard.

Chapter 419: Megan’s Thoughts

After they arrived at the courtyard, they sat down as a servant went and served them some tea. After that, Smith waved his hand to make the servants leave the room for the two of them.

Seeing the situation, the madam couldn’t help but stare, she turned her head to Smith and said, “What’s the matter my dear City Lord? Why are acting so mysterious?”

With a calm face, Smith looked at the madam and said, “This matters implications are going to be big. Today, I received a letter from the family that said about their plans of sending a 9th rank expert to deal with Zhao Hai.”

The madam stared at her husband,, then she knit her brows. Even if she didn’t care much about the matters of the family, she took not of Zhao Hai since she has a good impression of the young man. In her opinion, Zhao Hai was an honest and reliable man with great strength. Such a young man was very difficult to find nowadays.

In the past, she didn’t care too much about the family’s plans of dealing with Zhao Hai. For her, it should have been just been Juwan doing his thing. She believed that Smith would have this under control. However, she didn’t realize that the family would go and send a 9th rank expert to Zhao Hai. With a 9th rank dispatched, the matter turned more complicated. How could the situation reach this point?

Seeing the madan not talking, Smith said, “I want to save Zhao Hai, if the family were to kill him, no Dark Mage would trust the family ever again. This loss would be too much for the family.”

The madam frowned, “But didn’t you say that the family will send a 9th rank expert? If this decision came from the Patriarch and the Elder’s Assembly, then how can we guarantee Zhao Hai’s safety?”

Smith looked at his wife and said, “Dear, Megan’s age isn’t that young. I think it’s time for her to get married. I want you to ask her how she feels about Zhao Hai.”

Upon hearing her husband, the madam’s expression changed. But she wasn’t a normal woman and didn’t immediately oppose, she thought about it more carefully.

Seeing his wife like this, Smith was glad, he looked at her and added, “You know what kind of man Zhao Hai is. You have also seen Laura and Meg. I think if Megan were to marry Zhao Hai, then she wouldn’t suffer in the future. This way, Megan would have a safe home to return to. At the same time, we would be able to save Zhao Hai. However, this matter fully depends on Megan, if she doesn’t agree, then I will think of another solution. I’m here to ask ask you opinion, what do you think?”

The madam thought for a moment and then nodded, “That young man Zhao Hai is good. But my condition is that if Megan were to marry him, he should reveal to us his own family background. Otherwise, I will oppose to their marriage.”

Smith nodded, Zhao Hai’s background is very mysterious. Nobody in the continent knew, this was one of the misgivings inside Smith’s heart.

Now that the madam agreed, Smith can now proceed to the next step, he turned to his wife and said, “Since you agreed, then the next matter is easy. I want you to help me ask Megan what he thinks about this. After all, this is not something that a father could just ask his daughter. Don’t ask directly, ask her what she thinks of ZHao Hai first. After all, the time that they came in contact wasn’t that long. Inquire her slowly, but remember that I will need to send Zhao Hai a letter in the next days, making him come back to Sky Water City immediately. If Megan disagrees, at the very least we should inform him that the family is planning to send a 9th rank to deal with him.”

The madam nodded, “Alright, leave it to me. Dear, do you really like Zhao Hai? The plan was decided by the family, if you really go on with your plan with Zhao Hai, then you would be offending almost everyone.”

Smith sighed, “I cannot please everybody. But if the family succeeds with this operation, then its fate would be beyond redemption.” Then Smith told his wife about the speculations that him and Phil came up earlier. The madam frowned, even if she didn’t care about these matters, it didn’t mean that she couldn’t understand it. She lived inside the family for along time, so she was still clear about its inner workings. She agreed with Smith’s speculation.

After Smith talked, the madam sighed and said, “The family had been suppressed by the Radiant Church for so long. Now that they experienced a single win, they already thought that the world belongs to them. Right, Zhao Hai is a good young man, but he’s currently together with the Third Prince. This matter is too risky, did you already think about that?”

Smith smiled faintly and said, “I didn’t really think much about it, but that situation was in the end caused by the family. Zhao Hai isn’t a fool, he’s smart. Seeing that he had some accidents here, he naturally would give himself an escape route. But that doesn’t matter, even if our Great Family didn’t join struggles for the throne, Zhao Hai didn’t belong to our family. Even if he marries Megan, he wouldn’t bear our family name, so it should be fine for us. And if the Third Prince were to succeed, then it would be a good bonus for our family. In the end, this matter has both danger and benefits, half and half.”

The madam then said, “Alright, I will go approach Megan in the next two days. What about you? When will you send the letter for Zhao Hai? You should use the Blood Hawk he gave you to get it to him as soon as possible or else it would be too late if the family already sent their 9th rank expert.”

Smith nodded and said, “From what I heard, Zhao Hai was still not in Jade Water City. This made it difficult for us to find him, which also made it difficult for the family to find him. And even if he comes back, he should still be safe inside the city. After he returns to Jade Water City, I will immediately send him the letter asking him to come back to Sky Water City.”

The madam knit her brows, “But will Zhao Hai come?”

Smith replied with a serious tone, “He surely will, for his two previous actions, it showed that he didn’t want to get in serious conflict with the family. But even if he suffered a bit from the family, he should still have good impression of me. If I send him a letter, he will certainly come.”

The madam nodded, “Alright, then I shall ask Megan’s opinion as soon as possible.” Smith also nodded, then sighed. The madam looked at him and knew that he was anxious about this situation, so she consoled him, “The family had been around for so long, it has surely experienced its ups and downs, but it is still standing today. It wouldn’t be easy for it to be destroyed.”

Smith sighed and said, “It was because the Calci Family existed for a long time that father and the elders thought that nothing fatal would happen to the family. In the past where the Radiant Church still had its knife on the family’s neck, the family was constantly pushed till their backs were on the wall. And now that the we have won a single battle, they didn’t see that there was virtually no damage done to the core strength of the Radiant Church. The family even couldn’t wait before they completely got rid of their enemy, this is too pitiful.”

The madam sighed as well, she knew that her husband had given his all for the family for all these years. But now the family was heading towards its current direction. It was no wonder that Smith felt very sad.

…

When the day turned noon, the madam found Megan inside the study room, reading. These days, Megan rarely went out to play, for her going out was now pointless. She had already played around sufficiently, already ate everything she found delicious, right now, there was nothing that came to interest her.

The madam naturally knew Megan’s thoughts. She quietly stood at the door of the study and looked at her daughter who was focused on her reading. The madam’s heart couldn’t help but sigh, her daughter had finally grew and and reached marriageable age.

While Megan was very focused, the madam coughed slightly, this woke Megan up. Then she saw her mother and immediately placed down the book as she stood up, “Mom, why did you come? I thought you were at your medicinal garden.”

The madam smiled and said, “I just can’t stay inside the garden all day. Right, Megan, why haven’t you gone out to play? Is there something wrong? Are you unhappy?”

Megan shook her head and said, “It’s nothing, but nothing just excites me. I feel bored when I go out to eat and drink. I might as well read at home.”

The madam arrived at Megan’s side as she patted Megan’s head, she smiled and said, “My small Megan had grown up, she finally became very sensible. Hehe. Your father will certainly be happy.”

Megan pouted her lips and said, “I don’t think so. I already told father and asked him to do something for me. But until now, he still hasn’t come up with something for me. I can only be here everyday, reading and being bored to death.”

The madam couldn’t help but smile to Megan and reply, “You silly thing. You think handling matters is that amusing? That is much more boring compared to reading a book. Otherwise, why do you think I always stay inside my medicinal garden and handed everything about the house over to the housekeeper? You silly girl should think properly for yourself, truly.”

Megan spat out her tongue and chuckled naughtily. Seeing Megan’s expression, the madam couldn’t help but sigh heavily inside. But she still said in a soft manner, “Megan, do you like Laura and Meg?”

Upon hearing her mother’s words, Megan couldn’t help but put on a gloomy expression as she nodded, “Sister Laura and Sister Meg have become my best friends. They also saved my life, but the family is currently going after them. Mom, couldn’t Dad just stop them?”

The madam sighed, “You silly girl, do you think that your father is the Patriarch? There are some matters that your father cannot handle, he must listen to the family.”

Megan didn’t say anything, although she was like her mother who didn’t care much about family matters. Children of the family were still aware of the simple matters within it. She also knew that there were some things that even her father cannot deal with.

The madam looked at Megan and knew that her daughter understood. At this time she softly said to Megan, “There really is something wrong with the family, hai, I don’t know what would happen to Zhao hai. Right, Megan, what do you think of Zhao Hai?”

Megan’s heart couldn’t help but jump when she heard her mother. To be honest, Megan’s impression of Zhao Hai was very good. When she was attacked before, she asked Laura and Meg and found out that without Zhao Hai’s warning, the two wouldn’t be able to protect her. Because of this, Megan felt grateful to Zhao Hai.

But she was a girl, thin-skinned, she couldn’t go to Zhao Hai and express her gratitude personally. Also, when Zhao Hai was staying inside Sky Water City, they didn’t have a lot of interactions with each other. In her mind, Zhao Hai was that man who seem to have an ever-present smile on his face, someone who loved Laura and Meg, the kind of love that made people feel envy.

The most important point was that Zhao Hai respected Laura and Meg very much. He just let Laura do their thing and trusted them wholeheartedly. He also seem to have something that made Megan feel attracted to. Therefore, when the madam asked Megan what she thought of Zhao Hai, her heart couldn’t help but beat crazily,  making her face flushed.

Smith’s wife was an experienced person, when she saw Megan’s expression, she understood. She sighed and thought that this girl had finally fallen. But the madam still opened her mouth and say, “Mister Zhao Hai just recently dealt with your fifth Uncle. He also snatched 20 ships from the family. I heard that your fifth uncle is still out at sea.”

Megan stared, she gave her mother a look and said, “Mom, what about fifth uncle? Why did he find trouble with mister?”

The madam sighed, “Not only this, your father has received a notice from the family today. It said that the family would be sending a 9th rank expert to deal with mister Zhao Hai. This time, I’m afraid that mister Zhao Hai wouldn’t be able to escape.”

Megan’s complexion paled, she looked at her mother and said, “Mom, are you sure? The family would really send a 9th rank expert to kill mister Zhao Hai? How can the family do this? No, I’m going to find father, I’ll make him save mister.”

The madam held Megan’s hand hastily and said, “Megan, wait. Don’t worry, your father and I already discussed this. Sending the 9th rank was still awaiting approval from the Elder’s Assembly. But we also think that rescuing Mister Zhao Hai is very difficult, at the very least your father wouldn’t be able to do it.”

Megan’s face changed color, she looked very anxious as she asked, “Mom, what should I do to stop the family from sending a 9th rank to kill mister?”

The madam looked at Megan’s face and knew what her daughter was thinking. She patted Megan’s head and said, “You father had thought of a way to save Mister Zhao Hai. Megan, you’re not young anymore, I think we should start looking for your husband. Did you already have someone on mind? You can tell me and your mother will help you in this matter.”

As soon as Megan heard her mother, her face immediately reddened, “Mom, we are talking about Mister’s matter. How did we arrive to my own matters?”

The madam smiled, “You’re already not young. At your age, your mother had already kissed your dad. Let’s talk about it? Why are you so embarrassed?”

Chapter 420: Megan’s Idea

Megan looked at her mother, she wasn’t embarrassed, but she really didn’t have someone who had moved her heart inside Sky Water City, for her this matter was quite awkward.

At this time, a figure slowly appeared on her mind, becoming clearer and clearer. The person wore a gentle smile, had a decent body, wore his robe in a way that she hadn’t seen before, and was speaking in a very relaxed tone. After the image became very clear, she saw one person, Zhao Hai!

When thinking of Zhao Hai, Megan’s face couldn’t help but turn red. However, when she was reminded of Zhao Hai’s present situation, her complexion paled. But Megan was  stronger than before, she had once come across a situation where she was helpless. She learned something from the assassination attempt done on her.

Without a doubt, she was concerned about Zhao Hai. So when her mother told her about his current predicament, she became very anxious. At this point, her mind had two matters in it, one was Zhao Hai, and the other was her marriage.[1]

But when Zhao Hai’s figure appeared on her mind, the two immediately connected with each other. Megan seemed to have cleared her mind as the two thoughts united.

When the madam saw that Megan didn’t speak, her expression changed alternately from feeling strange to feeling confused. She looked at Megan and said, “Megan, did something happen? What are you thinking about.

Megan turned her head to look at her mother’s eyes and said, “Mom, what method did father think about to save mister Zhao Hai? Can you tell me?”

The madam looked at Megan and said, “Megan, we really cannot do anything. It’s not something you should worry about. Come tell me what you were just thinking about.”

Megan looked at the madam and said, “Mom, if I marry mister Zhao Hai, can father save him?”

Megan’s question took the words out of the madam’s mouth. Her main purpose for explaining Zhao Hai’s situation today was to gauge Megan’s thoughts about the young man. If Megan had a good impression of him, then the madam would slowly inch their conversations in the next few days  towards marrying Zhao Hai. If she agrees, then the matter would be easily solved.

The madam didn’t think that Megan would actually think of such a thing. Because there are a lot of factors involved, the madam thought Megan’s mind would be on other matters.

Megan saw her mother not speaking, she thought that her idea wasn’t received well. She quickly added, “Mom, if I marry mister Zhao Hai, he would be one of us. If he becomes family, then won’t the family stop sending people to deal with him?”

The madam recovered, she looked at Megan and sighed, “Megan, do you really want to? If you marry Zhao Hai, you would have to share him with Laura and Meg.”

Megan’s face turned red, but she still nodded firmly, “Yes mom, I’m thinking that if marry mister, it won’t just be because I have a favorable impression of him, but also for the sake of the Calci Family.”

The madam looked at Megan in shock, “Megan, why do you say that?”

Megan replied, “Mom, although I don’t know much about the family, I’m quite aware of its recent situation. Mister Zhao Hai has the ability and strength, if he became a member of the family, it would gain a lot from him. I know what our ancestors said about not marrying the family’s women for benefits, however, I have a genuine good impression towards mister. And now that the family is going to send a 9th rank after him, father wouldn’t be able to save him easily. But if I marry mister Zhao Hai, he would become one of our own, that would give father a proper reason to save him, right?”

The madam stared at Megan, she didn’t think that her daughter would say those words. She hugged Megan and said, “My little girl has grown up. Megan, what you said is indeed true. But do you really like Zhao Hai? If not, your father and I won’t support you in marrying him.”

Megan said in a soft voice, “Mother, I have decided.”[2]

The madam still felt as though she had something strange in her heart, she thought that Megan indeed had interest in Zhao Hai, but not to the point where she would want to marry him. And the reason behind Megan’s decision would be in a large part her consideration for the Calci Family. This would leave a bad taste in the madam’s mouth.

Fortunately, Megan has feelings for Zhao Hai, and its stronger that what she expected. The madam replied, “I’ve wronged you, my little Megan. But don’t worry, if Zhao Hai dares to treat you badly, then I’ll let Father tidy him up. Now that you have made your decision, we have a way to save him. I’ll go tell your father to send Zhao Hai a letter so that he can be safe as soon as possible.”

Megan nodded, then the madam stood up and left the room. Megan was left in the room staring, thinking about what she just said. Now that her words had finally caught up, her face immediately turned hot as though it was burning. She didn’t know what she just did, she just uttered those words unconsciously. Now, when she recalls her words, she couldn’t help but blush.

But no matter what, she has already decided. Changing it now would be impossible, and Megan didn’t think of changing it anyway. She just felt strange, she didn’t expect that she would actually get engaged.

At this point, the madam’s mood was very complicated. When she returned to their courtyard, she found Smith and told him about Megan’s situation.

Smith didn’t think that Megan would make her decision this quickly. While he felt relief, he was also angry at Zhao Hai. Smith didn’t know when Zhao Hai had unexpectedly captured her daughter’s heart.

Although Smith looked highly upon Zhao Hai, as a father, he was obligated to get mad at the person who took the heart of his daughter.

At this moment, the madam looked at Smith and said, “Dear, will you write Zhao Hai’s letter now?”

Smith thought for a moment and shook his head, “Not is not the time. We’ll wait until Zhao Hai returns to Jade Water City before sending it. In any case, we have his Blood Hawk with us, he’ll receive the letter at the quickest time possible.”

The madam nodded then sighed, “I hope that nothing goes wrong this time. Otherwise, Zhao Hai will be in danger. I wish that the family wouldn’t be quick in sending people to deal with him.”

Smith agreed, “Right, now we can only trust Zhao Hai’s speed.”

….

When Zhao Hai saw this Blood Hawk, he knew that this should be the one he left behind for Smith. He immediately went outside and took the letter that Smith wrote to him.

After reading the contents of the letter, Zhao Hai’s complexion changed. Naturally, Smith didn’t include his plan of marrying his daughter to Zhao Hai in this letter. He only wrote about how the family disagreed with his plan of reconciling with Zhao Hai and that they were prepared to send 9th rank experts. He also expressed that he has a plan to deal with the matter and that Zhao Hai needs to meet him at Sky Water City.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Calci Family to send 9th rank experts to deal with him. Although he didn’t fear the other party’s 9th rank expert, he also didn’t want to develop a mortal enmity with the Calci Family. If he does become enemies with the family, it would be disadvantageous to his future plans. The family might pressure Charlie, and Charlie might not want to offend the Calci Family in favor of him. At that time, Zhao Hai feared that he wouldn’t be able to stay inside Rosen Empire.

When Zhao Hai returned to the room, he gave the letter to Laura. From what Laura saw in Zhao Hai’s complexion, it must have been a serious matter. She immediately read the letter and soon enough, her expression also changed. She handed the letter off to Meg as she turned to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, what do you think?”

In a serious voice, Zhao Hai replied, “I guess we have no other choice other than to head towards Sky Water City and go see what Smith plans to do. Otherwise, we can only deal with the 9th rank of the family and hope that they will stop bothering us.”

Laura thought that this situation was impossible. If they really kill the 9th rank of the Calci Family, they definitely wouldn’t let them off. 9th ranks are extremely important to any family.

After Meg and the others read the letter, their faces changed as well. They understood that if the Calci Family goes through with sending 9th ranks after them, then that meant that the family has decided to completely destroy their group.

Laura said, “When do we leave?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I’ll go and talk to Trezebo first. Then let’s have the Haven head towards Ape Island while the rest of the ships stay behind to be filled up by Mu’en. I’ll go send a Blood Hawk carrying the Ghost Staff back to Sky Water City. After it arrives, we’ll appear there via the Space. For us, the seas are no longer safe.”

Laura understood what Zhao Hai meant, if the Calci Family sends its 9th rank after them, the seas would certainly be unable to keep them safe. For a 9th rank expert, there was no need to use a ship to travel the sea, flying was enough.”

Laura nodded, “Alright, i’ll go inform Mu’en while you go see Trezebo.”

Zhao Hai nodded and immediately went out to give the Blood Hawk the ghost staff before releasing it. Then he went to look for Trezebo. At the same time, Laura took the carriage and headed towards Mu’en.

Although he might be exposing some of his secrets with his method of going to Sky Water City this time, Zhao Hai didn’t care. If they cannot deal with the matter of the Calci Family, then they would have a powerful enemy, Zhao Hai didn’t want to see that.

Trezebo was currently on his room resting and drinking wine. At this moment, a servant came and reported that Zhao Hai came to ask for an audience. He stared for a moment before immediately inviting Zhao Hai inside.

But when Zhao Hai came in, Trezebo couldn’t help but notice the strange expression on Zhao Hai’s face. Trezebo quickly said, “Mister Zhao Hai, what happened?”

Zhao Hai looked at Trezebo and said, “City Lord, I’m afraid I have to leave Jade Water City immediately. I might be gone for several days, but I promise to return as soon as I have taken care of the situation.”

* * *

Ruyen got baited by her mother. Moms are scary man.

I love how they just knew that Zhao Hai would agree, xD, what do you think our homeboy is?

Chapter 421: Doesn’t Need a Reason

Trezebo looked at Zhao Hai and said, “For mister to leave immediately, it seems like a really important matter. Can I do something to help?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “We’ll handle this matter ourselves. I just came to say my farewells to the City Lord before we leave.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, Trezebo decided that there was nothing he could do. So he just nodded and said, “Alright, then mister must go immediately. If there’s anything I can do, then don’t hesitate and tell me. Even if I’m busy, I’ll try my best to help.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Very well, if the time comes, I won’t be polite. Well then, I’ll go take my leave.”

When Zhao Hai left the City Lord’s Mansion, Shue and Shun were already outside. The three immediately rode the carriage that Trezebo prepared and hurried towards the pier.

After arriving at the pier, they immediately boarded the Haven. This was also just a way to let people see that they left Jade Water City using their ship.

Shortly after they arrived at the Haven, Laura and the others also arrived. They told him that Mu’en was already informed. Zhao Hai left the five ships that they had stolen from the Markey Family behind Jade Water City.

Zhao Hai didn’t know, but after he left Jade Water City, Trezebo immediately asked his people to see what happened that made Zhao Hai very anxious to leave. At the same time, he also wrote a letter to Charlie.

Trezebo knew how much importance Charlie had attached to Zhao Hai. After seeing Zhao Hai so anxious, Trezebo understood that he must have ran into a very thorny matter otherwise he wouldn’t be acting like this. This also made Trezebo very concerned.

..

At this time, Zhao Hai was sitting inside the cabin while looking at the monitor. He was very annoyed right now, he actually didn’t want to see Smith at this time. However, he didn’t expect the Calci Family to be very imposing. But reason told him that he needed to endure this time and go take a look at what Smith had planned.

Laura and the others were also closely observing the monitor, in reality, they weren’t actually worried about the 9th rank experts of the Calci Family. They believed that with Zhao Wen and Cai’er, even if the other party came with three or four 9th ranks, they could still find ways to kill them. But the Calci Family cannot afford to send that many experts for just this matter, so naturally they wouldn’t send that much to deal with Zhao Hai.

But although they weren’t worried about their safety, they need to consider the impact this matter would bring. After all, they aren’t a huge power in the continent, they cannot provide anything that could threaten the Calci Family.

The Blood Hawk was quick, after several hours, it finally arrived at Sky Water City. The city didn’t have a curfew, so the streets were still quite active even if it was already evening.

Zhai Hai made the Blood Hawk place the Ghost Staff outside the city, then they immediately went there from the Space to proceed towards the City Lord’s Mansion. But Zhao Hai didn’t ride his eye-catching bull-pulled carriage. Instead, he released some horses from the Space and rode them towards the Mansion’s direction.

At this time, Zhao Hai and the others already changed their clothes to those that ordinary warriors wore. Only Meg was different since she wore a Mage’s robe. When people saw them dressed like this, they could only assume that they were young nobles who went out to play, so they didn’t pay Zhao Hai’s group any more attention.

Zhao Hai and the others arrived at Sky Water City’s Mansion quickly. The mansion looked just like what it did before. Zhao Hai sent the Blood Hawk to deliver his letter to Smith telling him that they would be waiting at the mansion’s side entrance.

Sure enough, not long after the arrived, Phil opened the door to the mansion. Zhao Hai immediately jumped down from his horse and looked at Phil, “Uncle Phil, the matter has become very troublesome, how would Brother Smith deal with it?”

Phil looked at Zhao Hai strangely, “The City Lord will tell you, please come inside.” Then he brought Zhao Hai and the others to the mansion’s living room.

Smith was already waiting for Zhao Hai there, at the same time, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would arrive this quickly. When he saw Zhao Hai outside the room, he immediately went and invited him in as Phil served them some tea. Smith looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I didn’t expect you to come this quickly. How did you do it?”

Zhao Hai replied with a serious voice, “Before I answer, let’s talk first. How could the situation arrive here? Does the family really want me dead that they were even prepared to send a 9th rank expert after me?”

Smith smiled bitterly, “I didn’t think that the family would respond like this as well. Unfortunately for them, they informed me.”

Zhao Hai looked at Smith and said, “How are you planning to solve this problem? If you can’t, then we’ll do it my way.”

Smith stared at Zhao Hai, he was puzzled, “Your way? Do you have a method to solve it?”

Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed a cold light, “Killing the 9th rank they send out. Let’s see how many 9th ranks the family is prepared to lose in dealing with me.”

Smith almost stood up, his eyes were set on Zhao Hai. He understood from Zhao Hai’s words that he had the power to kill 9th rank experts.

This made Smith very surprised.  9th rank experts aren’t people who were easy to please. Ordinary Clans wouldn’t even have a 9th rank to take care of them.

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure? We’re talking about 9th ranks here, not 8th ranks.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted, “I’m speaking the truth. If the Calci Family were to send one 9th rank after me, he will definitely die. If they send two, they will die as well. To be frank, as long as they don’t send five 9th ranks, everything they send will just be exterminated. I can assure you that I will stay intact, but I cannot say the same for your Calci Family.”

Smith stared, then his complexion turned ugly, “What? Are you threatening me?”

Cold lights passed through Zhao Hai’s eyes, “You all want to take my life and I can’t even say threatening sentences? Are you afraid?”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and suddenly laughed, “Good, young man, your words are very good, hahaha. Alright, I’ll tell you my method.”

Seeing that Zhao Hai was determined, Smith couldn’t help but calm down, “Looking at your appearance, you don’t really want to be enemies with our Calci Family.  Am I right?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I don’t want to. To be honest, I’m not afraid of the people from your family, I’m not actually afraid of your Calci Family. But I don’t want to get in trouble with the Rosen Empire. I have a lot of things in my hand, but they still needed to be turned into money to provide for what I need. Currently, other than the Rosen Empire, the influence of the Radiant Church is very strong in the continent. And since the church is my mortal enemy, doing business on other nations would be very difficult. This is the reason why I don’t want to get driven away from Rosen Empire. If there’s a way to avoid fighting with your Calci Family, then I would prefer that. If I have no means of getting money, then things would be very hard for me.”

Smith nodded and said, “Looks like I guessed right. Then I’ll tell you my method. This wouldn’t only stop us from dealing with you, this will also make the family attach great importance to you and help you succeed.”

Zhao Hai stared, he was confused, he looked at Smith and said, “What is it?”

Smith smiled faintly and said, “You getting engaged to Megan.”

Zhao Hai froze, he looked at Smith with shock and said, “Are you cracking a joke? Megan? Are you crazy?”

Smith shook his head, “I’m not. If you marry Megan, you’ll become someone on our side, and the family would support you. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “This wouldn’t be good, Megan doesn’t like me. And we don’t have any emotional foundation. It’ll also be unfair to Megan, we can’t do this.”

At this time, Megan’s voice was head, “Brother Zhao Hai, I already knew of this matter, and I agree. I like you as a person, I don’t want to see you in trouble. Most importantly, I don’t want to see you and my Calci Family in trouble with each other.”

When Zhao Hai followed the voice, he saw Megan. She was standing in front of the living room and calmly looked at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at Megan ang gave a smile, “Megan, why are you doing this? We have no feelings with each other. You don’t know much about me, this will be unfair to you.”

Megan shook her head and said, “There’s no reason to like someone. There is also no such thing as unfair. I just came to like you, and I don’t know when it started. I know that we haven’t been interacting for long, and you don’t think much about me, but I still like you.”[1]

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he really didn’t know what to say. It was just like what Megan said, their meetings weren’t that long. Even if they were together, Zhao Hai didn’t seriously talk with Megan. He really didn’t know how such an ordinary, boring man like him managed to attract Megan.

At this time, Laura smiled, she went towards Megan’s side and said, “Megan, fantastic! We can be sisters forever, right Meg?”

Meg also smiled, “Yup, we’re going to be sisters later.”

Zhao Hai looked at the two insane women, he was speechless. He didn’t know why even though they’re going to divide their husband, they were still happy.

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and snorted, “Boy, you got it easy, I didn’t know you had such game. To actually dare snatch my daughter from me. But you should tell me about your identity. Who are you?”

Zhao Hai looked at Smith. A soon as he heard how he was called, he couldn’t help but smile. It seems like he has to reveal his identity.

* * *

cmonbruh

Chapter 422: Identity

At this time, Laura and Meg were at the side chatting with Megan. On the other side, the madam had been lead to the living room by Phil and then she sat in front of Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai can only force a smile and said, “Actually, my background isn’t really that mysterious, but there were only a few who knew about it. My surname is Buda, I changed my name to Zhao Hai later.”

Upon hearing that Zhao Hai was surnamed Buda, Smith stared blankly. His complexion changed as his voice was raised, “Are you really surnamed Buda? That Buda Clan’s successor who was bestowed the Black Wasteland by the Aksu Empire, Adam Buda?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, I am Adam Buda. But I have changed my name to Zhao Hai, the Adam from before is now dead.”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Didn’t you drink the Water of Nothingness? Why can you use Magic? Right, according to Bell, you’re not using magic, but a divergent ability. So you really can’t use Magic?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, I can use Magic. The toxin from the Water of Nothingness has already been solved. I’m now a Magic and Battle Qi Dual-Cultivator. My Battle QI is at 8th rank, and my Magic is at 8th rank as well.”

Smith was very surprised, he stared at Zhao Hai, “Water of Nothingness can be cured? Is that really possible? You’re not deceiving me right?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “I’m not deceiving you. My toxin from the Water of Nothingness has indeed been cured. But there is only one cure and it took me a long time before completing it. Otherwise, why did you think that Laura and Meg were still my fiance’s and not my wives?”

Zhao Hai understood why Smith was too worked up, this was because the Water of Nothingness was a hereditary poison. If Zhao Hai’s toxin was not solved, then Smith might not let Megan marry him. After all, if they have children, they wouldn’t be able to cultivate either Magic or Battle Qi.

Because he read Smith’s mind, Zhao Hai immediately told Smith that his toxin has already been solved.

When Smith heard Zhao Hai he couldn’t help but turn to look at Laura. Laura smiled at Smith and faintly smiled, “It’s true, Brother Hai’s poison has indeed been solved. If you didn’t call us today, we might have had our wedding two days later.”

Smith relaxed and said, “Good, it’s solved, good! No wonder nobody can find out about your origin. You’re actually a member of the Buda Clan. Hahaha. Nobody in the continent would think that the Water of Nothingness actually had an antidote.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “This isn’t strange, there’s no poison that didn’t have a cure. So what about the engagement that you proposed? Will you reconsider it?”

Smith blinked. “What? You don’t want to? Are you saying my Megan isn’t worthy for you? If you dare to decline, I will really have the family chase you with 9th ranks.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile, “Alright, I’ll talk to my elders at home later and discuss when we’ll get engaged.”

Smith coldly snorted, “No need to discuss it. It will be tomorrow, the sooner the better. Otherwise, it will be troublesome if the family sends its 8th ranks.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown, “Did the family really plan to send 9th ranks my way? Isn’t this too strange? Is there something I have done to offend the whole Calci Family?”

Smith sighed then he told Zhao Hai about the guesses that him and Phil had made. After Zhao Hai listened to it, his shocked face turned to Smith, “Because of that? Killing me because of my leadership ability? If they continue doing this, then the Dark Mage profession would surely die out. What kind of idiot decides to kill talented people? How did it came to this?”

Smith smiled bitterly, “I don’t know, but this has always been the family’s style. Even I cannot prevent them from doing this.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I initially felt it strange that the Radiant Church didn’t offend any other Mage profession other than the Dark Mages. So this was the reason, the Calci Family was actually destroying the profession’s future.”

Smith smiled bitterly, he didn’t have any good thing to say. He just sighed and said, “Let’s let that go for now. You should head back and rest, tomorrow we’ll release information about your engagement with Megan. Not only to the family, but also to the entire continent.”

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brow “How about Charlie? If information about my engagement with Megan gets passed on, how will it affect the Calci Family? Did you already think this through? Didn’t Great Nobles abstain from participating in battles for the throne? Will this bring misunderstanding to the Calci Family?”

Smith smiled, “It’s complicated, but it shouldn’t have effects. Prince Charlie might even be happy, as for other people? Their opinions don’t matter. What’s important right now is your safety.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod. Smith looked at him and said, “It’s already late, go get some rest. We still have a lot to do tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he lead Laura and the others back to Sweet Plum Courtyard. The moment they entered the courtyard, they immediately went to the Space and headed to Iron Mountain Fort to report everything to Green.

When Green heard Zhao Hai’s report, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Fantastic! Hahaha. Young Master, this is very good news. If we have the support of the Calci Family, we would have less problems when restoring our Clan’s prestige. I didn’t think that the young master would actually be so fierce.”

Kun looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Boy, why are you so lucky? First, Laura likes you, now it’s Megan. One day you will make all the women in this world crazy. What would the other young men say then?”

Zhao Hai can only smile bitterly while listening to their teasing. Even he didn’t expect it to be like this, he didn’t have anything so say.

Merien didn’t care so much. When she heard Zhao Hai had acquired another fiance, she couldn’t help but happily said, “Good. Young Master, we should find some time for your wedding as soon as possible. It’s important for the Buda Family to have a proper branch.”

Green agreed, “Before, we didn’t get to arrange your wedding with Laura and Meg because of your toxin. But now that you’ve been cured, we should immediately arrange for your wedding.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “I also thought that, and I told Laura and Meg about it today. In the past, I really wanted to marry them, but that would be unfair for them. I think that since the Buda Clan still hasn’t re-emerged on the continent, it would be an injustice to them if we marry secretly. And now, with the addition of Megan, the situation became even more complex. Who is Megan? She’s Calci Family’s little princess. Even if she becomes engaged, it was impossible for her to immediately marry. So if I arrange my marriage with Laura and Meg, the Calci Family would certainly not agree. In the end, it seems like we need to delay the marriage.”

Green sighed, “Looks like we can only do this. Also, for a Great Noble such as the Calci Family, they should have their own special customs. I heard that there are some other ceremonies to do if a female from their family gets married. It seems like we can only delay the wedding.”

Kun nodded, “Actually it doesn’t matter if they wed later. Now that Little Hai’s body has been solved, his body is much better than before. Not like in the past where we fear that he will only live a short life. Now we only need to avoid being enemies with the Calci Family, otherwise trouble will keep chasing us in the future.”

Green agreed, “That is true. Right, Little Hai, you said that you want to be engaged tomorrow? Do you want me to come?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No, Smith wanted to engage us by himself. Let’s just wait and see what the Calci Family will do.”

Green nodded, “That’s also good. It seems like Smith wanted this engagement to be simple. Just for the sake of announcing it immediately. Alright, it’s still an unusual time to get married anyway. Let’s just wait and prepare a better wedding.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “My engagement with Laura and Meg was simple as well, so we might as well do the same with Megan, so that it’s not unfair on the two. I’ll tell this to Smith tomorrow.”

Green nods, “Right, Little Hai. Yesterday, the final beer product finally came out. It’s just as you said, it’s good, its taste is very nice.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes lit up, “They’re done? That’s great! How were they? Are there several types?”

Green smiled, “It has, one came out golden, another one is grey, and the last one is black. And the grain wine that you talked about? It’s really good.”

Zhao Hai’s grain wine wasn’t the same as the others, it was in fact rice wine. It’s method of brewing was relatively simple. However, it had its advantages. It’s degree was no high, it tastes mellow. And rice wine can be drank by many people, men, women, and children.

Merine immediately brought the liquors over. Zhao Hai tasted them, the beer were vastly better than what he tasted before. The taste of rice wine was also good. After all, the rice was from the Space, it would be strange if it wasn’t good.

Zhao Hai placed his glass down and turned to Green, “This is very good. Grandpa Green, I want to mass produce these types of liquor. What do you think?”

Green nodded, “We should. Young Master, you should leave some undead here and pull out all of the stones you mined. I’m directing those undead to build a liquor factory. You should know that the space inside the Castle isn’t enough. If we don’t build a new building, there will be no place for further expansion.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I’ll leave behind 10 thousand undeads as well as the mined stones. Right, I have the Shi Lie Jie twins, they’re Earth Mages and can make stone golems. Constructing houses shouldn’t be problem.”

Green gave anod, “That’s good. Young Master, you should go rest.” Zhao Hai agreed and returned to the Space to rest.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others were summoned by Smith to the courtyard to have some some breakfast. After eating their meal, Smith had Phil announce Zhao Hai’s engagement with Megan back to the headquarters. This was deliberately done by Smith to pressure the family into not destroying the engagement by stopping its acts against Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai also told Smith that he wanted the engagement to be simple. Smith didn’t oppose, it was a special case this time, those extra things could be exempted.

However, even if he said this, Smith still had Zhao Hai and Megan go out together and play. This was to increase their familiarity with each other. Megan was very embarrassed, he face was entirely red as she and Zhao Hai left the City Lord’s Mansion.

But at this time, news of Megan’s engagement with Zhao Hai had already spread all over the entire Sky Water City. This threw an unexpected bomb into the usual state of the city.

One must know that in Sky Water City, there were a ton of people who wanted to marry Megan. But they hadn’t imagined that Megan would actually get engaged suddenly. There was even no ceremony for the engagement, nor was there a banquet. In deep silence, Megan would no longer belong to them.

Soon enough, the people of Sky Water City became crazy. When Zhao Hai went out to play, there were more than 20 Noble men to approached as though Megan needed to be rescued. When Megan told him that the engagement was true, they all turned away with their hearts broken.

Looking at this scene, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. One must say that Megan was very popular inside Sky Water City. It seems like this has also become a quite troublesome matter.

Even more troublesome was the fact that Zhao Hai didn’t know what the Calci Family felt about his engagement with Megan. Smith engaging his daughter to him this time was a clear indication that SKy Water City’s Lord was adamant in protecting him as well as the future of the Calci Family. In front of the supposed action against ZHao Hai, Smith decided to slap the face of the family. Now, wouldn’t the elders in the family have ugly expressions?

At the thought of this, Zhao Hai turned his head to look at Megan who was chatting with Laura and Meg. Seeing Megan’s flower-like smile, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but say in his mind, “No matter what the Calci Family decides on, I will marry Megan.”

Megan felt Zhao Hai’s gaze on her, she looked up and met Zhao Hai’s eyes before lowering her head again as she blushed. Her brave appearance yesterday seemed like a dream, but Zhao Hai had to admit, this Megan was quite cute.

Chapter 423: The Family Patriarch Arrives

Just as Zhao Hai thought about this, the Calci Family received the information regarding Zhao Hai and Megan’s engagement. Their initial response was surprise and was immediately followed by anger!

The Calci Family are experienced in regards to their member, so naturally they understood what Smith wanted to do. Smith wanted to guarantee Zhao Hai’s life.

Initially they wanted to disregard the engagement and continue on with their plans. However, upon further consideration they didn’t want to have a falling out with Smith. Although Smith was a member of the family, he was strongly independent. If they really made Smith distance himself from the family, they would definitely lose a huge chunk of their income.

Moreover, the family understood that with Zhao Hai’s engagement with Megan, he was now on the same side as them. This was equivalent to gaining more strength, for the family, this was great.

Although the ancestors had ordered that the women of the family cannot be married for benefits, for families like the Calci Family, that kind of situation rarely happens. No matter what kind of marriage they do, it will always be linked with politics. In the end, the marriage would inadvertently bring forth benefits.

Megan was in good graces with the family, she was their precious little princess. Naturally, the people from the family wouldn’t want to marry her off as a tool. But at the same time, the family had concerns about who Megan was going to marry. In any case, they have to find a common ground.

From their point of view, Zhao Hai’s identity was not worth marrying Megan. But if the family didn’t acknowledge their engagement, the people will lose faith and then and at the same time they would become a laughingstock among the nobles. Similarly, Megan’s reputation would also be ruined.

But they really couldn’t just swallow this outcome. In the end, the Patriarch of the family, Smith’s father, Randolph Calci couldn’t sit still anymore. So he decided to head towards Sky Water City and personally meet this Zhao Hai.

Although Randolph was the Patriarch, he was also a person, and he loved Megan. So he wanted to go to Sky Water City to see what kind of person Zhao Hai was and see how he will handle the situation.

Ever since he heard Zhao Hai’s name until now, he hasn’t seen Zhao Hai’s face. He only decided on his impression of the young man based on the reports of his subordinates, as well as Bell, Smith, and Juwan.

However these people had differing impressions of Zhao Hai. According to Bell, Zhao Hai was a very good Divergent Mage, moreover he also had a lot of businesses that could make money.

Smith’s assessment of him was high as well. According to Smith, he was a very smart person, moreover, his leadership ability is very strong. Most importantly, his strength is immeasurable deep.

Juwan, on the other hand, naturally didn’t put in good word in behalf of Zhao Hai. According to Juwan, Zhao Hai was a very arrogant and domineering person, a villain who was ignorant regarding the proper action to take.

After combining all of these descriptions, Randolph thought of Zhao Hai as an ambitious and arrogant man. This was why he decided to deal with him.

But now that Smith had shown his hand, Randolph was placed on an embarrassing situation. He had to stop the family from sending 9th ranks to deal with Zhao Hai since he needs to meet that man himself when he arrives at Sky Water City.

At this time, Charlie also received the information. Upon receiving it, he was glad. Then he felt that something was wrong. He knew that Zhao Hai was in conflict with Juwan from the Calci Family not too long ago. So how did he arrive to the situation of marrying the princess of the family?

Charlie was very familiar regarding the Calci Family. He was someone who was fighting for the throne, so of course he was informed about the old nobles of the empire.

And for Megan, he also knew about her, it was impossible not to, she was the family’s precious Sugar Plum Princess. This was why when Lionheart made a move against Megan in the past, Charlie knew that he wouldn’t live long, the Calci Family wouldn’t allow him to.

Then suddenly, Zhao Hai unexpectedly got engaged to Megan. This made Charlie feel awe. He wanted to know what was going on, so he sent a letter to Trezebo in order to check it out.

Trezebo was also very confused. Just a day after Zhao Hai was very anxious to leave Jade Water City, he suddenly got engaged to Megan. This made Trezebo extremely surprised, judging from Zhao Hai’s expression when he left, it didn’t seem like he was going to be engaged.

The fifth day after Zhao Hai arrived at SKy Water City, Lando arrived. He came in secret this time, he didn’t want to be overly known.

Just as he disembarked from the ship, he saw Smith and Phil already there waiting for him at the pier. When he gazed at the people who received him, he didn’t see Megan’s figure, nor did he see Zhao Hai. His face became sullen as he looked at Smith, “Where is Megan?”

Smith quickly replied, “She went to sea three days ago. Little Hai had something to do, and Megan wanted to follow, so she went.”

Randolph snorted, he looked at Smith and Phil and said, “Let’s go to the mansion and talk.” Then they rode the carriage and headed to the City Lord’s Mansion.

Upon arriving at the mansion, they entered the living room. Smith asked Randolph to sit down before he waved his hand to order everyone other than Phil to leave the room.

Smith and Phil had long prepared for this day, so they calmly stood there and waited for Randolph to unleash his anger.

When Lando saw that the two were acting like dead pigs who weren’t afraid of boiling water, his anger couldn’t help but flare up even more. But he suppressed his rage then looked at Smith and Phil, “Talk, how did this happen? Why did Megan get engaged to Zhao Hai? Why didn’t they wait for me to arrive? They actually dared to not see me?”

Smith calmly replied, “Because Megan likes Zhao Hai. Therefore, I just allowed her and Zhao Hai to be engaged. As for why they went to sea, it was because God’s Grace Day is fast approaching, and Zhao Hai had already made an appointment with Charlie to give him a set of shipments before then. That’s why then needed to leave early.”

Randolph look at Smith and snorted, “What? Since you’re now old and quite established, you can now ignore my words? You knew that I already gave the command to deal Zhao Hai, but you actually engaged him to Megan. What are you thinking? Are you still Calci Family? Why did you decide to trip us over?”

Smith looked at Randolph and calmly said, “Naturally, I’m still a person of the family. I did this for the family. Megan was my very loved daughter, do you think that the daughter that I very much love would just get married, without even a ceremony to Zhao Hai, just for nothing? It was you who forced me.” At the end of his dialogue, Smith was almost roaring.

Randolph looked at Smith and said coldly, “Good, you even dare shout at me. You say that you’re doing it for the family? How could it be good for the family?”

Smith looked at Randolph coldly as well, “Of course it’s good for the family. You shouldn’t treat Zhao Hai like that, if you do, the other members of the League of Dark Mages wouldn’t think well of us. Do you really want to disband the league? You want to make the Dark Mages scattered, only to be cleaned up by the Radiant Church?”

Randolph retorted, “What do you know, I’m doing this to fight against the Radiant Church. As long as we unite all of the Dark Mages under our family, then we will have the strength to fight the Church.”

Smith seemed to not listen, he then gave his reply, “is it? In the past when the Radiant Church didn’t suppress us, didn’t we also try that? What happened? Did those Dark Mages listen to us? In the end, what we did was make it harder for people to learn the profession, causing our numbers to get fewer and fewer. And when the Radiant Church finally wanted to deal with us, the Dark Mage profession almost got exterminated. Is this what you call unity?”

Randolph’s face was currently very ugly, He knew about the past matter. But he thought that time time would be different. With the plan provided by Zhao Hai, he felt like the Dark Mage was on its was to the top. At that time, the Calci Family would happily assume its leadership. It would make the family’s strength almost as great as the Radiant Church.

However, when he thinks about these, Randolph couldn’t help but be embarrassed. The method was given by Zhao Hai, and now they were actually planning on dealing with him.

Smith looked at Randolph and said, “Are you thinking that with Zhao Hai’s idea, the Dark Mage profession would grow explosively? So in that case, even if you kill some Dark Mages here and there, then it’s no big deal? Is that what you think? How long do you think training in becoming a Dark Mage would take? 20? 30? 40 years? Do you know what will happen in 20 years? Yes, with Zhao Hai’s idea, Dark Mages would certainly increase exponentially, but it was under the premise that all of the schools in Rosen Empire were producing Dark Mages. If you really succeed in placing all Dark Mages under the influence of our Calci family then our family’s power would truly increase. But at that time, what would differentiate us from the Radiant Church? Why was the Radiant Church being suppressed? Why did it vanish from Rosen Empire? Do you want to turn the family into the second Radiant Church? Even if the church were to be suppressed by the Rosen Empire, it still had its influence outside the empire. But what about us? What would happen if we do get suppressed by the alliance of all the Nobles of the empire? Do we leave? Don’t forget, other than the Rosen Empire, the world outside belongs to the Radiant Church!”

Smith’s words made Randolph perspire. His plan was just like what Smith said, essentially turning the family into a second Radiant Church. But he actually forgot that the Calci Family was still a only a Great Noble of the empire. There were also Great Nobles like them, as well as the Imperial Clan above. If they really become another Radiant Church, then they would be threatening the rule of the Imperial Clan. What would happen then? Will the other Nobles just let them off? If those Great Nobles got together and suppressed the family, what can they do?

Beside the Rosen Empire, the Radiant Church’s influence outside was overwhelming. If they leave Rosen Empire, then the Radiant Church would surely run them over.

Before, Randolph admits that he had been stunned by their victory. After all, he was the Patriarch of a Great Family, he experienced the ups and downs of the family. Now that he heard Smith’s thoughts, he sobered up and measured the pros and cons. In the end he has to acknowledge what Smith said.

At the same time, as a Patriarch, Randolph knew that the Imperial Clan wouldn’t allow the presence of a power that could threaten their rule. The same was true with the other Great Nobles. If he really did what he planned, then they both the Imperial Clan and the Great Nobles would join together in suppressing the family.

Smith looked at his father and knew that he was thinking things out. So Smith just stood there quietly, he believed that his father would figure it out. If he couldn’t, then he didn’t deserve being the Calci Family’s Patriarch.

After quite some time, Randolph let out a long breath and said, “Even if you are correct, you don’t have to marry Megan off to Zhao Hai. In the end, what does he really have?”

Upon hearing that Randolph had somehow softened, Smith felt relief. He knew that Randolph was convinced. He immediately gave his answer, “Father, I did it for the family. If we really did send a 9th rank to deal with Zhao Hai, then I fear that we would have problems. I’m afraid that the 9th rank may not be able to return.”

Randolph stared before his complexion changed, he looked at Smith and said, “Do you know what you’re talking about? That is a 9th rank expert, do you really think that Zhao Hai is that strong?”

Smith forced a smile and said, “I don’t know if he really is strong. But Zhao Hai told me that as long as you don’t send five 9th rank experts, then those 9th ranks wouldn’t be able to return. And even if we send five 9th ranks, he was confident that he could escape.”

Randolph snorted, “You actually got terrified just by listening to him? Did you really believe what he said?”

Smith smiled stiffly and said, “I believe him, father. Did you know how long he took to travel from Jade Water City to Sky Water City? Only a few hours, he flew that fast. Even common falcons aren’t that fast. Can most 9th ranks fly that fast? Because of this, I believed his words.”

Randolph’s shocked face looked at Smith and said, “Are you sure? Is he really that quick?”

Smith smiled, “If you don’t believe me, you can ask Uncle Phil.”

Phil nodded and said, “Patriarch, it’s true, Zhao Hai is indeed very quick. We have arranged a person inside Jade Water City to specifically watch out for Zhao Hai, as long as Zhao Hai appears in Jade Water City, that person would immediately send us a letter. Six days ago, in the morning Zhao Hai arrived at Jade Water City. After his arrival, the person immediately sent a Wind Falcon to us. After we received his word, we then quickly had a Blood Hawk deliver a letter to Zhao Hai, telling him to rush towards Sky Water City as soon as possible. When the Blood Hawk bearing his reply arrived at Sky Water City, Zhao Hai also arrived.”

Chapter 424: The Sea

When Randolph heard what Phil said, he couldn’t help but frown.  It would take a Wind Falcon several hours to fly from Jade Water CIty to Sky Water City. But after Zhao Hai received the letter, he unexpectedly arrived along with the Blood Hawk, this made him extremely surprised.

He had also seen the Blood Hawk that Zhao Hai gave Smith. It was very handsome, whether it be fighting strength or speed, it was much better than a Wind Falcon. However, Zhao Hai actually reached Sky Water City at the same time as the Hawk, a feat like this is extraordinary.

Smith looked at Randolph’s appearance and said, “Father, I heard some whispers coming from the Shelley Family. It said that Zhao Hai is a Space Mage, but I don’t know if it’s true or not.”

Randolph couldn’t sit still, he immediately stood up and said, “Space Mage?! Are you sure?”

Smith nodded, “The Shelley Family had issued a gag order regarding this. No matter how hard I try to inquire, I couldn’t get certain proof.”

Randolph circled the ground twice, “If he is really a Space Mage, then he is certainly worth of Megan, but what is his identity? I never did find out about it, how can you be assured in leaving Megan to such a person?”

Smith forced a smile and said, “Father, I already know his identity. Although I just knew out about it, I should not be wrong.”

Randolph said, “You found out? How is that possible? Almost all Great Clans in the continent were determined to find out, but came back with nothing. How did you manage to find out?”

Smith smiled and said, “I didn’t actually find it, Zhao Hai himself told us. Before he got engaged to Megan, I asked him for his background. And he agreed to tell us.”

Randolph looked at Smith and frowned, “So what is it? Is his identity special? Did he belong to a hidden family or a Great Power?”

Smith shook his head, “None of those. From the beginning, we had been looking at the wrong direction. He didn’t belong to a hidden family nor a great power. His surname is Buda, formerly known as Adam Buda and now he changed his name to Zhao Hai Buda.”

Randolph stared, then his eyes widened, “Buda? Are you talking about the lord of the Black Wasteland? That Buda Clan?”

Smith nodded, “Right, Black Wasteland’s lord, the Buda Clan. This was the reason why he first appeared at Black Earth Fortress. This was why his first actions happened in Purcell Duchy.”

Randolph nodded, and then his complexion changed, “You bastard, if he really is from the Buda Clan, then didn’t he drink the Water of Nothingness? How can you let him marry Megan? Are you insane???”

Smith looked at Randolph and sighed, when looking at his father’s appearance, it seems like he was looking at himself. At the time, when he found out about Zhao Hai’s identity, his reaction was the exact same as Randolph. However, he still needed to answer his father’s question, so he smiled and said, “If Zhao Hai still had the toxin from the Water of Nothingness, then how could I possibly give him Megan? The poison on his body has already been solved.”

Randolph replied, “Solved? Really?”

Smith nodded, “Indeed, I made him demonstrate Magic as well as Battle Qi. Right now, his Magic has reached 8th rank, his Battle Qi as well, 8th rank. But since he didn’t practice his Martial Arts that well before, he can only combat a 7th rank in regular battle. However, he’s actually a Mage of every element, and he’s skilled in them as well. He can also do Compound Magic. According to my calculations, his current fighting strength would make him invincible to those below 9th rank.”

Randolph stared at Smith, “Are you serious? Is he really a Multi-element mage in all elements? Dual cultivating Magic and Battle Qi? What kind of fortuitous encounter did he experience?”

Smith smiled stiffly and said, “I also want to know, but he didn’t agree to tell me. Perhaps he will tell Megan later, he couldn’t just tell anyone he couldn’t fully trust.”

Randolph knit his brows, “He’s very careful, but this is good as well. Your decision this time is truly correct, I didn’t expect this kid to be this strong. If we really did continue to cause him trouble, then we would certainly suffer a huge loss. But for this youngster to steal my granddaughter away from me, I definitely won’t forgive him.”

Smith smiled, “Father, you should know that because of our earlier actions, Zhao Hai had been pushed towards Prince Charlie. Will this affect our family?”

Randolph thought for a moment and then shook his head, “I don’t think so, Zhao Hai is still engaged to Megan, not married. And even if they are married, he is still primarily a member of the Buda Clan, not the Calci Family, so it shouldn’t affect us. Just pay attention to not get too close with Charlie.”

Smith nodded and looked at the weather as he said, “Father, it’s already quite late. Let’s go eat something. Right, Zhao Hai told me that he would return in a while. I think you’re better off staying in Sky Water City for a while if you want to see Zhao Hai.”

Randolph thought for a moment and nodded, “Alright, I haven’t seen Megan in quite a while. Then I’ll stay here for some time.”

Smith nodded, then he lead Randolph towards the dining hall along with Phil. But they didn’t think that at this time, Zhao Hai was heading towards the Rock Shrimp Tribe.

After getting along for a few days, Zhao Hai and Megan were now comfortable with each other. Although it still didn’t reach the level he had with Meg and Laura, it was still very good.

However, Zhao Hai was still indecisive about telling Megan about the Space. Megan’s situation was different than Laura and Meg. Laura had a falling out with her family and cannot return. Also, Meg had always been with him, so her loyalty was not an issue. Therefore, Zhao Hai can rest assured in telling them about the Space.

But Megan was different, standing behind her was a Great Noble Family. A family that ranked as one of the powerful families in the continent. Moreover, Megan still had a good relationship with her people. She was extremely favored by the family, so she still had deep sentiments towards it. If Zhao Hai tells Megan about the Space, then he was afraid that Megan would tell Smith if ever he asks. Then Zhao Hai’s biggest secret would be exposed to the outside world, and Zhao Hai didn’t want this to happen.

Megan didn’t feel anything, she was just sitting on the deck of the Haven. The ships stolen from the Markey family were right next to it.

Ever since she was young, this was the first time that she had gone out this far to sea. When Megan was still at the family, she mostly got along the river and rarely the sea. Additionally, the family didn’t include her in their businesses, so she was mostly just riding the boat near the coastlines. It was the first time that she got to travel such a long distance.

Two days after they left, Megan was still very excited. But on the third day, she became quite bored. In addition to the sea and the people on the boat, there was hardly anything to see.

Zhao Hai and the others were already used to Megan being on the ship, so they didn’t enter the Space during the day. They needed to wait until the evening before entering the Space. In the morning, they could only play around on the ship.

In reality, the ship was very big, so there were alot of things to play around with. But because Zhao Hai and the others were used to the ship, they just chatted peaceful while drinking some tea and eating, unknowingly making the days past by.

It was already the third day after they left Sky Water City. Megan was currently feeling boredom, she just stood on the deck, watching the sea silently with a frown on her face.

At this time, Laura saw Megan’s frown, she immediately walked over and asked, “Megan, why do you look so unhappy? Did you miss home?”

Megan turned to look at Laura and said “I don’t really miss home, it’s just that I’m feeling quite bored of the sea. We can only stay inside the ship, it’s too boring.”

Laura gave a smile and said, “We really have no other choice, this is how it is at sea. We still have seven days left of travel before we arrive at our destination.”

Megan rolled her eyes and said, “I’m afraid I won’t stay sane at that point. It’s terrible, I don’t think I would be able to endure the boredom.”

Laura smiled and said, “If you really can’t stand it anymore, just make something fun for yourself. There are books on the ship, we can also chat, you can learn how to cook. If that’s not enough we can fish. If you always think about boredom, then you will be really bored.”

Megan smiled and said, “Alright, then you should teach me well, I want to learn how to cook.”

Laura smiled and said, “We can’t right now, meal time isn’t here yet. Actually, it isn’t that boring sometimes. There were moments that we will come upon some pirates and might meet an attack. Those times were the most exciting. Ballistas firing arrows, Magic Cannons roaring, those really stimulate your senses.”

Megan smiled stiffly and said, “I really couldn’t understand how that could be interesting. I’d rather be bored that be attacked.”

Laura smiled, “Rest assured, I’m just talking about it. It isn’t necessary that something will happen. Especially since we have a five-masted armored shp, there weren’t a lot of pirates that would attack us. Pirates would generally attack three-masted ships.”

At this time, Zhao Hai walked over, he looked at the two and said,” What’s wrong? What are the two of you talking about?”

Zhao Hai also understood that Megan was probably unhappy. Actually, he wasn’t prepared to take Megan to the sea this time. But he didn’t have the means to decline her joining them. So he could only bring Megan along. He didn’t expect that Megan wouldn’t be able to adapt to life at sea, it has only been three days.

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Elder Brother Hai, aren’t you bored? There’s nothing at sea, only a few occasional seabirds passing by, or maybe a ship. Moreover, you have an undead crew, isn’t that more tiring?”

Chapter 425: Decision

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “A little bored, but there are advantages in having an undead crew as well. They will not betray you, they don’t need any salary, and moreover, they won’t bother us, isn’t that great?”

Megan pouted her mouth and said, “Is it really? Why couldn’t I see it? Elder Brother Hai, how about you tell me about your life. What happened to the Buda Clan after being being bestowed the Black Wasteland?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, a lot happened after the Buda Clan got sent to the Black Wasteland. But most of those matter were related to the Space. If he tells Megan about those experiences then he could only expose the Space. And Zhao Hai didn’t want to deceive Megan, so he didn’t know how to proceed from here.

When Laura saw Zhao Hai fall into an embarrassing situation, she inserted, “We can talk about those later. Megan, let’s go cook. We’ll have to let Brother Hai taste the meal that we create today. By the way, we need to call Meg, otherwise Brother Hai would be poisoned by us.”

Megan’s interest was piqued when she heard Laura. So she smiled and followed along. Then the four women ran towards the kitchen. When Zhao Hai saw the backs of the four he talked to Blockhead who was at his side, “Blockhead, what do you think? Should I tell Megan about the Space?”

Blockhead smiled and said, “That depends on the Young Master. But if you think about it, even if the Space were to be exposed, there were only a few powers in the continent that could still be a threat to us. With the numerous undead inside the Space, we have numerical advantage against anyone. If we really can’t endure, we can just escape to the Beastman Prairie.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, and said, “Your ambition isn’t small, but what you said is right. Right now, we don’t need to be afraid of anyone. And I also feel like I’ve been deceiving Megan, I feel sorry for her. Anyway, if I didn’t trust her, then I shouldn’t have gone and got engaged to her.”

Blockhead smiled and said, “I don’t really understand much about these things. Young Master can do it himself.”

Zhao Hai looked at Blockhead and smiled, “While we’re here, you and Rockhead are already quite old enough to get married. I’ll go discuss this with Grandpa Green. The both of you can’t just be single your whole life, you need a woman to look after you.”

When Blockhead heard Zhao Hai, his face couldn’t help but turn red as he said, “Young Master, you really do like to make jokes. I’m already quite happy serving the Young Master along with Stonehead.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Serving me and getting married are two different matters. You can get married and still serve me. It seems like I really do have to tell this to Grandpa Green.”

After the group had their lunch, they went on to have an afternoon nap. In the afternoon, Zhao Hai practiced his Battle QI and Fighting techniques on the ship. At the side, Meg was teaching Megan how to fight using Magic.

Although Megan was a 5th rank Water Mage, while also having good magical skills, her practical experience wasn’t good, so Meg went forward to guide her.

But Zhao Hai understands that this type of guidance can only take Megan so far. What she needed was actual combat experience. When comparing practice with actual combat, the atmosphere between the two was completely different. There were quite a lot of people who were very gifted in training but were complete dunces in the battlefield. They would get killed because they couldn’t adapt to the environment of the battlefield. They would become scared of the enemy’s charges, making their overall combat capability drop to about twenty percent. And this was fatal for a warrior.

In the evening when Megan had gone to sleep, Zhao Hai and the others went to the Space. Green and Kun were already waiting for them inside. After Zhao Hai practiced his martial arts, the group entered the living room to sit down. Then Zhao Hai turned to Green and said “Grandpa Green, I want to tell Megan about the Space.”

Green stared for a moment before he knit his brows, “Why did you suddenly mention this? In the past few days, you were sure that you wouldn’t tell her your secret, in fear that Smith and the Calci Family were to find out.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It’s true, if I tell Megan about the Space then the Calci Family might know. But if I don’t tell her, then I would feel that I may have been unfair. If I wouldn’t trust Megan, then I might as well have not agreed to the engagement. Upon thinking about it, I really do think that it is unfair to Megan.”

Green nodded, but didn’t say anything. At this point, Kun frowned and said, “Is it okay? If we do this, then we need to think about what will happen if the continent were to know. Including the Calci Family, there were also a lot of great powers in the continent who could take interest. You must know that there are endless greed in this world.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I also know that. But currently, we don’t need to fear the Calci Family’s strength. If we really cannot endure, we can just end them.”

When Green heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but knit his brows as he said, “In that case, we may become the enemy of the entire continent, then we won’t have any place inside it.”

Zhao Hai sighed, “I also know, but the continent places importance to strength. We are currently very strong, but now very known, making these small troubles arrive to us. But if we show off our strength, then wouldn’t they naturally disappear?”

Green knit his brows, obviously not in approval with Zhao Hai’s proposition. But he thought that Zhao Hai’s thinking was correct. If the Calci Family knew that they had the strength to contend against a 9th rank expert, then they might’ve not treated Zhao Hai like what they just did.”

However, Green still thought that this wasn’t a safe approach. The 9th ranks on their group were still very few. If they were to fight against all those people, then they can only be pushed back to the Black Wasteland.

At this time Kun said, “Little Hai, how about you take those 9th ranks back at the Carrion Swamp. We already have Cai’er and Zhao Wen on our side, so getting those other 9th ranks shouldn’t be too difficult. If we take them one by one, then we can slowly weaken their Flower Protection Alliance’s power, and eventually, they will all be taken over by us. After all, they are Magic Beasts, and if Magic Beats enters the Space, it will immediately take control over them. We wouldn’t even have to worry about them betraying us. If we have them on our hands, we can be on the same level as the Humans, Beastman, Merfold, Elves and the Dwarves, we would become a formidable existence on the continent.”

Zhao Hai froze, he didn’t think about this. Because they were always thinking about the Flower Protection Alliance, they actually forgot to take into consideration that those Magic Beasts have their own respective domains, rarely coming in contact with the others. If Zhao Hai caan subdue those 9th ranks, then his strength would immediately be risen to among the top of the continent.

Green’s eyes also lit up, “If this is the case, then we could definitely do it. However, now’s not the time. We must wait until afterwards. Right, Young Master, I think you can tell Megan about the Space. But you have to make her promise to not divulge it to any other person no matter what.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Grandpa Green, another matter, it’s about Blockhead and Rockhead. They aren’t that young anymore, how about setting them up to get married? There is also Shue. I think we should find them a companion. They can’t serve me while being unmarried forever, wouldn’t that be unfair to them?”

Green didn’t say anything, it was Merine who smiled and said, “Right, Young Master’s idea is quite good. The two boys, Blockhead and Rockhead, should have a family. Shue even more so. They should get married.”

Blockhead and Rockhead’s faces looked like boiled shrimp, their necks were red as well. But Shue was very calm, he turned to Zhao Hai and Merine and said, “I thank the Young Master and Madam Merine for the good intentions, but I’ve already made an oath to never marry in my entire life.”

Zhao Hai stared at Shue for a moment before he nodded gently. He didn’t talk anymore. He knew the Shue might have his own reasons. He was also afraid that he might’ve made Shue recall a painful experience.

Merine didn’t ask further, but she still looked at Shue and sighed, “Alright, you’re free to have own reasons. But Young Master, I think you need to talk to Megan about the Space tomorrow. It’s just like you said, since you’re now engaged to Megan, then you should trust her, otherwise you would be unfair to her.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to Laura and Meg and said, “Laura, Meg, are you fine with this? I felt that If I leave Megan out of the Space’s matter, then I might have been deceiving her.”

Laura smiled and said, “Of course we’re fine. Brother Hai, you don’t know but we have long wanted to tell you about this matter. If we discuss sentiment, our feelings towards Megan is comparatively better than yours.”

Zhao Hai cannot help but laugh, “If you say so, then I’m relieved. Actually, I’m quite fortunate that I have the favor of you girls. And since you all were taking care of me, then I want all of you to see each other equally. I hope that all of you gets along with each other, otherwise my Buda Family wouldn’t have a great future.”

Laura smiled and said, “Be relieved, we wouldn’t struggle with each other. But if you prefer one of us, then all of us won’t be happy, we are now one group.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh even louder, Green and the others also laughed. To be honest, with Megan’s engagement to Zhao Hai, Green was afraid that Laura and Meg would have some misgivings. If Zhao Hai’s backyard was on fire, then their Buda Family wouldn’t fare very well.

Kun sighed inside, he knew that Laura loves Zhao Hai very much. Otherwise, she wouldn’t have such considerations for him. But Kun also knew that Zhao Hai is very happy with Laura. There’s no decision that he wouldn’t discuss with her. Kun could even say that Zhao Hai’s feelings for Laura was the same as Laura’s feelings for him.

Chapter 426: Hot Spring

The next morning, Megan woke up early. Although she had been on the sea for four days, she was still unfamiliar with sleeping on the ship. This made her rests each day quite unpractical.

.This was also the reason why Megan’s mood was not very good these days. If one was not well rested, then their temperament wouldn’t be good. It was precisely because of this that Megan had been very depressed in the past days.

After washing up, Megan went out of the cabin. She thought of breathing in the sea breeze outside. This time, she went out of her house without bringing any servants along with her. But Megan wasn’t regretful, since she was going to marry Zhao Hai, then she must be familiar with his lifestyle, she doesn’t want Zhao Hai to see her as a young lady that need servants all the time to help her.

When Megan arrived on the deck, she saw that Zhao Hai and Laura were already up. Megan quickly went forwards and embarrassingly said, “Big Brother Hai, Sister Laura, you’re all up. I’m sorry I woke up late.”

Zhao Hai turned to Megan and saw that there were dark circles around her eyes, he couldn’t help but feel very apologetic towards her. He smiled and said, “What’s wrong? Not sleeping very well? This is normal for newcomers at sea, always feeling sick because of the swaying and shaking. Hehe.”

Megan smiled stiffly and said, “I really don’t know. I’ve already been used to the swaying since I was young. But I think If I still stayed here when I was young, I would still get sick.” This caused Laura and Zhao Hai to laugh.

Megan also laughed, although she underwent hardship and suffered a bit over the past two days, she also learned a lot from Zhao Hai’s group. They were hard-working, persevering, and optimistic. It was because of this that she can still joke about at this point.

Now Megan understood the thing about Zhao Hai that attracts her, it was his spirit of optimism. No matter what happens, Zhao Hai was still optimistic. The most important thing about Zhao Hai was that he strives to move forward no matter what happens, this seemed to be attractive to her.

While looking at Megan’s face, Zhao Hai calmed down. He looked at Megan and sternly said, “Megan, now that we’re engaged, you’ll be a person of my Buda Clan in the future. Because of this, I’ll tell you our Buda Clan’s greatest secret. I hope you keep this secret, even from your father, can you do it?”

When Megan heard Zhao Hai’s first couple of words, she felt her face turn hot. But as soon as she heard the last ones, she froze and looked at Zhao Hai, but she didn’t agree immediately.

She quietly thought about Zhao Hai’s words. Yes, she was now engaged to Zhao Hai. And although they hadn’t been married, the matter was already set. She will become a person of the Buda Clan, no matter what others thought about it, and it was also not in her mind to leave Zhao Hai.

However, she also needed to take her parents into account, which made it difficult for her. Her feelings for Smith and the madam was too deep. So if she wanted to keep a secret from her mother and father, she was afraid that she would be unable to do it.

Seeing that Megan didn’t answer immediately, Zhao Hai didn’t become angry. On the contrary, he was quite glad that Megan didn’t quickly agree. I meant that she held relationships as important, and it also showed that her feelings for Zhao Hai were genuine. Otherwise, Megan could just agree immediately and when she returns, she could just sell Zhao Hai out.

Zhao Hai looked at Megan and said, “Megan, you must know that this secret is known by Laura, also Meg, all of the people from my Buda Clan knows. Since you’ve become engaged to me, I hope that you will have the same status as Laura and Meg. Otherwise, it would be unfair for you. At the same time, I completely believe in you, if I didn’t, then it wouldn’t be good in the future if you marry me. I hope you can take these words into account as well.”

When Megan heard Zhao Hai, she understood that Zhao Hai hoped for her to reach the same status as Laura. This also meant that in his heart, she held the same place as Laura and Meg. This fact made Megan happy, she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, you can rest assured, if you trust me that much, then I wouldn’t disappoint you. I will protect the Buda Clan’s secret, even from my mother and father.”

Zhao Hai looked at Megan’s face then laughed, “Alright, I already feel relieved from hearing your words. Are you prepared? Because you will now know about the biggest secret of the Buda Clan.”

Megan took a deep breath and said, “I’m ready.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and made an intention on his mind. Megan felt a flash of white light before she appeared in front of the villa.

Megan looked at everything in front of her and thought that she must have been in the Prairie. All around were green grass, and not far from the villa was a cultivated land where various plants were planted. But most importantly, she didn’t know how they arrived here, weren’t they on the ship just now?

At this time, Meg came and opened the door to the villa. As soon as she saw Megan, she smiled and said, “Megan, you’re here? Come in quickly, breakfast is already prepared. We can talk while eating at the same time.”

Megan’s mind was hazy as Meg pulled her into the villa. When they arrived at the dining doom, Meg didn’t serve the dishes immediately, they waited before Shue and the others came and also sat down.

This was Zhao Hai’s custom. When there was no special event, Shue and the others would dine with him, chatting on the table, increasing their sentiment to each other. Although they were under the Blood Oath, and were not allowed to betray Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai didn’t want to depend on the Blood Oath for their loyalty. He hoped that Shue and the others would sincerely work for him

Megan was still hazy when she sat down, she was very puzzled seeing all of this. The villa was just fine for her, but the environment made her very confused.

At this time, Zhao Hai also sat down and smiled, “Megan, this is our Bida Clan’s greatest secret, Um, Laura, go introduce Megan to the Space.”

Laura didn’t object, she smiled faintly and talked to Megan about the Space along with its various mystical properties.

Megan already forgot to eat as she just stared and listened to Laura telling everything about the myriad magical things that was in the Space. Laura also kept talking for about one hour, at this point, Zhao Hai and the others were already finished eating. The only people who have not yet eaten were Laura and Megan.

When Laura finished, Megan couldn’t believe it as she looked outside the window and said, “You mean this entire place belonged to Brother Hai? In here, Brother Hai is a god?”

Laura smiled and said, “It’s just like what you said, everything here belongs to Brother Hai. And even if he is a god here, he is a miserable god, why? It’s because he needs to pay the Space for everything, also he needs to upgrade the space, otherwise he wouldn’t be able to use its full potential.”

Megan didn’t understand so much about it, but she still muttered, “Everything here surprisingly belongs to Brother Hai, amazing, this is too amazing.”

Seeing her appearance, Laura didn’t say anything and just faintly smiled. She went to the kitchen to warm their meal. She had to, otherwise they wouldn’t be able to eat it.

After some time, Megan recovered. Currently, it was only her who was left inside the dining room. Laura was busy in the kitchen while Zhao Hai and the others were in the living room.

Megan didn’t head to the living room, but instead she went to the kitchen. She asked Laura about the questions she had about the Space. Laura was also patient in answering them all. Soon after, their meals were already prepared, then the two went to the dining room to eat. After the meal, they went to the living room and saw Zhao Hai and the others looking at the monitor. The screen displayed the state of the sea.

As the various images popped out of the monitor, Megan was again reminded of the various mysteries of the Space. Zhao Hai looked at her and faintly smiled, “Megan, is Laura done in telling you about the Space? This is our Buda Clan’s ace, right, you should know about the good things i have right? Those were outputs of the Space, hehe, I can say that without the Space, you wouldn’t be able to meet me.”

Megan nodded at Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, rest assured, I will certainly not mention the Space to anybody.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “Very well, I believe you. Megan, I know that you haven’t been resting properly these days, you can go sleep inside the Space. I’ll let Laura and Meg accompany you. The ship can just sail without us outside, but I still can’t feel at ease.”

Laura also said, “That’s right, we haven’t had a good rest these days either, so let’s sleep here. Megan, let’s go and take a rest.” Then she pulled Megan and left.

Zhao Hai also lead Blockhead and the others outside the Space, leaving the girls alone. The women didn’t immediately go to bed, they took Megan to have a good bath first. There was a hot spring spool in the Space, they can just bathe there and relax.

The hot spring of the Space was placed underneath the villa, which was Karen’s former laboratory before he moved to Iron Mountain Fort. Since the basement was not used, Laura proposed to Cai’er her intent to make the basement into a Hot Spring pool. The pool was supplied with flowing water since there was a spring underneath the villa. At the same time, there was also an outlet on the pool, since it was hard to control the amount of water inside the basement.

In the basement, there weren’t only some stone tables and other furnitures, Cai’er can also send some fruits and wine for Laura and the others to enjoy. After the basement was prepared, it was very well regarded by the group. Afterwards, Zhao Hai proposed dividing the place into two rooms, one for the women, then the other one is for men. [1]

* * *

Zhao Hai, a.k.a. The enemy of men. ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)

Chapter 427: Trade

Megan sat in the hot spring pool and felt an unprecedented sense of comfort. This was her first time experiencing a hot spring ever. Sky Water City was on a coastal region, there were no hot springs available there.

Soaking in hot water inside the spring made her feel really good, it was very comfortable. Sitting in the hot spring while eating fruits and drinking wine was something she thought only fairies could do.

After taking her wine glass and taking a sip, Megan turned her head towards Laura and Meg who were also soaking in the hot spring while sipping wine. Megan made a discontented pout and said, “You two are really good sisters, enjoying such good stuff these days but only telling me now, hmph.”

Laura and Meg both laughed, after which Laura said, “It’s not that we don’t want to tell you, this place is just too important to the Buda Clan. If this secret were to be known by others, the Clan’s final trump card would be gone, so we dared not to tell you immediately. We only told you this time because of Brother Hai’s proposal.” Although Laura also wanted to tell Zhao Hai to inform Megan about the Space, she didn’t say it. No matter what, it was Zhao Hai’s decision. Moreover, she also said that to make Megan’s impression of Zhao Hai better, to make Megan’s heart accept Zhao Hai more.

One had to recognize how much Laura thought about Zhao Hai, even such small details were taken into consideration. This was because Laura knew that since she wanted to spend her lifetime with this man, it would help him if she solves all of his troubles. So Laura decided to think about such matters.

When Megan heard Laura, she snorted, “I forgive you. I’ll never tell anyone about this, be relieved .This place really is too good, you’ll really enjoy it here.”

Laura smiled and said, “It really is. Actually some of those things were Brother Hai’s ideas, he just couldn’t come enjoy them, he has too many things to do, he is too busy.”

Megan also sighed, she also saw how much things Zhao Hai handled these past few days. Although Zhao Hai was not signing documents like her father, Zhao Hai also had a lot of matters regarding the Buda Clan to think about. Just like Laura said, Zhao Hai was indeed very busy.

After the group soaked at the hot springs for a while, they then went to rest upstairs. There were more than 20 rooms in the Space’s villa, so there were still plenty of empty rooms. Since Megan had not rested well lately, she immediately fell asleep after the hot spring bath.

She didn’t think that she would fall asleep until the afternoon. When she got out of bed, there weren’t any other person inside the Space. After she wore her clothes, Megan immediately appeared on the Haven.

She stared for a moment before she understood that it was certainly Cai’er’s doing. Zhao Hai already introduced Megan to Cai’er yesterday. But Zhao Hai didn’t tell Megan that Cai’er was in fact a 9th rank expert.

When Megan arrived on the ship, Laura saw her. Laura immediately went and greeted her with a smile, “You woke up. Seeing you sleep so much during the day makes me think whether you can still be able to sleep at night.”

Megan spat out her tongue and said, “I haven’t slept well these past few days, so I had a very good rest. But I surprisingly overslept. Haha.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “We can just return to the Space in the night and rest. It’s quiet there, and the air is very good as well. Sleeping there is very comfortable.”

Megan nodded and looked at the scenery of the sea. She smiled and said, “Looking at the grass inside the Space, while gazing at the sea on the ship, this lifestyle is very good.” Her words made Zhao Hai and the others smile.

After some time, Megan turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, what are we doing on this trip? Why do I see that we’re heading towards the deep seas? Do you intend to go there?”

Zhai Hai smiled faintly and said, “Right, we’ll head towards the deeps seas, as well as Ape Island, we have a base there.”

When Megan was reading a few days ago, she also came across information regarding Ape Island. So upon hearing Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but be startled as she said, “Ape Island? Isn’t that the one written in the book that had reefs surrounding it as well as strong magic beasts?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Yes, that Ape Island. We’ve already subdued the magic beasts there. One of them is called Little Jin, I’m sure you’re going to like him. Moreover, that island is rich in Bread Fruits.”

Megan also knew about the Bread Fruit, she had eaten several of them. She didn’t think that the fruit was grown inside that ominous island.

After several days, Zhao Hai and the others finally arrived at Ape Island. Upon arriving, Little Jin’s group received Zhao Hai and the others. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on staying long this time. He stayed for two days and then they left, but this time Little Jin joined them. Zhao Hai didn’t oppose it, after all, there’s a transmission point inside Ape Island, Little Jin can just return anytime.

Megan also came to like Little Jin very much. Although Zhao Hai and the others told her that Little Jin was formidable, Megan just can’t see it just by looking at its face. She didn’t really believe that Little Jin was as scary as what the others said,

After leaving Ape Island, Zhao Hai’s group naturally headed to trade with the Rock Shrimp Tribe. Zhao Hai also told Megan about this, which made her shocked, she didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be trading with the Merfolk.

Keeping this as a secret was also tol to Megan. Even if they can cooperate with the Calci Family about marine products later on, they cannot tell the family about their transactions with the Rock Shrimp Tribe.

Megan didn’t oppose, ever since Zhao Hai revealed the Space to Megan, she already classified herself as someone from the Buda Clan. What she needed to do right now was to contribute into developing the clan. Not saying Zhao Hai’s matter wouldn’t affect the Calci Family’s benefits anyway. Conversely, if she cooperates, the Calci Family would be obtaining a lot of advantages in the future.

Megan’s transformation was also in small part the Space’s doing. Although the Space’s influence on a person was very minimal, almost nothing, ever since Megan started to stay inside the Space every evening, she changed bit by bit.

Naturally, this influence on a person was very limited, so Zhao Hai didn’t really care about this point. Before long, they arrived at the Shrimp Tribe’s domain. The tribesmen immediately came to meet them and escorted them to the reef where the tribe lived.

But when Zhao Hai arrived, he was shaken, this was because it was not only the Shrimp Tribe that was trading with him, there were also the Crabs and the Shellfishes. The deals with the two tribes were also very beneficial to Zhao Hai. There was needless to say about the Shell Tribe, since they were the ones who had the pearls. But the Crab Tribe also traded Zhao Hai with crab magic beasts. These crabs were really very big, if they were placed on the ground with their claws outstretched, their length would be about ten meters.

Altogether, what Zhao Hai gained from the trade this time were 100 jins of pearl, 100 corals, 200 gigantic crabs, 100 giant shrimps, as well as various marine plants and other Magic Beasts. One could say that Zhao Hai’s harvests were very great.

Moreover, Libben also told Zhao Hai that he was still contacting other tribes to see who wanted to trade with Zhao Hai. Naturally, Zhao Hai was extremely glad about this, so he gave the Shrimp Tribe some Bread Fruits as well as some Milk Wine. As to whether how they will drink the liquor, it wasn’t under Zhao Hai’s worries.

When Zhao Hai left the Shrimp Tribe’s area and headed towards the shallower sea, Megan couldn’t help but release a breath. She looked at the Shrimp Tribe’s territory and turned to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, aren’t you scared when seeing those Shrimp and Crap Tribesmen?”

Zhao Hai already saw Shrimp Tribesmen from before. Now, he saw the Crab Tribesmen. Their upper bodies were vaguely similar to the Shrimps, but they didn’t have as many arms like them, the Crabs were just like humans. However, their eyes were not normal since they stretched outwards their heads, they may even turn them 360 degrees to see all around their body. Their arms were like the humans, but their hands were replaced with huge claws. Their lower body had crab-like feet, they also had large shells. One could say that the Crab Tribesmen just looked like a long crab with half a human’s body.

On the other hand, the Shell Tribesmen were very much like humans. But on their backs were a pair of wing-like shells. The shell was quite huge, as long as a Shell Tribesman curls their body, they could fit themselves inside their shells. When Zhao Hai saw the appearance of the Shell people, he couldn’t help but think about Shell Girl. However, the Shell Tribesmen weren’t very beautiful.

It was because of the odd and strange appearances of the Merfolk that Megan asked Zhao Hai that question. He just smiled and said, “Why should we be afraid? They are also creatures who had wisdom no lesser than our own. They just had appearances that appear strange to us, just like how us humans look strange to them. Megan, you have to remember this as a future senior member of the Buda Clan, you must be good if you meet different races. The most hated thing for these races are when Humans look down on their appearances. Therefore, even if you do fear them, don’t show it. An expression of fear or loathing will enrage them, they might even possibly go out and attack you.”

Megan stared, then she turned to Laura. Laura smiled and said, “In a few days, we will lead you to Iron Mountain Fort. There, you will be able to see some Giant-Horned Ox Clansmen. They are huge, with giant horns. We felt strange when we saw them for the first time, but give it some days and you will get used to it. You would be getting along with them and see that they are much more easy to interact with than other humans.”

Although they already told Megan about the transmission points, Zhao Hai still hadn’t brought Megan to Iron Mountain Fort. He just invited Green and the others to the Space to meet Megan.

Chapter 428: Raise the Banner of the Wild Dragon, Show them Who is Invincible!

When Megan knew that she was going to meet Green, she was very anxious. From what she heard from Laura, Green was Meg’s grandfather, the Buda Clan’s housekeeper. He also looked after Zhao Hai while he was growing up, Green was no different from Zhao Hai’s blood grandfather. Although Green still called Zhao Hai Young Master, Zhao Hai was extremely respectful to him. To get the recognition from the Buda Family, Grandpa Green’s approval was required.

This made Megan nervous. When she saw Green, she didn’t know what to speak, this made Green and Merine very amused.

At this point, Megan knew that Laura was just teasing her and chased her around for a long time. However, as a result, this made Megan look better in the eyes of the elders, and in the end she got Green’s recognition.

These past few days, Zhao Hai had been busy sailing. So he didn’t have the time to bring Megan back to Iron Mountain Fort. He just waited for a proper time before going back.

And now, when Megan heard Laura, she became very curious. She had known about Iron Mountain Fort for quite some time, but Laura and the others didn’t talk much about it. She just knew that the Milk Wine that was very in demand in the continent was produced in the fort, this made her want to take a look at the place.

But Zhao Hai really didn’t have much time to return to the fort. So Megan had no other choice but to wait. Now that they’re on their return trip, there was now a lot of spare time, naturally it was also time to go back to the fort and take a look.

Just as Megan was about to ask Zhao Hai as to when he plans to take her to Iron Mountain fort, a hawk’s sound was suddenly heard. Zhao Hai turned his head and saw that it was coming from a Blood Hawk, but he didn’t know where this one came from. So he immediately called it down and took the letter attached on its body. When Zhao Hai read the letter, his expression sank.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and knew that something important just happened. She quickly asked, “What is is Brother Hai? Did an accident happen?”

Zhao Hai handed the letter off to Laura, which made Laura’s calm face change. She muttered, “It’s surprisingly Uncle Evan, 200 thousand mercenaries? How is this possible? Are they fools?”

Meg looked puzzled at Laura, “Sister Laura, what happened?”

Laura gave the letter to Meg, “The letter is from Uncle Evan, he said that Casa City is suddenly besieged by 100 thousand mercenaries. There was also another 100 thousand outside the city’s vicinity to block reinforcements for the Purcell Family. Currently, Casa City is receiving no help, it will be broken into in five days.”

Although Megan didn’t read the letter, she stared blankly just by listening to Laura’s words. Even if she wasn’t an expert in military, hearing about 200 thousand mercenaries made her feel the absurdity of the situation, are the mercenaries crazy? 200 thousand mercenaries actually grouped up to attach a duchy? This was something a military would do, Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, which extraordinary person did the Purcell Family offend? Otherwise, why would so many mercenaries attack them? 200 thousand mercenaries, even if people who didn’t understand militaires would definitely think that they are just soldiers in disguise.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It should be Southern King Boris. Back when Ruyen was heading home, Southern King acted against her, but was saved by the Swordfish Ship that I had sent. And now that Ruyen came home safely, it seems like Boris wants to extinguish the Purcell Family.”

Laura turned to look at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what do you want to do?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “We’ll go discuss this with Grandpa Green as well as Uncle Smith. Both of them are veterans in politics, they should have good inputs on this matter. As for the fleet, let them head towards Jade Water City. Let Mu’en handle this matter.”

Laura nodded, “Mu’en can deal with it, in any case, he only needs to hand them over to Trezebo. We should indeed ask Grandpa Green’s advice, however, he had minimum contact with the outside world lately. I think Uncle Smith’s input is very valuable this time.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he immediately gave the Ghost Staff over to a Blood Hawk before sending it flying towards Sky Water City. At the same time, he had the five-masted ships gotten from the Markey Family to head to Jade Water City. He also left the traded items behind as well as an undead Water Mage to freeze the goods over. After that, everyone went to the Space and returned to Iron Mountain Fort.

Megan didn’t think that this would be the reason why she could go to Iron Mountain Fort. After arriving at the fort, Zhao Hai had Meg take Megan to walk around and see the place. Zhao Hai found Green and the others in the living room, then he told them about Evan’s matter.

Green frowned and said, “Of course we need to help, but if we do, then wouldn’t we be exposing our status?”

Zhao Hai snorted and said, “If we get exposed, then we get exposed. We happen to be looking for an opportunity to do so. It’s time to let the continent know that the Buda Clan has risen back. Grandpa Green, it seems like our Buda Clan’s Wild Dragon Banner hadn’t been shown in the continent for quite some time, should we take it?”

Green stared blankly before he stood up and laughed. From his body an intense killing aura, only those who experienced the battlefield would have, appeared, making the temperature in the room decrease by a several degrees.

Green turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, have you really decided?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ve decided. Our Wild Dragon Banner must return to the face of the continent. Let people know that our Buda Clan is back.”

Green laughed, “Alright, the Wild Dragon Banner needs to be inherited, one day it would land in your hands. Now that the strength of our Buda Clan has increased, I think it’s time for the Young Master to receive it. Young Master, please wait, I’ll go bring it right away.”

Before long, Green arrived while carrying a neatly folded scarlet coth. When he arrived at the living room, he unfolded his hands and revealed the banner.

The banner was 2 meters high by 4 meters wide, fully red, and embroidered with a clawed dragon. This wasn’t a Chinese dragon, but a Western dragon with wings. But the embroidery was quite abstract, the dragon was drawn on its side, along with some fire coming out of its mouth.

However, what made Laura and the others surprised was that the banner looked a bit tattered. A hole was even present on the middle of it, but not damaging the dragon image. On the contrary the hole was lined with gold thread, making it glitter.

Zhao Hai was excited while looking at this banner, from the memories he obtained from Adam, he knew the significance of this banner. This was a War Banner of the Buda Clan’s First Patriarch. The banner itself was made with the most common red fabric, the dragon was also embroidered with ordinary yellow thread. However, during a battle, the First Patriarch was seriously injured while the flag was heavily damaged. The First Patriarch picked up the banner and wrapped it around his body, and struggled to survive while wearing it. In the end, they won the battle, and the banner was soaked with the blood of the family, making it even more scarlet red.

Afterwards, the Aksu Empire’s Emperor personally assigned someone to use fire silk to fix the banner as well as use gold threads to redraw the dragon before giving it back to the Buda Clan. The Clan then continually used the banner for several wars and battles, even though the the cloth and the silk were getting damaged, the Clan never changed the banner. Finally, when they left Aksu Empire’s capital, Green sold all of their things aside from the Clan’s banner. This banner could be said to be the spirit of the Buda Clan.

Green looked at the War Banner and turned to Zhao Hai, “Young Master, this Banner represents the honor of our Buda Clan. Today, I bestow this banner to you. I hope you take the Clan’s honor into heart. And most importantly, you must wave this banner in front of the Continent and let them know who is truly invincible!”

He said before handing the banner over to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai received the banner and solemnly nodded, “Grandpa Green, be relieved. I will certainly ingrain the image of this banner onto the eyes of everyone in the continent, I promise!”

Green laughed, and at the same time, tears flowed down his face. More than a year, it was more than a year before the Buda Clan had been relocated. Ever since being relocated, Green had always hoped that the banner could re-emerge into the continent. Now that the opportunity has arrived, the continent would have to know, that the Buda Clan is back!”

Meg and Merine were also silently shedding tears on the side. After experiencing everything, the banner had finally been handed over to Zhao Hai, and he even appeared very noble while doing so.

Zhao Hai turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, I’ll go now. SInce the Buda Clan is going to reappear on the continent, do you have any other advice?”

Green looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I only have a few words. You must express the power and prestige of this flag, you cannot discredit this flag.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he folded the flag before sending it to the Space. But as the War Banner entered the Space, a prompt was unexpectedly heard, “Inheritance-type Special Item detected. Item can only be passed from generation to generation. Added to spirit department, special item class. This item can be used in battle, bound to the host, cannot be damaged, cannot be dropped. Can enhance soldiers, and increase host’s leadership ability. Increases the Host’s influence, loyalty of subordinates to the host increased. Also increases the Space’s attack power.”

Zhao Hai froze, he didn’t expect the banner to be very special. He quickly told Green about this development.

After listening, Green laughed, “Good! The Space is truly made for the young master, it actually recognizes the family’s treasure. This would be a great help to the Young Master. Right, the Young Master should leave. Don’t hesitate to approach us if you ever need anything.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he led Laura and the others to return to the Space. After looking at the monitor, they saw the blood hawk quickly flying towards Sky Water City. Then he shifted to the Haven, and upon seeing that there were no other ships in the vicinity, he immediately stored the ship into the Space.

The group sat in the living room and looked carefully at the screen. Laura sat beside Zhao Hai and gently said, “Brother Hai, this time if we use the Buda Clan’s War Banner, will those people shift their attention to the Black Wasteland? What do we do if they send some people over to investigate?”

Zhao Hai who was looking at the screen snorted, “They can come, but they won’t be able to return. This time I’ve planned let out 10 thousand creatures for the attack, too much is no good. The rest of the undead, about 100 thousand, will be left behind the Black Wasteland. And with Cai’er, even if they send in a 9th rank, they wouldn’t be able to leave.”

Laura didn’t oppose and just asked again, “Isn’t 10 thousand too few?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “10 thousand is already a lot. There are several Dark Mages who can command 10 thousand undead to battle. For me to dominate with these 10 thousand could already shake some people.”

Laura nodded, and then said, “Alright, 10 thousand is enough. We can also turn those we attack into undead, this way, nobody would get suspicious.”

Zhao Hai nodded, at this time the Blood Hawk arrived outside Sky Water City. Zhao Hai and the others immediately flashed out of the Space and then rode horses directly towards the City Lord’s Mansion.

Zhao Hai repeated his movements from before and sent a Blood Hawk to inform Smith about his arrival.

…

It was already afternoon, Smith and Randolph were in the living room talking about Zhao Hai. Megan had already been gone for ten days, they were now worried.

At this time, a hawk’s cry came. When Smith heard this, he knew that it must be the Blood Hawk. He immediately had someone go out and retrieve the letter from the Hawk. After reading the letter, Smith quickly had Phil go to the side entrance and receive Zhao Hai. At the same time, he also returned to the living room and said to Randolph, “Father, Little Hai and Megan’s group had come back. But this time it seems like they came with an important matter, they seem to be anxious.”

Randolph knitted his brows and said, “What could it be? Alright, we’ll just wait for them here. For them to return this soon, they must have something they needed to discuss with you.”

Smith nodded, at this time Zhao Hai’s group arrived at the side entrance and was greeted by Phil, “Mister, Miss, you’re already back? Come in, the Patriarch is waiting.”

Thunder seemed to erupt in Zhao Hai’s mind as he heard Phil’s words. But no matter what, he had to meet this man from the Calci Family, so he didn’t say anything. However, Megan’s face changed, “Grandpa is here? Does Grandpa oppose my engagement with Big Brother Hai? Grandpa Phil, what did Grandpa say?”

Phil smiled and said, “Young Lady need not worry, the Patriarch already agreed to your engagement. Now, the City Lord and the Patriarch are waiting in the living room, come in quickly.”

Megan relaxed her uneasy expression, she was really worried that Randolph would stop her engagement with Zhao Hai.

Chapter 429: Primary Interest

Zhao Hai and the others headed towards the living room with Phil. They saw that Smith was already standing outside the door, so Zhao Hai gave a bow and said, “Uncle Smith”

Because they still hadn’t married, and adding on to the customs of Great Nobles, Zhao Hai can only call him Uncle Smith right now.

Smith nodded and said, “Alright, let’s enter the room and meet Megan’s Grandfather. Megan hurry up, your grandpa has already waiting for you for several days.”

Megan nodded and ran into the room. Zhao Hai then went along with Smith as they slowly entered. When Zhao Hai entered the living room, he saw Megan sitting on an old man and acting like a spoiled brat.

The man looked very old, having hair that was somewhat grayish white, but it was extremely well kept. He wore a stern face and most importantly, he had an imposing aura about him. Comparing this aura to Smith, one could see that he held a much higher standing than the City Lord.

Smith turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, this is Megan’s Grandfather.”

Zhao Hai immediately went forward and bowed, “Zhao Hai has seen Grandpa Patriarch.”

Randolph nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was already experienced with this situation, so he just calmly stood there, returning Randolph’s gaze.

Then with a deep voice, Randolph said, “Sit”. Zhao Hai complied and sat down. Randolph didn’t speak again, and just looked at Zhao Hai. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood for this right now, so he turned to Smith and said, “Uncle Smith, I have a matter to discuss with you today.”

Smith stared at Zhao Hai and said, “What matter?”

Then Zhao Hai told Smith about the Purcell Family’s situation, and then expressed his intention to provide help. Smith and Randolph both frowned while listening to Zhao Hai’s words. After waiting for Zhao Hai to finish, Smith looked at him and said, “Do you really want to help? Moreover, you will use the Buda Clan’s Banner?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I do, and I’m capable of helping them. Moreover, the Purcell Family had given some grace to our Buda Clan. Even if the Purcell family is an established noble of the Aksu Empire, they still chose to give aid to my Clan.”

Without even waiting for Smith to speak, Randolph opened his mouth and said, “You should go and help them. You would be using your undead right?”

Zhao Hai nodded, and was confused as he stared at Randolph. When he entered the room, he could see that Randolph was somewhat upset with him. He knew the old man wasn’t very happy to speak to him. But he didn’t think that Randolph would actually support his decision.

Randolph didn’t stare at Zhao Hai for a long time. He opened his mouth and continued, “Since there hadn’t been any major battles in the continent these past years, we Dark Mages barely had any opportunity to show our might. This made people forget about how formidable the undeads of our profession were. If you help the Purcell Family this time, you would surely need to use your undead, you could also make use of this situation to show the continent how fearful a Dark Mage was inside a battlefield. Therefore, not only do you need to endure, you should win, and make sure that it’s an overwhelming victory. You must express the might and power of a Dark Mage.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but Smith said, “I’ve heard about this matter, I think the 200 thousand mercenaries are only used to deceive people. When other people see it, they would understand what’s going on. However, this matter was well thought out, from what I’ve got, the other side wasn’t very violent towards Casa City. I think they might have been waiting for you to appear. As long as you go, they would then immediately deal with you. You wouldn’t fare well if they send a 9th rank expert, are you really confident?”

When Zhao Hai heard Smith, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he asked, “The really came for me?”

Smith nodded and said, “I’m not sure of it in the beginning, but now that you came, I think that this is the case. They don’t know your true identity, but they know of Zhao Hai the Dark Mage. And you as a Dark Mage seem to be secretly related to the Purcell Family. In addition to the time when you saved Ruyen some time ago, they reckoned that you will also help Casa City. Therefore, they decided to attack the Purcell Family in hopes that you would come, and then have an expert come and deal with you as well as the Purcell Family. As the matter stands, your enemy can stand to gain great things with this operation.”

Zhao Hai frowned, “Southern King really has this much influence in Aksu Empire? I didn’t expect this, would the other nobles of the Aksu Empire just ignore it?”

Smith shook his head and said, “It is very likely that Southern King had paid a hefty price so that the Great Nobles would choose to ignore this matter. But it is certain that Southern King cannot hold out for too long, and they would also keep the damages to a minimum. And similarly, they wouldn’t act against other people, only the Purcell Family and you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and in a serious voice he said, “This is also good. This way, I can beat them once and make them unable to dare to come again. Rest assured, as long as they don’t send five 9th ranks, they will not be able to return from where they came from.”

Hearing this, Smith knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t joking before. When Randolph heard Zhao Hai, his eyes couldn’t help but narrow.

In the past they didn’t believe Zhao Hai’s words, since Zhao Hai said that he was from the Buda Clan, they knew that the demise of the Clan was in large part because of their lack of 9th rank experts. However, now, Zhao Hai actually said that they wouldn’t be able to return if they don’t send five 9th ranks. This meant that four 9th ranks wasn’t a match against this young man.

One must know that in order to deal with four 9th ranks, one would generally need seven to eight 9th ranks to make sure. Otherwise, it would be impossible to entrap the other party. How could the Buda Clan have this much 9th ranks.

However, now that Zhao Hai said this, they thought that maybe he wasn’t lying. Since Zhao Hai wanted to support the Purcell Family immediately, then if he wasn’t confident with dealing with 9th ranks, then there was no point in telling this.

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and knew that he was already det on going, he just nodded and said, “When do you plan to leave?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Right now. This time, Megan wouldn’t need to come with me, it’s too dangerous. We need to head out immediately, the Purcell Family couldn’t hold out for long.”

Smith nodded and stared at Zhao Hai, “Do you need our family to send you support? In any case, you’re now engaged to Megan, this is also somewhat related to our Calci Family.”

Randolph also nodded, “Since you became engaged to Megan, I don’t hope for you to get in danger. Boy, will you really go on your own?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Me alone is enough, Uncle Smith, Grandpa Patriarch, I’ll be taking my leave,” Then he gave a bow before heading out.

At this time, Megan said, “Wait! Brother Hai, I’ll go with you.”

Zhao Hai stared, then frowned, “Megan, it’s fine, we’re heading off to war. Although you wouldn’t be in relative danger, I think you wouldn’t be able to stomach the scene.”

Smith and Randolph also frowned, “Right, Megan, you should stay at home. You can’t contribute anything if you go.”

Megan actually shook her head and said, “No, I must go with Brother Hai. You must let me go.”

Zhao Hai looked at Megan’s appearance and didn’t know what to do. At this time, Laura’s voice was heard, “Brother Hai, you should let Megan come. After all, she wouldn’t be in any danger.”

Seeing the resoluteness in Megan’s face, to the point of shedding tears, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but soften and said, “Alright, you can come.”

Smith’s complexion changed and said, “Little Hai, are you really confident? If Megan gets injured, I will never forgive you.” Smith also knew Megan’s disposition, although Megan didn’t have such a strong temperament normally, if she really decided to be stubborn, she wouldn’t listen to anybody.

Randolph also knew Megan, therefore he could only frown at Zhao Hai right now. Seeing the two’s expressions Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Feel relieved, there won’t be any problems. When we come back and Megan lost a single hair on her head, then you can hold me accountable for my sins.”

Smith turned to Megan and said, “Megan, what do you think? Do you really want to go?”

Megan nodded with full effort, “Yes, I’ve decided.” Smith couldn’t help but sigh, it seems like his little girl really didn’t want to stay, so he could only agree, “Alright, you go. But remember that you’re not allowed to enter the battlefield.” Megan nodded.

Zhao Hai looked at the time and said, “It’s already quite late, we need to save time as much as possible. I’m afraid that the Purcell Family wouldn’t be able to wait for a long time.” Then he bid Smith and Randolph farewell once again before he headed towards the Mansion’s side gate.

Phil had already arranged their mounts, then the group hastily left the City Lord’s Mansion. When they left the city, Zhao Hai gave a command to Cai’er, “Cai’er, go find an area in Stony Mountain where there is no one, we need an exit.” Cai’er complied and got to work.

They already have a Transmission point at Stony Mountain. Originally, the place they could teleport to was only two kilometers around the point, which was the monitor’s range. But now, since the range had increased by five times, Cai’er could definitely find some place that was to Zhao Hai’s specifications.

Zhao Hai knew that Southern King had started to form suspicions. He might have suspected Zhao Hai of having a magic tool that could teleport people. So he already sent some of his men to monitor Stony Mountain and see if Zhao Hai emerges from there, and if he did, it would confirm Boris’ suspicions. This would bring Zhao Hai a ton of trouble, and he didn’t want this right now.

Since Cai’er already got into the task, she soon found a suitable place for Zhao Hai to exit. However, they only released a Blue Eyed rabbit to bring the Ghost Staff to survey the place before having it picked up by a Blood Hawk to deliver them straight into the Casa City.

Zhao Hai’s group appeared inside an unknown warehouse. This place had been bought by Green in the past. Now they could finally be put to good use. They immediately went out of the warehouse to contact Evan about how they would destroy the enemy.

Chapter 430: Gift for Women

Cai’er’s movements were quick, before long, she already told Zhao Hai that the Blue-eyed Rabbit had already been released. Now she was waiting for the opportunity to release the Blood Hawk. Zhao Hai wasn’t anxious, he had just left Sky Water City and was currently looking for a desolate area so that they could enter the Space.

At this time, Zhao Hai also released Xenomorph. SInce the Space had been upgraded, Xenomorph’s body also become much bigger. Now it’s main body was already ten meters high and 20 meters long. The space within its body was now divided into two stories, the upper and lower floor, all in all providing 50 square meters of floor space. Zhao Hai, Laura and the others sat on the upper floor while Blockhead’s group sat on the lower floor.

As soon as they entered Xenomorph, it immediately went to Law River and swam in it. However, it cannot swim for a very long time, since it wasn’t a Water element Undead.

Not long after Xenomorph entered the water, Cai’er told Zhao Hai that the Blood Hawk has been released. After a couple hours, the hawk would arrive at Casa City.

If one were to travel from Stony Mountain to Casa City, a horse would take two day’s worth  travel, but for a Blood Hawk, two hours was enough.[1]

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it, he just lead Xenomorph to swim towards the sea. They were now travelling underwater.

Because Alien cannot travel underwater for too long, Zhao Hai was now considering about having a Water element Undead, something like the Blade-Scaled Whale.

Although he was thinking about this, Zhao Hai knew that it wasn’t time to do it. They hid underwater for two hours before the Hawk finally arrived at Casa City. Then Zhao Hai’s group went into the Space.

This made Laura and the other’s quite regretful, this was the first time they saw such a view of the sea. Although it wasn’t that early, there was still a bit of light coming from the surface, this made them see all kinds of underwater sceneries, like small fishes swimming. This was a new experience for them.

It was not only them who experienced this for the first time, it was the same for Zhao Hai as well. He hadn’t that much time to play around at see before, now he was just sitting and gazed through Xenomorph’s transparent body towards the depths of the sea.

But it was a pity that Xenomorph wasn’t suitable for going too deep because of its element. Presently, they could only go on waters near the sea’s surface, they wouldn’t dare go too deep.

As soon as the group entered the Space, they also immediately went out. The place where they appeared in was exactly the place that Green had bought before. This place was Zhao Hai’s temporary transmission point, but lately they hadn’t been using it.

But since the place was owned by Green, nobody would come here, so Zhao Hai re-used the it.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t dally in the courtyard, upon arriving, they immediately rode their horses to head towards the Grand Duke’s mansion. They didn’t sit inside Alien since Casa City was in a state of war, they didn’t want to make any unnecessary misunderstandings.

Although Zhao Hai knew that Casa City was in a war, he still froze upon arriving. This was because its current appearance was very far from what it was before.

Casa City was Purcell Duchy’s capital, it was even dubbed as the Pearl of the North. Trade was very flourishing here, its streets were very lively.

However, the current Casa City was deserted, not a single person was seen, it was no different from a ghost town. At this moment, a sudden boom was heard, making Zhao Hai look for its source. He understood that the sound must have come from the city wall. His expression couldn’t help but change. He didn’t expect the enemy to still attack in the evening, no wonder Evan said they couldn’t hold on for long.

Zhao Hai frowned and didn’t say anything, he immediately had his horse sprint towards the Grand Duke’s Mansion’s direction. Their action attracted the attention of the people in side the city. Soon, the city’s defenders were onto them, doors and gates were closed in order to block them.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the time to deal with those people, he just continued on towards the mansion. But upon arriving, Zhao Hai noticed a group blocking his way. There were a thousand knights in front of them, all paying attention to Zhao Hai. The lead Knight closed his visor and seemed to be in the ready for a charge.

When Zhao Hai saw this, he couldn’t help but immediately stop his horse. Then he bowed to the knight and said, “To the Purcell family knight, my name is Zhao Hai, I came to see the Grand Duke, I’ll have to give you the trouble of informing him.”

The Knight stared, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You said that you’re Zhao Hai? Does Mister Zhao Hai intend to help our Purcell Family?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, “I wouldn’t dare. I’m just here since the Grand Duke sent me a letter asking for assistance, please do notify him.” The knight excitedly raised his Knight’s spear, an act which Zhao Hai knew was a knight’s way of salute. Then the knight said, “Mister, please wait a bit. I will immediately return, the Grand Duke is still currently at the walls defending.” Then the knight turned towards the wall.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it, it was a special time, so it was natural for them to be careful. He looked at the Cavalry by his side, they should be the elite troops of the Purcell Family. The weakest of them were 4th rank while the strongest were 6th rank. This wasn’t a bad composition, it clearly showed the high caliber of the Purcell Family. It really deserved to be called a Great Clan with its rich heritage.

While Zhao Hai was inspecting the cavalry, the cavalry were also inspecting him. For them, Zhao Hai’s name was very well known. He was quite popular among the people of the Purcell Family since he had helped them in the past.

What’s most important was his and Laura’s legendary love story, it was the people’s favorite topic to talk about in their spare time. Although Zhao Hai had been gone for quite some time, if you mention his name in Casa City, it was impossible for people to not know him, those who don’t number in the scarce few.

But now that they look at Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but feel disappointed. He looked very ordinary, dressed ordinary, even his magic staff looked very ordinary. He didn’t look any special while sitting on his horse. Then they saw Laura and Megan who were at the back, so they immediately knew it was indeed Zhao Hai since Laura’s face was very well known inside Casa City.

Before long, the sound of hooves galloping was heard as two shadows were quickly approaching. With his own eyes, Zhao Hai noticed Evan beside the Knight.

After Evan arrived in front of Zhao Hai, he immediately pulled the reins and jumped down from his horse. Then he laughed and said, “Zhao Hai, good, you really came. You really made me worried, if you came a few days later, then you wouldn’t be able to see me anymore.”

Zhao Hai also jumped down from his horse, he bowed and said, “Little Nephew has seen Uncle Evan. Uncle really has been living a great life for a few thieves to attack him.”

Evan laughed, “Boy, this isn’t any small thief. It’s that son of a bitch Boris. If he doesn’t kill me this time, then he won’t live well.”

Evan was originally a warrior, he had wandered outside before. Even if he had been immersed in being a Grand Duke for the past years, his unyielding warrior spirit was still ingrained to his very bones. This time, this trait of his was rediscovered as he himself fought in battle to kill his enemies.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Nephew has heard of this matter, I’m afraid that this this situation was caused by me, so I came here in order to help solve it. After receiving your letter, I immediately made haste to come here. Right, Uncle, let me make an introduction, you’ve already seen Laura, Meg, and Nier, you should also recognize Blockhead and Rockhead. This is Shue, this is Shun, this is my new fiancee, the Calci Family’s princess, Megan. Megan, this is Uncle Evan, Purcell Duchy’s Grand Duke.”

Megan blushed and then bowed to Evan, “This one has met Uncle Evan.”

Evan laughs and said, “Good, good, this youngster really has a gift for women. In such a short time, you already have another fiancee. Right, we shouldn’t be talking here, let’s enter the mansion.”

Zhao Hai then replied, “Uncle Evan, it seems like someone is attacking the city. Is it alright to leave the walls as it is?”

Evan shook his head and said, “It should be fine, it’s evening, those fellows wouldn’t make that much of an effort. They would wait until the day before doing so.”  Then he led Zhao Hai’s group into the Grand Duke’s Mansion. The scene earlier made the knights confused, they knew that Zhao Hai had a good relationship with the Purcell Family, but they didn’t expect it to be this good. From Evan’s actions, it seems like he didn’t treat Zhao Hai as any other outsider.

This made it strange for those who didn’t know Zhao Hai’s true identity. They already heard that his relationship with Evan was good, but the two of them didn’t have that much contact. So how was it that the two of them were so familiar with each other?”

After the group entered the mansion, Zhao Hai noticed something different. At this time, Zhao Hai didn’t notice a lot of servants, instead there were a lot of warriors inside. All of these people were naturally the Purcell Family’s foreign elders, since the family was now in a crisis, it was their duty to come and support it.

When Evan arrived, he immediately greeted every person he came across, before long, the group arrived at the living room. After sitting down, a warrior came and offered them some tea. Evan wasn’t polite, he took the tea and drank it before he turned to Zhao Hai, “It’s fortunate that you came quickly. If you were a few days late, I’m afraid you won’t be able to help anymore. Those guys are too powerful, they have quite a lot of 8th ranks. But even if they didn’t seem to have a 9th rank expert, the ancestor gave word two days ago that the other side had quite a number of 9th ranks among them. If the ancestor came out this time, the other party would be forced to act.”

* * *

Stony Mountain -> Casa City’s distance was much farther than I remember

Chapter 431: Another Reason

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also heard about this from the information Megan’s family had acquired. They said that the enemy wasn’t really trying to break into the city, they were waiting for me. Hehe. I think they wanted to get the both of us in one fell swoop.”

Evan frowned, he knew about the Calci Family, they were more formidable than his Purcell Family. Information obtained from such an established family would certainly be real, it seems like the siege’s aim this time was both him and Zhao Hai.

From the passing years, Evan has already shed some of his warrior parts. After hearing about this matter he knew that the enemy attacked him to pressure him to send Zhao Hai a letter asking for help. WIth this, they could eliminate Zhao Hai and him at the same time.

Thinking about this, Evan’s face couldn’t help but change. With an apologetic face, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I had been inconsiderate this time, I have involved you. How about this, I’ll go distract them while you leave Purcell Duchy immediately. I will also have some juniors of the family come with you. No matter what, the blood of the Purcell Family shouldn’t be extinguished.

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he understood Evan’s words. He smiled faintly and said, “Escape? Why must I escape? This time, not only would I not run away, I have also brought my Buda Clan’s Wild Dragon War Banner. This time, I will make the people on the continent know that my Buda Clan hasn’t fallen yet, and that we have re-emerged.”

Just after he said that, a loud ‘Bang’ was heard. Zhao Hai turned and saw Ruyen standing in front of the living room door. His words made her drop the pot of tea she was holding to the ground.

Ruyen has heard that Zhao Hai come. This time, when Zhao Hai appeared, she knew that he was a genuine friend of the Purcell Family. Adding on to the fact that she was under the care of Zhao Hai when she was returning from Rosen Empire, Ruyen wanted to express her gratitude to him. Therefore, she had a servant hand over a pot of tea since she wanted serve Evan and Zhao Hai a cup. But she didn’t think that when she arrived in front of the door, she heard Zhao Hai just as he delivered his speech. From what she got, Zhao Hai was actually a person of the Buda Clan. Zhao Hai had already revealed his identity, he was actually her former fiancee, Adam Buda!

When Evan and Zhao Hai turned their heads and saw Ruyen, Evan’s face couldn’t help but sink, he said. “You came? Come over and greet Little Hai.”

Zhao Hai stood up and gazed calmy at Ruyen, then he gave a bow and said, “Miss Ruyen seems well. Zhao Hai gives his greetings to Miss Ruyen.”

Looking at Zhao Hai, Ruyen used all of her courage and asked, “Your surname is Buda? Are you Adam?”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “I am indeed surnamed Buda. Adam was my former name, I go by the name of Zhao Hai now.”

Ruyen felt that she didn’t have the face to see Zhao Hai, she covered her face and turned around to run. At the same time, while she was getting farther away, the sound of weeping can be heard.[1]

Seeing this development, Zhao Hai was left not knowing what to do. He really didn’t expect this to happen, at this time Evan talked, “Well, let’s just leave her to herself. Little Hai, did you really bring the Wild Dragon Banner? Little Hai, listen to me, you must escape, 9th rank experts aren’t people you can deal with.”

Zhao Hai just smiled faintly and replied, “What’s great about 9th rank experts? Rest assured, even if the other party sends 9th ranks, I can deal with them, no problem. Let’s rest first, tomorrow, I’ll go with you to the walls and declare that the Buda Clan has come back.”

Evan looked at Zhao Hai’s face and sighed, he didn’t know what else to say. He just gave a nod and said, “Alright, go rest for this evening, we’ll head to the walls tomorrow.” After looking at the situation from the wall tomorrow, he believed that Zhao Hai would know the enormity of the situation. At that time, he would try to persuade Zhao Hai to escape again, he believed that Zhao Hai would agree.

Evan didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be so strong. He thought that Zhao Hai would look at the attackers and decide that battling them wasn’t possible. As long as Zhao Hai can be persuaded, Evan can have the young generation join him in retreat.

While Evan was dwelling on the scenarios on his mind, Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and Megan and then smiled, “Tomorrow, I’ll head to the walls to take a look. Then I’ll go dispatch the troops to deal with them. Let’s see what other plans they have. The two of you should head to the Space and look at the situation in the monitor, just in case they other party sends 9th ranks after me. Don’t come out.”

Laura nodded, “Alright, we’ll just look at your actions there. But Brother Hai, this time, shouldn’t you invite Grandpa Green? This time, our reappearance in the continent would be a key moment of the Buda Clan, Grandpa Green should be present right?”

Zhao Hai though for a moment and said, “That would be good. Let’s go invite Grandpa Green.” Then the group immediately want to Iron Mountain Fort to tell Green about this matter.

Green immediately agreed and also proposed to include Merine as well, Zhao Hai agreed. In the same day, Green and Merine went to the Space. While Zhao Hai’s group was resting in the Space, Green and Merine wasn’t, they had been waiting for this day for quite a long time. And since it was just around the corner, the two were too excited to fall asleep.

 The next morning, after Zhao Hai and the others woke up, they immediately went out of the Space. Green and Merine didn’t eat their meals inside the Space, they knew that Evan would certainly ask them to eat with him.

Sure enough, not long after they reappeared in the mansion, Evan sent someone to invite Zhao Hai and the others. Zhao Hai immediately led Green and the others to exit from the courtyard.

When they came out, the servants couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai’s group. This was because of the two additions, Green and Merine. The servants certainly didn’t misremember the faces on the group. However, they knew that they didn’t have anything to do with it so they just welcomed Zhao Hai to the dining room.

When they arrived at the dining hall, Evan couldn’t help but stare blankly. Naturally, he knew Green and Merine, he just didn’t think that they would be appearing here today.

Evan immediately went forward with haste, he respectfully gave a salute and said, “Uncle Green, Aunt Merine, when did you two arrive? I was just about to ask Little Hai as to why the two of you aren’t present. I was afraid that the two of you are too busy, I didn’t expect to see the two of you today, this is fantastic!”

Green gave a faint smile while giving Evan a small bow, “Young Master Evan, without your help, our Buda Clan may not have survived this long. Let this old man express his gratitude in behalf of the Clan.”

Evan quickly replied, “Uncle Green, I wouldn’t dare accept your bow, do you want to shorten my longevity? Let’s not talk about this anymore, come and sit with me. I’ve already prepared the meal, moreover I have something to tell the two of you.” Then Evan led the group inside the room.

“……..”

Evan’s arguments were very solid, Green and Merine understood where Evan was getting at. In all honesty, if they didn’t have their current capabilities, Green and Merine would surely follow what Evan suggested. But this time, their Clan’s strength was more than enough to deal with the enemies.

Thus, Green looked at Evan with a faint smile, “Young Master Evan, you can rest assured. This time, me and Merine didn’t come because we want the Young Master to leave, but to witness the Buda Clan’s Wild Dragon Banner fluttering again. Don’t worry, dealing with four 9th ranks aren’t a problem, the 200 thousand troops aren’t as well. This time, we’re here to let the continent know about our return, as well as make those who plan to offend us shudder at the mention of the Buda Clan.”

Evan looked at Green, he didn’t think those words would come from Green, he replied, “Uncle Green, this is a 9th rank expert! 9th rank!”

Green smiled, “I know, rest assured, as long as they send four 9th ranks or less, you won’t even need to send Senior Origin Sword Saint. Those 8th ranks are nothing as well. Right, no need to talk about these right now, we’ll eat first. After eating we’ll head towards the city wall to take a look.”

When Evan looked at Green and Merine’s confident appearance, he couldn’t help but calm down. He knew that the two weren’t impulsive people. Their initial purpose was to protect Zhao Hai’s poor life, protect the Buda Clan, and because of this, they even regarded Zhao Hia’s life with more importance than their own. Therefore, how could they allow Zhao Hai to take such a risk? For them to agree with Zhao Hai’s action, that mean that they were fully confident this time.

Thinking about this, Evan’s heart couldn’t help but loosen. But he also felt confusion, he knew clearly that the strongest experts of the Buda Clan were Green and Merine. Although they were formidable themselves, they weren’t 9th rank experts. But the enemy has 9th rank experts, maybe even four 9th rank experts. Can they contend with them? Did they get the support of another 9th rank? But that couldn’t be it, a single 9th rank cannot go against four. In the end, what were the cards of the Buda Clan?

…

Evan invited Zhao Hai’s group for breakfast today, however, he didn’t include his family. He knew that the people in the Purcell family weren’t very much in Zhao Hai’s good books. When the Buda Clan had lost their home, those people didn’t give the clan any face. Meeting them right now would be very embarrassing.

After eating their meal, the group was led by Evan to walk towards the City Wall. Casa City was now on a state of Martial Law, there weren’t any commoners seen walking around the city, instead, groups of warriors were seen patrolling the streets.

But the garrison troops of Casa City weren’t a lot, all in all they just numbered 20 thousand people. They were initially sent in order to protect the Grand Duke’s Mansion. The majority of the Purcell Family’s forces were in Iron Mountain Fortress, guarding the Duchy from the Beastman raids. With most of their troops there, the troops inside Casa City weren’t that much. If not for Casa City’s walls being thick, then they feared that the city may have already fallen.

When Zhao Hai and the others got up on the city wall, they saw that some of its parts were damaged. From those damages, one can see that the source was magic, while some were from magical cannons as well as ballistas.

Stood on the walls were the garrison troops. The troops were composed of the Purcell Family’s elites. If not for them, Casa City wouldn’t have stood to this day.

Zhao Hai gazed outwards, at this time, the entire city was completely encircled by something, probably the doing of Earth Mages. Outside the City, numerous depressions were seen on the ground, probably placed there in order to stop cavalry charges coming from Casa City. It really seems like they really want to place Evan’s family in dire straits.

After looking at the situation outside the city, Zhao Hai turned his head to Evan and said, “Uncle Evan, it has been some time since those people started to besiege the city, did you really not have any reinforcements?”

Evan smiled bitterly, “How could it be impossible to have reinforcements? But in the end those troops were rendered useless. In addition to the 100 thousand troops laying siege here, there was another 100 thousand who were actively blocking off all the reinforcements. In addition to our reinforcements, the noble families that we have good relations with were suppressed by the empire. They simply couldn’t come and help us, we’re really at a loss at this time.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Boris’ preparation this time is indeed very adequate. When he attacked Ruyen last time, I should have already been mindful, I just didn’t think that he would attack the Purcell Family immediately. Upon further consideration, the Purcell Family really didn’t have any enmity with him, moreover, the family is an established noble clan, nobody would dare go this hard on you. I actually didn’t expect that someone would be this brazen, they were ruthless as well, to think that they are thinking about extinguishing the family.”

Evan shook his head while forcing a smile, “This time’s matter shouldn’t all be because of you. Moreover, our Purcell Family didn’t buy Boris’ purpose. Looking at Boris’ recent actions, it seems like he wanted to act against some nobles for quite some time. His goals just seemed to coincide with this matter, therefore, he decided to begin with me.”

* * *

Zhao Hai, breaking hearts of men and women ever since transmigrating.

Chapter 432: Attack

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware that there would be such a thing. He looked at Evan and said, “I didn’t expect that there was such a matter inside Boris’ mind. It’s fine, we’ll be cleaning up today. I think Boris would think twice if he wanted to repeat today’s matter.”

Then he turned to walk down from the city wall along with Evan and the others. Upon arriving down, Zhao Hai immediately let Alien out. Then he quickly place the Buda Clan’s Wild Dragon War Banner that was already installed into a pole on top of Alien’s back. After that, he made Green and Merine center inside Alien’s body. Evan looked at this scene and couldn’t help but come with them. Zhao Hai didn’t block him, he allowed Evan to enter the space inside Alien’s body.[1]

After the group sat at the upper floor, they prepared themselves for tea. When Zhao Hai sat down, he turned to Evan and said, “Uncle Evan, make them open the gate, then leave the rest to us.”

Evan turned to look at Green and Merine, when he saw that they were still calm, he didn’t object. He immediately relayed his orders to a guard. When Evan entered Alien, he took with him two guards. Evan was a Grand Duke, how could he not bring with him two assistants?

Soon after the guard left, the city’s gate was opened. Then Zhao Hai headed out of the city. When the enemies saw this scene, they immediately formed their lines and waited.

Those who laid siege to Casa City had no idea that Zhao Hai arrived. But they knew about the Cavalry units of the Purcell Family. These elite troops regularly clashed with the beastmen cavalries, how could their fighting prowess be low? It was because of this that they deliberately made ditches outside the gate, to prevent the cavalry to fully utilize the might of their charge.

However, it seems like they were mistaken this time. As they prepared to meet the cavalry of the Purcell Family, what they saw coming out of the city gate was a very large undead instead. The undead’s body was 20 meters long, with a height of about 10 meters, it had a dark green skeleton, and it was covered with spikes. It looked extremely terrifying.

And on the undead’s body, a banner was seen fluttering with the wind. The banner had a blood red surface, along with an embroidery of a threatening dragon. The banner may have some damages here and there, but it only increased its killing aura. For those who were experienced, they knew that this was a War Banner!

The mercenaries outside were stunned. They never thought that what came out this time would be an undead creature. At this moment, the leader of this troop immediately thought of another reason for their attack this time, isn’t it because of a Dark Mage?

He immediately issued an order loudly, the troops behind him quickly became more compact. The men and horses of the front line were also getting prepared to meet Zhao Hai.

At the same time, the leader also invited the Mages. They knew that Zhao Hai was a Dark Mage. The best way to deal with a Mage was another Mage. In dealing with Zhao Hai and the Purcell Duchy, the brought more than 50 Mages.

The Mages were specifically tasked to deal with Zhao Hai as well as act as mobile turrets. Therefore, most of the time, they were inside the camps and were only called out this time. Usually, soldiers were the ones doing the attacking, using magic cannons as well as ballistas.

Under the gazes of them as well as the garrison troops, the undead creature just slowly stepped over the ditches that were previously dug out. Although the ditches were quite wide, they weren’t enough to stop a large being such as Alien. Before long, Alien had already passed over several obstacles.

The troop leader decided that it was still not time to attack the undead. He wanted to wait for the Mages from the camp to arrive before dealing with Alien. Thus, he made his troops standy by and wait for a while.

But it was a mistake to give Zhao Hai this much time for preparations. While he went over the ditches, he didn’t immediately take action, he wanted the other party to be clueless as to what he wanted to do.

At this moment, with Zhao Hai’s intention, a battalion of undead cavalry appeared. These undead were all Beastmen. All of them were tall and were sitting on their own mounts along with huge maces on their hands. Just by looking at their appearance, one could see how terrifying they are.

Zhao Hai released 10 thousand cavalry this time. The group immediately covered the surrounding area. Although this number isn’t that large, the 100 thousand enemy troops were divided. The enemy troops’ 100 thousand soldiers aren’t enough to surround the city, so they only deeply guarded the city’s four gates.

This way, the armies on each gate numbered about twenty thousand each. With their losses these past few days, the estimation of 20 thousand was quite correct.

While the enemies were still silly from seeing the undead cavalry and were quite confused about how they would handle this, a sudden sound was heard coming out from Alien’s mouth. The sound issued a declaration, “With the Wild Dragon Banner as the witness, show them who is invincible! Kill!”

This sound naturally came from Zhao Hai. This was Alien’s recently acquired ability. As long as Zhao Hai is inside Alien’s body, his voices could pass along Alien’s mouth with an increased volume, much like how a loudspeaker worked.

After Zhao Hai gave his words, the Beastmen undead cavalry immediately help their weapons up as they charged towards the mercenary soldiers.

In Ark Continent, there were almost no other race that was able to block a Beastman’s charge head on. Their charges were too sharp, any other army wasn’t a match.

And in order to deal with the Purcell Family, all these soldiers were disguised as mercenaries. They didn’t have their standard issue armor in order to curb the Purcell Family’s suspicions, neither did they have any cavalry. With the only armor they were wearing being light armor, they could be classified as light infantry. For them to block a Beastman charge in their current state was akin to them looking for death.

Ten thousand undead Beastman cavalry began to charge towards the mercenary-dressed soldiers. With these scene, the soldier lines immediately became a mess. They were all quite experienced, naturally they knew the power behind a Beastman charge, and they also knew that an undead charge wasn’t any less powerful, they certainly didn’t want to be on the receiving end of such an impact.

However, their troop leader was quite tenacious as he didn’t issue any order for retreat. Because of this the soldiers had no other choice than to stay put. To be honest, the troop leader was quite hopeful, he knew that the level of an undead under a general Dark Mage wasn’t that powerful. Their fighting strength shouldn’t be that strong, so even if their appearances were quite scary, they might not be very terrifying in battle. Upon seeing Zhao Hai release these many undead, the troop leader was quite sure that they wouldn’t be too strong, thus he believed that they would be able to block this charge.

But before long, it was quite obvious that he was mistaken. Zhao Hai’s undead creatures were very capable and were unable to be stopped. Even if they aim specifically for the heavy armor cavalry, they still weren’t able to stop them, much less the light cavalry mixed in.

When the undead cavalry’s formation clashed with the mercenaries, the troop leader immediately realized his blunder. These Beastmen undead were too strong, maybe even stronger than a true Beastman. Their soldiers simply weren’t able to resist them, with just a single glance, one could see the mercenaries’ formation completely devastated.

Zhao Hai was not idle at this time. He sat inside Alien as it followed behind the undead charge. He gazed at the scene. After all, every mercenary that dared approach him were immediately destroyed by Alien.

Evan was also inside Alien staring blankly at what is happening outside. He never imagined Zhao Hai’s undead to be this strong. They were too strong that when they met the infantry, the latter were immediately ruined. Their charge was the visual form of the word ‘unstoppable’.

After Zhao Hai destroyed the enemy’s formation, he didn’t stop, he directly rushed towards the enemy camp on the other side. Moreover, Zhao Hai was also continually releasing Dark Magic, turning all those who had been killed into undead. The dead soldiers immediately rose up and began to chase the other soldiers who were escaping.

These people were very terrified, seeing their former allies rise up again and chase them with their weapons was a scene that would induce panic.

The soldiers getting killed by the Beastman cavalry were getting more and more numerous. The new undead also kept increasing. Aside from the initial Beastman undead that Zhao Hai released, they now had more than 2 thousand additional undead from those mercenary soldiers that died.

At this time, the enemy Mages also began to respond. Lines of magic went flying towards the undead, some of them even headed straight for Alien.

Zhao Hai simply didn’t care about any of these. He just sat inside Alien and continued to leisurely drink his tea. These magic attacks heading towards Alien were like small irritating itches. They didn’t have any effect on the undead.

This made the Mages very embarrassed, not only could they not deal with this huge magic beast, their spells towards the undead Beastmen Cavalry were also very useless.

The 8th rank experts on the camps saw this situation and immediately went out. In their view, even if these undead Beastmen were quite strong, if they have some 5th or 6th ranks, then they could already be good. They thought that if they give enough effort, they could exterminate all of the undead as well as Zhao Hai.

However, just like those before them, they were very mistaken. The undead were quite strong, to the point that each of the undead could contend with each one of the mages. If two undeads were to fight them, then they would certainly be defeated. If they were attacked by more, they would surely die.

This made the 8th rank experts feel blank inside, they didn’t think that they would meet this situation. What kind of undead were these? How could they be this powerful?

Since the mages cannot block the undead cavalry, the undead immediately crashed into their camp. The undead immediately chased down all the mercenaries as well as their servants. Most importantly, they focused their attacks on the Mages.

* * *

Fukkit, I’ll use Alien from now on. Xenomorph is too long.

Chapter 433: Might of the Undead

By this time, the people who sieged Casa City were now in a mess. Nobody can block Zhao Hai’s advances. Only those Advanced Mages could help themselves in order to escape. Any Mages with a rank lower were killed immediately, then were turned into undead. After which they immediately began casting magic in order to attack other mercenary soldiers.

The people’s minds were submerged in confusion. Due to the suppression of Dark Mages these years, most armies didn’t have any Dark Mages, this was especially true for Aksu Empire. This made them forget the fact that the most terrifying place to meet a Dark Mage was in a battlefield.

The reason for this was because the battlefield provided them with more than enough resources to raise undead anytime. Even if those undead couldn’t compare to Zhao Hai’s, the pressure they could give people were still very huge. This made people give Dark Mages another nickname while they are on the battlefield, they were called Death Gods.

Because there hadn’t been any major wards in the continent, and adding on to the suppression of Dark Mages, the soldiers present hadn’t met a practitioner of Dark Magic. So once they encountered Zhao Hai, they dissolved into panic.

Evan looked at the undead who were chasing the mercenaries outside and was completely dumbfounded. He had seen Zhao Hai before, and he has also seen Adam. The last time they met, he felt that Zhao Hai has let go of his playboy attitude. He became more sensible, more fierce. But when he saw the current Zhao Hai who was just leisurely drinking tea, Evan was terrified.

He thought that it was scary. Evan was a warrior, and as a warrior he had seen killings. And even if he became a Grand Duke he had also witnessed a ton of cruel and merciless people. But he hadn’t met people like Zhao Hai who didn’t even flinch upon seeing this much undead killing people. One could see why, upon seeing Zhao Hai right now, Evan felt fear.

Massacring people without emotion was something a lot of people can achieve. But Zhao Hai was different. While looking at the battle outside, he still drank his tea inside Alien, at the same time, his other hand was continually casting Magic, turning more people into undead and making those new undead kill more people. While all of this is happening, he was still drinking tea, such a person was terrifying.

Evan felt like Zhao Hai wasn’t the Adam that he knew. To him, Zhao Hai has become cold blooded. Evan felt strange, he felt mortified.

Zhao Hai had noted Evan’s expression, he understood what he was thinking. He placed his cup down and looked at Evan, “Does Uncle Evan think I was too ruthless? Too cold-blooded?”

Evan looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Little Hai, I know that the Buda Clan’s situation had forced you to undergo such a huge change. But you must know that plenty of these people are also innocent. It should be enough if we were to repel them.”

Zhao Hai stared at Evan and sighed, “Uncle Evan, do you think that I want it to be like this? But even if I didn’t, they are still our enemies. You see them right now as pitiful, but haven’t you thought? If we didn’t have enough strength, they will be pursuing us like ghosts. When the time comes, neither me nor the Purcell Family would exist, we would be completely destroyed by them. Do you think that at that moment they would let us off because of their tender hearts?”

Evan naturally understood this. If both armies fight, there was little space for pity. But this time, it was undead killing living people. This scenario made him feel terrible, if he were there, it would feel like was being betrayed.

Actually, it wasn’t only Evan who had this sentiment, majority of the people in the continent share this view as well. Otherwise, Dark Mages wouldn’t become the most hated profession, they didn’t even consider that Dark Mages can minimize their losses in the battlefield. Dark Mages would use anything to attack the enemy. For them, attacking the enemy with a blade or an undead was the same. In the end, they could get the job done.

Green, who had also become numb to the scene, coldly snorted and said, “What’s wrong? Do you prefer sending your subordinates to deal with the enemies rather than the undead? It seems like you have been poisoned by the Radiant Church as well.”

Evan, upon hearing Green, became embarrassed. There was no way for him to disrespect Green. Because of his position in the Buda Clan, Evan also regarded Green as an elder. Thus, he can’t do anything but listen to Green’s words.

At this time, the troops on the other gates were also made aware of the situation and sent some reinforcements. However, the reinforcements had no way to deal with the undead. The situation remained the same, the undead were still slaughtering their way along the enemy lines.

The 100 thousand who laid siege on the city were flustered. They immediately gathered their men and started to surround Zhao Hai. But Zhao Hai seemed to not care, he still commanded the undead to continue the slaughter.

If one were to look down from the sky, the battlefield displayed a strange image. A group of mercenaries were surrounding an Undead Creature in the middle, looking like to extinguish whoever was in the middle.

But if you look at it carefully, those who were wearing mercenary clothes were constantly falling. And when they get killed, they were immediately wrapped with a dark mist and then became an undead creature. After which they got up and then attacked their fellow mercenaries.

The fighting continued on for the entire morning. Finally, the mercenaries couldn’t hold long and chose to withdraw. They didn’t dare continue to attack Zhao Hai since they were constantly getting killed. In the end, those who were killed numbered between 30 thousand to 40 thousand people. Their losses were too great.

What made them very confused was that even if those undead were powerful, it was still impossible for them to suffer losses along these numbers. Some of them only suffered an injury and then died soon afterwards. Later on, they discovered that the weapons of the undead were all coated with poison. As long as they were wounded by the weapon, even if only a little, they would die in a short while.

The mercenaries were too ill prepared in a scenario where they would retreat. They expected that they would only retreat if the matter had already been dealt with. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s creatures continually hounded them from behind. Unlike them, the undead didn’t know the meaning of exhaustion.

One side is infantry, while the other is cavalry, their disparity in speed was very huge. But since they had the numbers, some were able to escape safely. In the end, 50 thousand mercenaries were saved.

The chase lasted until the afternoon, and Zhao Hai had obtained another 50 thousand additional undead. After the even, the group returned to Casa City. And after eating, Zhao Hai’s group returned to the place Evan arranged for them to rest in.

However, Evan was unable to sleep that night. Zhao Hai’s performance shook him to his core. Not only was he startled by how Zhao Hai handled life and death, he was also shocked by how powerful Zhao Hai’s undead were.

It was now that Evan understood why Zhao Hai was able to survive after all those powers sent people to deal with him. By what Zhao Hai has shown today, it would be strange if those assailants survived.

At the same time, Evan also had to acknowledge the strength of a Dark Mage. He truly didn’t pay any attention to the profession before, this was because of the continent’s constant suppression of them. This was even more true in Aksu Empire, because of the collusion between Boris and the Radiant Church, the suppression of the Dark Mages had reached another level. From a young age, children were already hearing bad things about Dark Mages. This idea bore into the minds of the people and made them feel disgust towards those who practice Dark Magic.

This was precisely the reason why when Zhao Hai resided in Stony Mountain, he immediately sent people to deal with him. This was also the reason why there were no Dark Mages among the Purcell Family’s forces.

But after watching Zhao Hai’s might today, Evan felt regret. He knew that casualties are greatest during the initial collision between two armies. And during the skirmish, there would also be losses here and there. If a Dark Mage was present, they could drastically reduce the losses they suffered in the battlefield.

As soon as his thought reached that point, Evan was completely regretful for not having a Dark Mage in his army. But it was now too late, there weren’t a lot of Dark Mages in the continent, and those people weren’t very trustful towards nobles. Recruiting Dark Mages during this time was close to impossible.

At this time, Zhao Hai was inside the Space. Green and Merine were inside as well. Green was very happy that his face turned red. He was really excited, they finally had shown their might. The Wild Dragon Banner had flown once again and achieved an overwhelming victory.

When Zhao Hai looked at Green’s appearance, he smiled faintly and said, “Grandpa Green, I think you should return to Iron Mountain fort tomorrow. The matter in Casa City will be resolved in around two days or so. The enemies cannot block our undead, so their 9th ranks should be making their move. Not just you, even I might need to retreat to the Space. The battle would be handed over to Cai’er and Zhao Wen.[1]

Green thought for a moment before he nodded, “Alright, we’ll return to Iron Mountain Fort tomorrow. My desire had already been realized. But Young Master, you should take care of yourself. If the opposite party sends 9th ranks tomorrow, immediately hide inside the Space. Moreover, I’m afraid that the Radiant Church would also make their move. Their main target this time is you and you cannot suffer an accident.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Rest assured, if something happens, I’ll immediately hide in the Space. Let’s see how they handle me then. But what you said is right, the Radiant Church had been quiet all this time. I’m afraid that when they receive the news about my identity, they will send people to Iron Mountain Fort. So it’s best for you to return.”

Green didn’t disagree and just nodded.

* * *

Correct me if I’m wrong, Zhao Hai should have four 9th ranks right? Wind guy, Fire guy, Cai’er, and Zhao Wen?

Chapter 434: The Thoughts of Origin Sword Saint

What Zhao Hai didn’t know was that the moment they returned to Casa City, their actions were under Origin Sword Saint’s attention.

A 9th rank expert can feel everything around them by using Mental Power. With Zhao Hai’s performance today, it was natural for the Origin Sword Saint to take note of him.

To be exact, these days, the entire Casa City was under Origin Sword Saint’s constant monitoring. After all, he was someone from the Purcell Family, he didn’t want an accident to happen to the family.

Zhao Hai’s arrival made him very curious. He had been continually paying attention to Casa City, but he didn’t notice Zhao Hai’s group entering its vicinity. Similarly, had no explanation as to how Green appeared while Zhao Hai and the others were resting.

For a 9th rank expert, this matter was very baffling. He always felt that Zhao Hai was disappearing every time he enters his courtyard, it was impossible for him to know what they were doing. Most importantly, in the daytime, he can feel every single person in the city except for Zhao Hai’s group. It seems like Zhao Hai was made of air, he couldn’t sense anything from him, it felt very strange.

So this evening, Origin Sword Saint went to Zhao Hai’s courtyard to check things out. But even in this proximity, he still couldn’t sense anything. It seems like Zhao Hai disappeared from existence.

This made Origin Sword Saint very puzzled. In the end, when he saw that the place’s lamp was not lit up,  he came out of hiding and went to the courtyard. He saw nobody, not a single person was present.

Seeing this scene, Origin Sword Saint couldn’t help but stare blankly. Then his complexion changed, then he thought of a possibility. It may be that Zhao Hai had someone with a formidable Spatial Divergent Ability, or he has a Space Mage.

In the continent, Space Mages were very rare. However, among the people who have Divergent Abilities, those who had abilities related to space were quite a lot. This may have been some sort of balance set by the world.

One has to recognize that among all Mages, Space Mages were the hardest to deal with. And among Divergent Abilities, Space related ones gave you the most headache. Therefore, when Origin Sword Saint noticed that Zhao Hai disappeared, he immediately thought of about a Spatial Divergent Ability. Besides that, he cannot think of any other reason as to how a group of people can silently disappear from the courtyard.

Origin Sword Saint stood for a while in the courtyard, then with an intention he immediately flashed away and appeared in front of Evan’s door. Then with a serious tone, Origin Sword Saint said, “Evan, come out.”

Evan wasn’t asleep, but with his current strength, there was no way for him to sense Origin Sword Saint’s presence. Therefore, when he heard those word, he immediately knew who came. He immediately got up from his bed, and wore his nightly robes.

Evan saw Origin Sword Saint when he went out of his house. He gave a bow and said, “Ancestor, what are your orders?”

Origin Sword Saint looked at Evan and said, “This Zhao Hai, I know about him. In the past, I didn’t support helping his Buda Clan. But now, it seems like your decision is correct. If Zhao Hai doesn’t have a Divergent Spatial Ability, then he should have someone who does. Moreover, it seems like he had acquired a huge backing, otherwise his Water of Nothingness wouldn’t have been cured. In addition to those strong Undead, if he can invite some 9th ranks to his side, then he would be formidable. What’s most important was the fact that he is in-laws with the Calci Family. His current status cannot be underestimated anymore. No matter what, you should maintain our Purcell Family’s good relation with him. Right, didn’t we have an engagement arranged with him before? You should carry out that agreement.”

Evan’s expression couldn’t help but express his pain. He knew that if he had the power before, the engagement wouldn’t have been cancelled. At this point, Zhao Hai already had three beautiful fiancees. In this case, how could he possibly look for another? [1]

Evan cannot accomplish these requests, he had no other choice but tell Origin Sword Saint about what happened. Upon listening to Evan, Origin Sword Saint frowned and said, “It seems like this matter isn’t easy. But it doesn’t matter, he can get married to another girl asid from Ruyen. Don’t we have some marriageable women in the Purcell Family? We can just change the girl we send.”

Evan gave a forced smile, “Ancestor might not know, but Zhao Hai is a very proud person. Moreover, I’ve asked his fiance’s and they said that there was no way for him to be with someone if the both of them didn’t have any sentiment towards each other. I’m very sure he won’t agree and oppose if we provide a marriage candidate.”

Origin Sword Saint nodded, “Alright, I really don’t care much about these things. No matter what, for the good of the Purcell Family, I’ve already told you about Zhao Hai’s strength. Make sure to handle this matter carefully. Also, pay attention to any potions that could enhance someone’s strength. Ever since we lost Buffy, the Purcell Family badly needs another 9th rank expert. I alone cannot provide all of the family’s security.”

Evan stared for a moment and then replied, “Ancestor, rest assured. If there’s anything you need, feel free to approach me.”

Origin Sword Saint looked at Evan and sighed, “It would be great if it was you who breaks through to 9th rank. But you have to take care of the family’s affairs, your attention would be divided. You should go find another person with enough talent to become a 9th rank to serve the family.”

Evan nodded, “Yes, Ancestor, be relieved.”

Origin Sword Saint nodded, “You must remember, for a Clan to survive, it needs a 9th rank expert. I suspect this Zhao Hai already had the support of a 9th rank expert, otherwise he wouldn’t be so unyielding. A 9th rank expert can guarantee a family’s survival for a hundred years. If I didn’t exist, all of those who has bad intentions towards our Purcell Family would’ve already gone to exterminate us. Therefore, you must go and find a candidate as soon as possible.”

Evan nodded, then Origin Sword Saint’s body flashed before he disappeared. Seeing that the ancestor has gone, Evan sighed. He didn’t expect the Origin Sword Saint to place this much importance to Zhao Hai. He actually made a special trip to Evan for such matter.

Evan couldn’t help but sigh, he didn’t need the ancestor to remind him that Zhao Hai was extraordinary.The re-emergence of the Buda Clan today would likely inform the entire continent that there was actually a cure to the Water of Nothingness.

One must know that the Water of Nothingness was something nobody has aside from the Radiant Church and the Great Clans. The Radiant Church uses this to deal with those wicked Dark Mages. Naturally, they also used these on other purposes that nobody knew, but they still claim that they at least used it for a “Righteous cause”.

But the Great Nobles in the continent have a lot of use for the Water of Nothingness. But its supply was scarce, moreover, there was no known antidote for it. This made this item a very terrifying thing for all experts in the continent.

And now, Zhao Hai appeared. Before, he had drank the Water of Nothingness, but now he was freely using magic. This represented the fact that he had a way to solve his toxin. This was a serious attack for both the Radiant Church as well as the Great Clans. This was akin to them losing their ultimate weapon.

Moreover, the strength that Zhao Hai has shown made them very startled. Adding on to his matter with the Calci family and his eventual engagement to Megan, most people were now paying attention to Zhao Hai. At this point, there wasn’t a person in the continent who dared to underestimate him.

The reason why Southern King Boris decided to attack Zhao Hai this time was not only because he was an exile of the Aksu Empire, someone who didn’t have any support from the Imperial Clan. Secondly, it was also because the Calci Family were enemies of the Radiant Church. Therefore, they didn’t have any hesitation in this time’s attack.

But no hesitation didn’t mean that there weren’t any disagreements. There a lot of people who were afraid of the Calci Family. Zhao Hai’s current fame wasn’t any worse than them.

In such a case, Evan didn’t know how to proceed with his relationship with Zhao Hai. Even if he worked as a Patriarch for a long time, he was still left with nothing to do this time.

In the past, Ruyen’s matter was handled by Caesar. That time, the Purcell Family were bent on severing their relationship with Zhao Hai. If it weren’t for this matter, Zhao Hai standing wouldn’t be like this. To Evan, he regarded Zhao Hai as his own nephew. He knew that if he wanted to further the family’s connection to Zhao Hai this time, their relationship might even deteriorate.

Evan sighed, then he turned back into his room. Although he couldn’t fall asleep, he still laid down on his bed with closed eyes. He needed rest, he still had a lot of things to do tomorrow.

Just like Zhao Hai, Evan also thought that since the other party’s army couldn’t deal with Casa City anymore, then they will certainly send their aces, the 9th rank experts.

Only with their 9th rank experts could they achieve victory in this war. What worried Evan right now was if Zhao Hai could really deal with the several 9th ranks that would be sent.

If Zhao Hai can deal with them, then that would be a good thing. But if he cannot, everything will turn for the worse. These thoughts kept circulating inside Evan’s mind over and over.

The next morning, Zhao Hai’s group appeared once again inside the courtyard. When they got up that morning, Cai’er told Zhao Hai that Origin Sword Saint had come to the courtyard yesterday to examine them. She also told Zhao Hai about the conversation between Evan and Origin Sword Saint.

Zhao Hai really didn’t think that this 9th rank Origin Sword Saint would pay any attention to him. But he had no plans of marrying into the Purcell Family. Just like what Evan said the last time, Ruyen was no longer worthy of Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about these things anymore. He had helped the Purcell Family mainly because the family had helped them before. Also, this was also a good opportunity to reveal the Wild Dragon banner of the Buda Clan. And another reason was because the Purcell Duchy’s position was right beside the Black Wasteland. The Purcell Family being here was a good thing for Zhao Hai. It was much better to have a friend as a neighbor than an enemy.

When Zhao Hai and the others went to the dining room, Evan was already there. Evan was alone, he was just there to accompany Zhao Hai’s group.

When he saw Zhao Hai come without Green nor Merine, Evan stared, then he asked Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, where is Uncle Green and Aunt Merine?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They had another thing to do so they left. In any case, we don’t need their help today. I think that the enemy’s 9th ranks would make their move this day.”

Evan nodded, “I thought so as well.  Yesterday, a fourth of their army was killed off by you. Now, they have no way of surrounding the city as well as stopping the reinforcements. Today is the best time for those 9th ranks to take action, or else it would be too late.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “I’ll be waiting for them. I hope that they won’t be too weak, otherwise I would be very disappointed.”

At this point, a voice was heard, “Boy, you’re extremely arrogant. Come and meet your death!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he appeared outside in a flash as he looked at the sky and saw four figures flying there. Three of them wore a warrior’s garments while one wore a mage’s robe. And that robe was colored white.

Seeing the group appear, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Good, three Warriors as well as a 9th rank Light Mage. Very good, it seems like you really wanted to deal with the undead that I have.”

After Zhao Hai’s words, the Light Mage snorted and said, “Stop talking, you demonspawn. Your judgement day has come, accept the baptism of the light!”

Zhao Hai laughed, “What was that name you gave me? When did I become a demonspawn? You really dare to say that you can baptise the darkness? Then why does the night still exist? You are just deceiving yourself. People might think that you people are righteous, but that doesn’t apply to me. Today, if you want my life, then you need to show some real skills.”

When Zhao Hai saw that the three warriors seem to be escorting the 9th rank Light Mage, he instantly knew that these people were sent by the Radiant Church.

This made Zhao Hai lose all of his hesitation. For him, it was impossible to resolve his hatred for the Radiant Church. And it so happens that this time, not only could he exterminate some 9th ranks, he can even weaken the power of the church.

These people from the Radiant Church may not have known that the 9th rank expert they sent to the prairie was actually killed by Zhao Hai. Otherwise, they would have some reservations in attacking Zhao Hai this time.

* * *

Oooh boi

Chapter 435: Wealthy Twin Stars

When the Light Mage saw Zhao Hai’s calm appearance, he couldn’t help but snort, “Young man, you’re quite insolent. You must know that insolent people don’t live for too long.”

Before Zhao Hai could reply, an old voice was heard, “To dare come to my Purcell Family wand acting unruly, don’t you think you’re being too much? I really don’t know what gave you the courage, young man, but you shouldn’t be too insolent. You must know that insolent people don’t live for too long.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to see an old man standing behind him. The old man gave out a strong and majestic aura. Although his hair was white, when seeing him standing there, one could feel as though they saw a ferocious beast crouching, ready to pounce at any time.

When the Light Mage saw the old man, his face couldn’t help but change, “So it seems like the Origin Sword Saint has arrived. Hehe, Senior is already too old, are your old arms and legs still function?”

Origin Sword Saint showed a faint smile and said, “Even if I’m old, I still have the decency to be disciplined for years. Not like you young people, these past several days, constantly shouting about killing, but still acting charitable. For this old man, killing is killing, there’s no other pretense in it.”

Hearing Origin Sword Saint, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. This old man was really amusing. Expressing this satire towards the Radiant Church helped him vent some of this pent up thoughts.

When the Light Mage heard the old man, his face paled, he looked at Origin Sword Saint and said with a cold tone, “The Radiant God is omnipotent, the great Radiant God isn’t someone a worldly person like you can understand. With the Radiant God, one can enter eternal bliss. Otherwise, you would be subjected to the eternal torment of hell. For you to slander the Radiant God, you will certainly be punished.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “What qualifications did the Radiant God have to punish me? If he was indeed real, then if he knew what you people who bear his banner were doing, then he would definitely punish you first.”

The Light Mage naturally treated Zhao Hai’s words as rubbish. He looked at both Zhao Hai and Origin Sword saint and then snorted, “Do you really want to contend with us with only the two of you? You’re really naive.” After that, there were two other people who appeared at the Light Mage’s side. The two men weren’t dressed as a Warrior or a Mage. Both of them wore normal clothes but were made of excellent quality materials. The two of them looked just like Big Merchants.

Zhao Hai was confused when he looked at the two persons. He already started practicing Battle Qi, but he didn’t feel any fluctuation from the bodies of the two people for both Magic and Battle Qi. This felt very strange.

Although feeling out 9th rank Warriors and Mages were very difficult. Zhao Hai can still feel them out using the Space. But these two people didn’t have anything on them.

At this time, Origin Sword Saint talked, “So you invited the Wealthy Twin Stars. Good good, you actually spent a lot of money to invite two famous Divergent Ability Users, doing so isn’t easy.”

Zhao Hai stared at the two people and then respectfully asked Origin Sword Saint, “Senior Sword Saint, did you say that the two of them are Divergent Ability Users? What type?”

Origin Sword Saint replied, “The Wealthy Twin Stars are famous in the continent for being Metal Divergent Ability Users. They are a pair of twin brothers, they love money as much as they love their own lives. They were initially merchants before they were deceived and lost all of their money. After that event, the both of them went ill. What they didn’t expect was that after they recovered, they actually developed Divergent Abilities. Both of them posses Metal Manipulation techniques, they could control anything metal under 100 jin. The two of them are also free assassins. If you pay them 100 jin of gold, they they would kill anybody in the continent, aside from a few notable people.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he turned his head to Origin Sword Saint and said, “100 jin of gold isn’t too much. It’s just 20 thousand gold coins. Such experts would actually kill people just for 20 thousand gold coins?”

Origin Sword Saint shook his head, “It’s 100 jin for each person, in other words, 40 thousand coins for inviting the two of them. Moreover, they love gold coins, all payments should be provided in gold coins. I really didn’t think that the Radiant Church would invite them this time. It seems like they really want to kill us today.”

When Origin Sword Saint finished speaking, one of the Wealthy Twin Stars said, “Senior Sword Saint really is formidable, you actually found out about us brothers. We brothers generally didn’t want to recklessly kill people, but the Radiant Church has offered us 400 thousand gold coins to deal with you, we just cannot refuse.”

Origin Sword Saint couldn’t help but stare, then his voice turned cold, “Four hundred thousand gold coins, the Radiant Church truly invested heavily this time.”

Origin Sword Saint didn’t mean that 400 thousand gold coins is a huge amount. In fact, for any established power in the continent, 400 thousand was nothing. But for a person to have 400 thousand gold coins on hand was something very rare. One had to know that people store their coins inside banks. They exchange these coins by handing over a crystal card that had its corresponding value. There was nobody who would carry around 400 thousand physical gold coins.

This was the problem with dealing with the Wealthy Twin Stars, they wanted physical gold coins for their commissions. They wouldn’t accept any other form or payment, Crystal Cards or so on. Because of this, not a lot of people can invite them, since withdrawing 200 jins worth of gold coin from the bank was a very troublesome thing to do.

Zhao Hai didn’t know of this, and he also didn’t care. He was only curious towards the Wealthy Twin Stars because of their Metal Manipulation Ability. Zhao Hai had the same ability, he wanted to see if he can learn something from the two of them,.

But Zhao Hai didn’t have the time to dwell on this since at this moment the Light Mage opened his mouth, “Enough with the idle talk, Begin!” Then he threw himself towards Zhao Hai.

With an intention, Zhao Hai made Zhao Wen appear in front of him. Then Zhao Wen transformed into a large mosquito before she fought with the Light Mage.

The Light Mage stared for a moment, but he immediately fought with Zhao Wen. At this time, the three Warriors threw themselves towards Zhao Hai as well. Origin Sword Saint, intended to block the three Warriors but he was blocked by the Wealthy Twin Stars.

At this point, nobody was blocking the three Warriors. For them, Zhao Hai was now like a fish on a chopping board, there was no escape.

But when they approached him, vines suddenly appeared on the back of Zhao Hai and curled towards them. The three warriors couldn’t help but stare slightly at Zhao Hai’s appearance. In the end, they didn’t give it much thought, they thought that Zhao Hai was one of those rare Plant Mages. But a Plant Mage’s fighting capabilities weren’t very strong. The vines were their most commonly used weapon, except in the forests, Plant Mages are pretty weak in any other place.

Moreover, their weapons can deal with Plant Mages. Metals were a Plans Mage’s worst enemy,

As they made their swords chop the vines off, they felt something strange. With their 9th rank strength they were confident in cutting those vines. But they didn’t think that the vines were actually very tough.

Their swords were basically incapable of cutting the vines. The vines took this opportunity to entangle their swords. And while the Warriors were stunned, the vines also engulfed their bodies. At this time, they felt that their bodies seem to be pricked by needles. Then they discovered that they didn’t have any strength anymore.

The one who attacked the three Warriors were naturally Cai’er. Cai’er was at the pinnacle of 9th rank. Otherwise, why would the other experts not dare approach Flower City. It was naturally because she had the strength to drive those experts away.

This strength was terrifying, clearly shown by how easily Cai’er managed to subdue three 9th rank Warriors. They were also injected with Cai’er’s poison, and that poison wasn’t a joke. Before her evolution, her poison could already deal with other 9th ranks. But now, after being upgraded by the Space, they it was rare for a 9th rank to resist the toxin.

The captured 9th ranks were not far from death. If not for their strength and vitality, they would have already died.

After attacking the Warriors, Cai’er didn’t stop and continued on to deal with the Wealthy Twin Stars. Even if the two’s strength wasn’t that formidable, they were still able to place the Origin Sword Saint in a deadlock. Because of their Metal Divergent Ability as well as Origin Sword Saint’s minimal understanding of Divergent abilities, there was no way for their fight to end very soon.

But now with Cai’er’s help, the situation was much easier to deal with. Before long, the two were also engulfed by Cai’er. It was estimated that they would die much sooner than the three Warriors.

Now, the only remaining person was the Light Mage. The Light Mage was simply not a match for Zhao Wen. One must know that Zhao Wen was a 9th rank Magic Beast, not something a Human 9th rank can contend with. Adding on to her improvements by staying inside the Space, even if she wasn’t peak 9th rank, she could still contend against anything below that level. With the innate superiority of Magic Beasts over humans, Zhao Wen didn’t suffer a single loss from fighting with the Light Mage, she was even on the winning side.

The Light Mage also thought that things weren’t doing so well, so he was thinking about escaping. Zhao Hai knew what he wanted to do so he smiled and said, “Go try and run.” Then with his mind, he made Little Jin appear on Zhao Wen’s back.

Little Jin’s body was already transformed into his Large Ape form. One should know that Little Jin was very well gifted in strength. Even if he was an 8th rank, his fighting strength was on level with common 9th rank experts. Therefore, he released Little Jin to support Zhao Wen.

Little Jin already knew what was happening, so when he came out, he immediately pounced towards the Light Mage.

Chapter 436: Level Up

Little Jin was now more like a Knight, but this knight didn’t use a weapon and instead used his own huge arms. And adding on his overbearing strength, the Light Mage became exhausted before long.

The Light Mage felt that the situation was becoming inconceivable. He didn’t know how Zhao Hai managed to get these Magic Beasts. One must know that 9th rank Magic Beasts are very difficult to come across. However, even if he only encountered one today, the other one not reaching 9th rank evident in how it was riding on the other one’s back, but both of its offensive and defensive strength were no less than a 9th ranks expert’s. This made the Light Mage very confused.

Although 9th rank Magic Beasts are stronger than 9th rand Human experts, 8th rank Magic Beasts were never as good as 9th rank Humans. Rank difference can never be compensated with racial traits. This fact was widely accepted by everyone on the continent.

But this understanding was shattered today because of this 8th rank Magic Beast in front of him that had the strength of a 9th rank. This was really inconceivable.

Origin Sword Saint had drawn back and didn’t participate in fighting the Light Mage. He already knew that the enemy had no chance of escaping. At the same time,  he was also startled, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai actually had such aces up his sleeves.

At this moment, Little Jin gave a shout as his body emitted a magnificent golden light. Then he moved and left Zhao Wen’s back. His figure soared in the air as it directed an attack towards the Light Mage, and surprisingly breaking the former’s guard.

It was not only Origin Sword Saint and the others who were shocked, Zhao Hai was shocked as well. But before he wondered what made Little Jin break through this time, a prompt came from the Space, “Massive amount of metal element energy has been received. Upgrading the Space. Space may now produce metallic ores, 100 ton per day output. Compatibility between Host and Metal element energy detected, upgrading Host’s Metal Manipulation Ability. Host can now freely control 200 jin of metal. Compatibility with Little Jin and Metal element energy detected, upgrading Little Jin’s strength and abilities. Space Ranch upgraded to Level 28, Space Farm upgraded to Level 35. Because of the Space’s promotion, monitor range increased to 15 thousand meters. Transmission Point quantity increased to 20. Because of the Metal element energy, plants in the Farm have evolved. Vines now have added metallic attributes, they are now more resistant to metal attacks.”[1]

Zhao Hai’s mind was blank upon listening to this. He didn’t think that he would gain so much from killing two Metal Ability users. The Farm actually levelled up to 35, while the Ranch rose to 28. Moreover, the Space can now produce metallic ores everyday. His metal manipulation has also increased. At the same time, Cai’er and Little Jin has also been upgraded, all of this seems too unbelievable.

However, Zhao Hai knew that the Space wouldn’t deceive him. If it said that it levelled up, then it certainly did level up. In other words, Zhao Hai’s strength has increased once again, this was a huge surprise.

While the Light Mage was stunned by the sudden appearance of the golden light, Zhao Wen made use of this opportunity to puncture its mouth into the body of the Light Mage. Before long, there was nothing left from the Light Mage aside from his skin and bones.

When Zhao Hai recovered, he immediately stopped Zhao Wen. Then he gave out a black gas before Little Jin and Zhao Wen vanished. At this point, they no longer have any opponents. Four 9th rank experts and two Metal Ability users actually died in less than a day.

Origin Sword Saint was blankly staring at all of this. He didn’t believe all of that just happened. One must know that a typical fight between 9th rank experts would take one or two months. Some special cases may even take 1 or 2 years. But now, the fight actually ended in less than a day. If Origin Sword Saint’s calculation was correct, then not even two hours had passed before the result was obtained The opposite party was totally exterminated, while Zhao Hai’s group was completely intact. This show of power was too astonishing.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the mood to think about Origin Sword Saint’s feelings, he just turned to the old man and said, “Sir Sword Saint, now that the matter here has been settled. I’ll have to go down and deal with those mercenaries before they run away, at the very least expelling them from Purcell Duchy.”

Origin Sword Saint recovered, he was also reminded of the people outside. He immediately stood firm and looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, then I have to trouble mister.” Then his body vanished with a flash.

At this time, Laura and the others appeared by Zhao Hai’s side. Megan held Little Jin on her bosom. Megan looked very surprised at Little Jin, she didn’t think that the little ape could actually change into such a ferocious form.

The fight outside was naturally seen inside the Space. Megan didn’t expect that the Little Jin that she loved to hug was that strong.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura and said, “Laura, did you hear that? Sir Sword Saint just called me mister.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Sir Sword Saint calling you mister meant that he regards you as an equal. On the other hand, Brother Hai, I didn’t think that Little Jin and Cai’er would get stronger.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I also didn’t think that Little Jin and Cai’er would be improved. Moreover, the Space levelled up as well. This is very good for us. And later on, the Multi-purpose Processing Machine wouldn’t be idle anymore. Since the Space can now produce metallic ores, we can make weapons from the machine.”

At this time, Shue suddenly knelt in front of Zhao Hai and with a serious voice he said, “Young Master, Shue has some words to say.”

Zhao Hai stared at Shue and said, “Get up, you can tell me while standing up.

But Shue didn’t listen, he kowtowed instead and said, “Young Master, Shue has always been disappointed with this world, but ever since Young Master has taken me in, you didn’t make me feel like an outsider. For this, Shue is very thankful to the Young Master. Shue has seen that after you absorbed the two ability holders, the Space levellup up. Young Master, Shue proposes that you kill me and make the Space absorb my ability. This way, the Space would level up again.”

Zhao Hai, Laura and the others stared blankly, then their faces changed. They didn’t think that Shue would have such thoughts. Zhao Hai replied with a flat tone, “Who told you that the Space levelled up after absorbing two Divergent Abilities?”

Shue replied, “This is Shue’s calculation. The Young Master has had a lot of undead, some of them are Mages, some of them Warriors. But those people wasn’t able to make the Space level up. Only those two Divergent Ability users managed to upgrade the Space. Moreover, it raised by five levels. Young Master, Shue thinks that as long as the Space absorbs Divergent Abilities, then it would get upgraded. This Shue doesn’t have any more aspirations in life, I only hope that I could help Young Master. If Shue’s ability gets absorbed into the Space, then it would certainly level up. This can be a great help to Young Master.”

Zhao Hai looked at Shue, then all of a sudden Shue’s mouth was knocked down as he fell to the ground. The slap made use of all of Zhao Hai’s strength. Shue’s face was swollen, one or two teeth might have been broken.

Zhao Hai looked at Shue and said, “This palm should have told you that your life is mine. I do what I want with it, it’s not for you to decide. What do you think your master sees you? A Magic Beast? I want to upgrade the Space, but not to the point of killing my own people. Remember this, if you dare say this again in the future, then I will have to drive you away. Now go back to my side and protect me.”

Although Shue fell to the ground, he immediately got up again. When he heard Zhao Hai’s words, he didn’t say anything and just returned to his young master’s side. This time, Shue has truly regarded Zhao Hai as his Master. If Zhao Hai were to tell him to commit suicide, he wouldn’t hesitate to do so.

At this time, sets of footsteps could be heard as Evan led some of his subordinates. When the 9th ranks came, Evan really wanted to assist Zhao Hai. But he was already delegated by Origin Sword Saint to look after his own family members. This was the reason why he only managed to arrive after those 9th ranks have been dealt with.

When Evan saw Zhao Hai, he seemed to have a complicated look in his eyes. But he immediately laughed and said, “Little Hai, you really are greater than you let off. With the Buda Clan under your care, glory would be flooding in. You shouldn’t forget about your uncle when that time comes.”

Zhao Hai looked at Evan and smiled faintly, “Uncle Evan is too polite. As long as Uncle isn’t afraid of being implicated. Uncle should know that the world is full of my enemies.”

Evan laughed, “Why do I need to be afraid, fear is useless. How could fear be useful in dealing with enemies? Hahaha. Right, Little Hai, what do you plan to do next?”

Zhao Hai coldly smiled and said, “The enemy seems to have some tens of thousands of troops remaining in Purcell Duchy. How could I just let them peacefully retreat? Wouldn’t it be too easy for them?”

Evan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Of course, I just feel like I have a little too few undead in my hand. I just want to increase their numbers.”

Evan couldn’t help but shiver. Although he didn’t know that Zhao Hai already had several hundred thousand undead, he still knew that Zhao Hai should have at least 60 thousand undead. Listening to a Dark Mage who has 60 thousand undead saying that he wanted more is too terrifying.

Zhao Hai seemed to not see Evan’s reaction as he released Alien, then he turned to Evan and said, “Uncle, do you want to come with us? In the shortest time, we would certainly expel those mercenaries from the Purcell Duchy.”

Evan stared at Zhao Hai ans shook his head, “Their attack had left a huge injury to the Purcell Duchy. I’ll take this opportunity to handle that matters of the Duchy. So I think I won’t be coming with you.” Zhao Hai nodded, and walked towards Alien before they left the city.

* * *

Raw says 15,000 kilometers… I say bs, that’s more than the earth’s diameter.. Maybe author typo. Let’s see

Chapter 437: Next Plan

All the forces in the continent didn’t expect this war to end so fast. It lasted much shorter than what they expected.

The end of the war was too sudden, too fast, and the victor seemed to be the Purcell Family, which were at the disadvantageous position since the beginning. Those with discerning eyes could see that the victory of this was was solely because of one person, Zhao Hai!

They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be a person from the Buda Clan, they also didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s prowess as a Dark Mage could be this strong. His enemies were simply looking to die. Most importantly, a Dark Mage was known for being able to increase his army as the battle continues on. Naturally, Dark Mages have their own limit as to how much undead they can command. However, this limit seems to not exist with Zhao Hai. The undead that he currently controlled has probably reached 100 thousand by now. This was the same quantity as a 7th rank Dark Mage can handle.

Although almost every Dark Mage didn’t summon undead, there were some of them who specialize in cultivating them. If these people use all of their energy to summon undead, they could summon at 6th or 7th ranks for an army numbering 100 thousand.

Naturally, all of these undead are common undead, unlike Zhao Hai’s advanced level undead.

However, those who didn’t face Zhao Hai in the battlefield had no idea how strong his undead were. Therefore, although they were surprised that Zhao Hai can control 100 thousand undead creatures, they didn’t pay much attention to this matter. What they paid attention to were some other points.

First, Zhao Hai’s status. When Zhao Hai revealed the Wild Dragon Banner, the people knew that Zhao Hai’s true identity was Buda Clan’s Adam Buda. He now changed his name to Zhao Hai, which surprised the people on the Continent.

In the past, the Buda Clan wasn’t very famous in the continent, this was because the Buda Clan were still emerging Nobles, for the major powers, this didn’t merit their attention. Only when the Buda Clan was given the Black Wasteland did they became famous. Everyone in the continent knew where the Black Wasteland was. For the Buda Clan to be transferred there was akin to giving them the death sentence. This was the reason why the name of the Buda Clan was still on the minds of everybody.

Second point, the toxin from the Water of Nothingness actually had an antidote. For the Radiant Church as well as the Great Clans, this was a serious attack. Before, the Radiant Church and the Great Clans would use the Water of Nothingness as a deterrent weapon against experts. No expert was willing to lose their strength, that would be worse than killing them.

Because of this, a lot of experts had no choice but hire themselves into the Great Clans as well as the Radiant Church. Because only by doing so will they be spared from the Water of Nothingness.[1]

But now, it was known that the Water of Nothingness has an antidote. For the Experts on the continent, this was definitely a good thing, because they didn’t need to be afraid anymore. Of course this information was also a huge blow to the Radiant Church.

Third point, the matter about the 9th ranks. The alliance between the Radiant Church and Boris had set out four 9th rank experts as well as two high-level Divergent Ability users. But with such lineup, they were still extinguished in less than two hours. This made all of those who were paying attention feel as though something was stuck in their throats, their hearts were jumping crazily, this development was too scary.

At this point, the major powers in the continent now had two things to consider, those powers under the control of the Radiant Church, and the matter about having Dark Mages in their armies.

It has been a long time since the last major war. Because of this, people have forgotten how terrifying Dark Mages were in the battlefield, they forgot the advantages of having Dark Mages.

But with the recent war in the Purcell Duchy, people now had an image of the Dark Mages’ appeal. For the profession to surprisingly turn the tides of war, this was something that all those who were paying attention to the event recognize.

Compared to all these people, Zhao Hai actually didn’t think much of these. After he eliminated the 9th ranks, he started to deal with those mercenaries who remained in Purcell Duchy.

The mercenaries didn’t expect Zhao Hai to kill the 9th ranks this quickly. They haven’t even thought that Zhao Hai would defeat the 9th ranks. Because of this, the mercenaries didn’t retreat far away, and instead, they even prepared themselves to attack Casa City.

Therefore, when Zhao Hai made his undead attack their camps, the mercenaries were ill prepared. And adding on the strength of the undead, all of them were immediately forced to run away. In the end, about 100 thousand managed to escape the Purcell Duchy, the other 100 thousand remained and would forever be part of Zhao Hai’s undead army.

After doing all of these, Zhao Hai gave Evan word that he would be leaving Casa City. He came to Purcell Duchy only to expel the attackers, he didn’t come here to do anything else.

Evan also understood Zhao Hai, and since he still had a lot of matters to deal with in Purcell Duchy, he didn’t stop Zhao Hai leaving.

Zhao Hai also knew about the amount of difficulties that Evan would face. Casa City was a big city, it cannot produce enough grain for its consumption, so the grains would have to be brought from outside. Although the Purcell Family had a stockpile of grain, it was not enough to feed everyone in the city. Even though the enemies didn’t manage to take down Casa City this time, they still managed to heavily damage the grain producing lands around the city.

So now, the Purcell Duchy was once again experiencing food problems. But this time, nobody decided to hoard the grains. The shops in the city also didn’t try to raise their prices. They knew that using this method to deal with the Purcell Family was no use.

Before Zhao Hai left Casa City, he also gave Evan a lot of grain, enough for the City to survive its food crisis. Since the Purcell Family would have to buy grain from someone, they might as well but from him.

After dealing with the problems of the Purcell Family, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately return to Sky Water City, instead, he went back to Iron Mountain Fort. He was ready to carry out his plan to make the 9th ranks in the Carrion Swamp his subordinates. With them on his side, the major powers in the continent would have no choice but see him as someone equal.

They weren’t afraid of other powers in the continent since they could just escape to the Space. But if those powers really did want to deal with Zhao Hai, he would have no choice but to hide inside his Space for his entire life.

Zhao Hai didn’t want that kind of life, he wanted to be able to give a good life to his people. So he had no other choice but to become strong and powerful. Although his status wasn’t low, it still came from Megan. At this rate, there wouldn’t be a lot of people in the continent who would give serious respect to the Buda Clan. The respect would have to be caused by the Calci Family.

But Zhao Hai already knew that depending on the Calci Family wasn’t a good choice. Nor does depending on Charlie. All of those scenarios are just him having fake strength, in the end, it wasn’t his own. He wanted to have strength and respect that was fully his. The Calci Family is a Great Noble Family, they could sacrifice almost anything for the benefit of the family. Although he was now their son-in-law, he could still be sacrificed at any time.

Moreover, Zhao Hai didn’t want to be know as the Calci Family’s son-in-law forever. In the future, he wanted people to regard him as the Patriarch of the Buda Clan, and not a son-in-law of the Calci Family.

…

This time, Zhao Hai was preparing to stay in Iron Mountain Fort for a few days not only because he needs to carry out his plan, but to take personal command of the fort and deal with those people who would be sent to the Black Wasteland by the major powers of the continent.

Zhao Hai was almost certain that that people would come and investigate him the moment he revealed his identity. Now, every power in the continent knew that he was from the Buda Clan. And they also knew that the Buda Clan was now residing in the Black Wasteland. From this, they would certainly send people to come and see the situation there.

If an ordinary person would come, then it would be easy, just kill them and that’s the end. But if they send a 9th rank expert, then matters would get complicated.

Therefore, after Zhao Hai returned to the Black Wasteland, he immediately released every single one of his undead. About 800 thousand undead roamed the entirety of the Black Wasteland. As soon as they see an intruder, they wouldn’t be polite.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also had Megan fully explore the Black Wasteland. Currently, the entire Black Wasteland was covered by Cai’er’s poisonous mist. Zhao Hai had also almost finished improving the land, making them fertile farmlands to be used in the future.

In order for these lands to be fully sustainable, Zhao Hai also began to prepare the waterworks system of the territory. As long as the waterworks gets completed as well as having watersheds implemented, the Black Wasteland would be transformed into the best farmland in the continent, making it the largest granary in the future.

These days, Megan was always in awe. She didn’t expect that the legendary Black Wasteland would look like this. And since it was still winter, the ground outside was full of snow. Megan grew up on the coastlines, she wasn’t able to see this scene before, this made her very excited everyday.

Aside from Megan, Little Jin was very excited as well. This little ape has not seen snow before. So when he came here, he was scared at first, but he quickly got used to it. He followed Megan and played around in the snow everyday, they enjoyed it very much.

Naturally, the factories inside Iron Mountain Fort were free for Megan to see. Especially the assembly line production that Zhao Hai has set up, which was an eye-opener for Megan.

Although Megan didn’t involve herself much in the matters of the Calci Family, she still learned a lot of things. So the naturally understood the usefulness of this assembly line method of production. Once could clearly see how it can greatly improve working efficiency.

Of course, there were some products that weren’t made using the assembly line method, examples of these were the blankets and carpets made by the Beastmen. Even if the method can be applied to those products, Zhao Hai chose not to do so, since if they did so, the carpets and blankets would lose their special touch. The products would be the same as those produced by the Multi-purpose Processing Machine.

When a person creates something, his feelings and efforts would naturally be reflected on his work. And this sentiment would be felt by those who bought the product. This was the biggest difference between products made by a machine and made by hand.

It has to be acknowledged that there were some things that were better when made by a machine, it can even be said to be close to a perfect product. But this perfection itself was precisely its shortcoming.

Those who make something by their own hands would find it impossible to make zero flaws in their work. But these flaws carry the feelings and personal touch of its maker. People arent’ perfect, and products that they make should be the same, perfectly made products do not exist.

Zhao Hai didn’t allow blankets to be made using the assembly line method. However, the other things were. Zhao Hai had a lot of products being made in Iron Mountain Fort. And most of these were made with the assembly line method.

Zhao Hai didn’t prevent Megan from telling the Calci Family about his production method. In all honesty, the only thing that Zhao Hai didn’t want Megan to tell the Calci Family was the situation in Iron Mountain Fort, anything other than that, Megan can freely say.

Zhao Hai knew that Megan had feelings for him, because of this, he didn’t want to place Megan in an awkward position where he couldn’t talk about anything in Iron Mountain Fort. He knew that there was no way for Megan to keep everything a secret, otherwise she wouldn’t have anything to talk about with her family, and Zhao Hai didn’t want that.

While they were staying in Iron Mountain Fort for several days, Zhao Hai began to deal with the Magic Beasts inside the Carrion Swamp. In fact, Zhao Hai had already regarded Carrion Swamp as his own back garden. And since the beasts in his back garden weren’t very obedient, all he needed to do was make them his subordinates.

After Zhao Hai greeted Green and the others, he lead Laura and the others to Flower City. The moment they arrived at Flower City, Megan begame stunned. Although Iron Mountain Fort had become a second Flower City, the place was too small. It was the first time for Megan to see a big city, enough for 500 thousand people, just like this.

The most important thing was that almost everything in the city was comprised of Cai’er. In the endless facade of flowers, Megan almost lost herself, the place was too beautiful.

Excluding Megan, even Laura and the others were continually awed by the beauty of the city. Everytime they come here, they couldn’t help but stare blankly at everything. The place was that beautiful and magnificent.

In order to make Megan happy, Zhao Hai decided to stay inside Flower City for three days. In the meantime, Zhao Hai let out Zhao Wen to see what the other 9th rank experts of the Carrion Swamp were doing, and then select their first target.

Since they weren’t very strong, they would start looking for the weaker ones. And after bringing it to the Space, they would continue on to the next target, slowly moving towards the stronger Magic Beasts. This way, the Magic Beast Alliance would get weaker and weaker until Zhao Hai subdued every single 9th rank inside the swamp.

* * *

What logic is this?

Chapter 438: Defending the Black Wasteland

The third day after Zhao Hai and the others arrived at Flower City, assassins started appearing on the Black Wasteland. These people brought various antidotes for poison as they investigated everything inside.[1]

However, they soon discovered that they were mistaken. Even if they drank some antidotes so that they wouldn’t be poisoned temporarily, they didn’t expect to get besieged by a large number of undead. Moreover, these undead were very powerful, and since they’re undead, they didn’t need eyes to see the intruders. This meant that stealth techniques were utterly useless. All of their methods of stealth were not effective in dealing with the undead.

It was already known in the continent that the most headache inducing enemies that an assassin could face were undead creatures. This was because most of their methods aren’t very effective against the undead. Hidden weapons were useless, poisons were useless, and assassinations were useless. In the minds of the assassins, the undead were a huge pain in the ass.

For the assassins, to have headaches is when dealing with ordinary undead. They had no other fate than to die under Zhao Hai’s undead.

Zhao Hai didn’t make his undead deal with the assassins by using their instincts. Instead, he grouped up a thousand undead and gave them to an Advanced Undead to command. When the assassins enter the Black Wasteland, they didn’t immediately attack them since it would be very troublesome. When those people penetrated deeply into the area, they will surround them and then kill them in one go.

When Zhao Hai heard that the first assassins had arrived in the Black Wasteland, he cared about it. He already knew that this day would arrive. As long as these people enter the Black Wasteland, then they wouldn’t be able to come back. After that, people would be too scared to enter his territory.

At the current time, the other powers wouldn’t be sending in 9th rank experts to enter the Black Wasteland. 9th rank experts weren’t as common as cabbages, they cannot just dispatch them casually.

Common 9th ranks weren’t very willing to be dispatched easily, especially into the Black Wasteland. The Black Wasteland was too close to the Carrion Swamp. All of them knew that the 9th rank Magic Beasts inside the swamp were very strong. Most 9th ranks in the continent weren’t their opponents.

More importantly, in the last few months, the poisonous mist from the Carrion Swamp has begun to spread to the Black Wasteland. All who entered barely managed to get out. Even if they did get out, the poison that they got from the fog eventually killed them.

This poison was the same as those that proliferated in the Carrion Swamp. Because of this, ordinary people didn’t dare to enter the Black Wasteland.

Naturally, this development was Zhao Hai’s arrangement. Zhao Hai wanted to instill the idea that the Black Wasteland has become the second Carrion Swamp.

Zhao Hai’s plan was very effective. In the beginning, when the Seven-colored poisonous mist started to spread to the Black Wasteland, some people started to examine what happened inside. Upon seeing nobody inside, they declared that the Black Wasteland has become a place full of beasts and poisonous mist.

This development naturally made the people of the Purcell Duchy very restless. They neighbored the Black Wasteland, if the Seven-colored poisonous mist continued to spread, they would be the first people to experience bad luck. This made the people from the Purcell Duchy attach great importance to the Black Wasteland.

Fortunately for them, when the poisonous mist spread to the whole Black Wasteland, it didn’t go any further. Instead, the mist engulfing the Black Wasteland became thicker and thicker. People may be able to survive entering the place in the beginning, but now, nobody managed to survive.

But ever since Zhao Hai revealed the Buda Clan’s Banner, there were a lot of people who entered the Black Wasteland. These people were assassins sent by various nations. They also made sufficient preparations, they brought all kinds of detoxification potions as well as protective masks. But all of these were useless, these people wouldn’t survive. If the only thing present in the Black Wasteland was the poisonous mist, then they might have a chance to survive. But unfortunately for them, in the Black Wasteland, the poisonous mist wasn’t the only thing they need to look out for.

These assassins entering the Black Wasteland was like a pebble entering the ocean. This fact made the Great powers feel suprise. They didn’t think that the Black Wasteland would become this terrifying.

But to Zhao Hai’s disappointment, they didn’t send out 9th rank experts to do their investigations. Just as what Zhao Hai thought before, 9th ranks weren’t as common as cabbage, they couldn’t just be casually deployed, especially to such a dangerous place. This made the powers hesitate in sending them over.

Although the great powers were somewhat wary of the Buda Clan, they weren’t afraid of them. After all, the Buda Clan was just another entity in the vast continent. Except for Boris who has a huge enmity with the Clan, most people didn’t take the Buda Clan too seriously.

Even if Zhao Hai had a lot of good things in his possession, those wouldn’t’ be able to drastically affect the continent’s economy. For a lot of Nobles, only when you touch their sources of income would they seriously come and deal with you.

In simple words, Zhao Hai didn’t pose a threat to their interests, so they didn’t go and intentionally provoke Zhao Hai. Naturally, the Radiant Church and Boris were different, their enmity with Zhao Hai was deep, there was no resolving it.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these, as long as the continent didn’t send in 9th ranks, he can carry on his plans in the Carrion Swamp.

At this time, undead filled the ground of the Black Wasteland while Blood Hawks filled the skies. The defense of the land was already very solid. Even if a 9th rank came in, Zhao Hai can still deal with it. Thus, Zhao Hai didn’t really worry about anything.

After playing around in Flower City for three days, Zhao Hai was already ready to carry out his plan. But before carrying out his operation, Zhao Hai did another thing, it was to absorb parts of the carrion swamp into the Space, whether it be the mud or the plants in the swamp.

Zhao Hai chose a place in the swamp and absorbed a chunk of it into the Space. Taking in small insects, plants, and the mud. Then he took another island sized chunk into the Space.

These two absorptions made the Space’s farm reach level 45. He could now cultivate most of the plants. But it was a pity that the Ranch didn’t get upgraded, so Zhao Hai didn’t know what happens when the Ranch and Farm reaches level 30 and 40, respectively.

After completing all of these, Zhao Hai began to deal with the Carrion Swamp’s 9th rank Magic Beasts. For other people, dealing with those 9th rank beasts was difficult. But for Zhao Hai, it was much easier, he already had Zhao Wen and Cai’er,

After Zhao Hai asked Cai’er about the positions of the 9th ranks, they started to plan their course of action. One must know that dealing with 9th ranks wasn’t an easy thing. If they made the 9th rank escape, then it would certainly alert the other 9th ranks in the swamp, and eventually the entire Flower Protection Alliance. By that time, Zhao Hai’s losses would be great, so he needs to be careful.

For the first target, Zhao Hai must choose someone who wasn’t very strong and was someone who didn’t get into contact with the others too much. This type of target would have the most chance of succeeding.

After Cai’er and Zhao Wen discussed for a long time, they finally decided on their first 9th rank target. This Magic beast was a flying type 9th rank Magic beast. It’s form was a Skylark, it flies quickly, has poison magic, and is very cowardly. This made it choose to not get in contact with other Magic Beasts often. His strength in the swamp was quite common, not the same as Zhao Wen. So Zhao Hai decided on this target as well.

Because of the Skylark’s personality, its territory was placed in an odd and remote location, ensuring that it would be the least attacked place. Adding this to the other reasons, this made Zhao Hai choose him.

But Zhao Hai was still very careful, no matter what, this was a 9th rank expert, someone not easily dealt with. Otherwise, 9th ranks wouldn’t be treated like nuclear weapons.

Flower City didn’t undergo a change since Zhao Hai and the others directly appeared their using the Space. Therefore, the 9th ranks defending Flower City didn’t take note of the differences happening inside.

Since Cai’er and Zhao Wen spent these past several months inside the Space, there shouldn’t be any huge change that happened inside Flower City. Therefore, the positions of the 9th ranks shouldn’t have changed as well.

Time didn’t have any meaning to 9th ranks. For them, what they needed to do was to comprehend the heavens and hopefully achieve supreme existence.

Ninth rank experts would generally close up for several years at a time. Therefore, when Zhao Hai enter the swamp in the past, even if he let out a small disturbance, the 9th ranks didn’t give it much attention.

Having decided on their target, Zhao Hai began their operation. Zhao Hai opened the monitor and released Zhao Wen, who was holding the Ghost Staff, on the northwest side of Flower City.

This was the direction towards the Skylark’s territory. But before arriving there, they needed to pass through the territory of another 9th rank Magic Beast, one having the form of a Platypus.

Platypuses were also present on the other parts of the continent. Moreover, its impression on the people was that of a very docile Magic Beast. If you don’t attack it, then it wouldn’t attack you.

But the Platypus inside the Carrion Swamp was different. It was because the Platypus’ defensive measure was poison. Adding on to the environment inside the Carrion Swamp, this made the Platypus on the other parts of the continent very different from the ones inside the Carrion Swamp.

As far as Zhao Wen knows, this 9th rank Platypus was one of the more terrifying existences in the swamp. It has tremendous strength as well as defensive power. The most important thing about this Platypus was that it was the most powerful poison expert in the entire swamp. This made him part of the top existences in this place.

* * *

Dead soldiers -> Assassins,.. I was really hoping that they would be some special profession before. But it seems like they weren’t

Chapter 439: Two-in-One

But the reason why Zhao Wen decided to pass through the Platypus’ domain was because even if the Platypus was strong, its attitude towards those inside the Carrion Swamp was very good. Moreover, it cared extremely well about rookie 9th ranks. Thus, Zhao Wen dared to go through its territory all the time.

However, if one wanted to pass, it was good practice to pay him greeting. This was respect meant for those who were strong. Unlike Humans, Magic Beasts have great regard towards those who had great strength. As long as they weren’t in war, they generally don’t challenge those who had higher strength than them

After Zhao Wen entered the Platypus’ territory, she stopped and then passed a message through her divine sense, “Blood Devouring Mosquito pays a visit to Sit Platypus.”

Before long, a calm voice was conveyed, “It’s you, what is the little mosquito doing in my territory?”

Zhao Wen immediately replied, “Sir, I just want to pass through your territory to reach Skylark. I have some business with him, I just came to specifically pay my respects to mister.”

Just as Zhao Wen voice fell, a platypus appeared in front of her. The platypus was very huige. It’s body had a length of 50 meters, it was also about 20 meters tall. Zhao Wen’s base form looked like a single dot in comparison.

Platypus had golden hair all over his body. The hair shook gently with the wind and looked very healthy. He also had a pair of small eyes, a huge duckbill, short limbs and a short and stout tail. Although he was very large, he didn’t give people any fear at all, instead, he looks very cute.

But Zhao Wen didn’t dare underestimate him. Although 9th rank Magic Beasts can change their form freely, most of them stayed in their true form. For the Platypus to be this large was a testament to his might as a 9th rank Magic Beast.

Zhao Wen said to Platypus, “I have seen mister. I want to go to Skylark, but I need to pass through your territory to do so.”

Platypus smiled and said, “You’re interesting kid. It seems like you’re not quite familiar with being a 9th rank, most of them don’t wander around. What business do you you have with Skylark.”

Zhao Wen stared at Platypus, then a sudden idea popped into his mind, “Sir, I have this recently acquired Magic Staff. Actually, this staff is a Spatial Equipment. Moreover, I also have my subordinates live inside it, I enter it from time to time as well. But the space inside the Staff is very big, I still haven’t found its limits. I heard that Skylark is very fast, I want to ask him to come with me inside this space and find its boundaries together.”

Zhao Wen was now getting more and more intelligent. What she said was actually made to bait Platypus. If she can deceive Platypus into entering the Space, then inviting other 9th ranks inside the Space would be much easier in the future.

Sure enough, when Zhao Wen said this, Platypus looked strangely at the Ghost Staff, “Does it really have a huge space? I have heard about spatial items, those have a lot of uses. In here, only Old Mouse can use Space energy. But his Space energy can only open a small pocket space, it didn’t have much use. Is it really true that the space inside of your staff is very big?”

Hearing that Platypus seemed to be tempted, Zhao Wen quickly replied, “It’s true, the space inside is very big. I haven’t found its boundaries even after flying inside for ten days. Thus, I’m going to ask Skylark for help, we’ll fly in opposite directions and measure how big the space is.”

Platypus looked very interested, he looked at Zhao Wen and said, “Can you open the space and let me in? I haven’t seen such a magical space yet.”

Zhao Wen quickly agreed, “Of course.” Zhao Hai was observing Zhao Wen inside the Space, when he heard Zhao Wen’s words, he immediately opened a spatial rift right beside Zhao Wen. Then Zhao Wen looked at Platypus and said, “Sir, please.” Then she stood inside the rift. Seeing Zhao Wen do this made Platypus relieved. One must know that Space energy can certainly kill 9th ranks. Platypus was afraid that Zhao Wen was deceiving him, he feared that when he was halfway through the rift, it would close, killing him in the process.

Now that he saw Zhao Wen’s action, Platypus nodded then crawled his body through the spatial rift.

After Platypus, Zhao Wen also entered, then at this time, a prompt was heard, “Platypus-type variation beast detected. High attacking strength, extremely dangerous. Subjugation function initiated, Platypus surrenders. Level 50 beast. Can be raised inside the Space. Needs four feed per hour, can be purchased in the shop. May reproduce 8 times, six children every time.”

:Ranch upgraded to level 31. Medium World requirements met, Ranch and Farm will now combine and become a medium world. Host has the right to name the world. Host has full control of the world. Perfect ecosystems can now be achieved, making all organism inside the Space self sufficient. Additional 100 mu of Farming Ground added, host can use every land in the World to plant as well, but they grown at a normal rate.”

After the prompt finished, the Space flashed a white light. The Ranch and the Farm combines. Zhao Hai can now see the Magic Beasts he raised freely going around the Farm. Beside the Farming Ground, the Magic Beasts could also go to the Villa and the Processing Factory, they can go almost everywhere. Moreover, when Zhao Hai stood on the vila’s balcony, he can clearly spot a sea. Also, on the side of the villa, a river came flowing, one could see it full of fishes jumping and leaping out of the water. When someone exits the villa and goes through the Farming Ground, one could arrive at the seaside and enjoy the beautiful fine white sand beach.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to enjoy the beautiful beaches right now. He quickly opened a file as it appeared on the monitor, showing every change that happened in the Space.

Now that the Space levelled up, the Farm and the Ranch had been combined. He can breed beasts and plant crops any way he wants. But besides the Farming Ground, all other places wouldn’t’ be able to speed up the plant’s growth. It was the same with the Magic Beasts, anything that exceeded the 10 thousand limit would only grow in their normal rates. Naturally, Zhao Hai can capture and kill Magic Beasts inside his Space, this was because he had absolute authority here. Even if a 9th rank expert enters, Zhao Hai can make them unable to use their abilities in just a flick of his hand. Inside the Space, Zhao Hai is a god, each word from him is akin to a heavenly decree.

He can also exercise control over the digitization of animals in the Space. For example, if he allows 10 thousand Argali to have accelerated growth this day, he can make them into normal Argalis the next day while having another batch of 10 thousand Argali digitized and  have sped up growth.

And since the Space has been transformed and wasn’t divided between the Farm and the Ranch anymore, the overall level of the Space was now Level 38. It was calculated by adding the levels of the Farm and the Ranch and dividing the result by two.

If Zhao Hai wants to transform the Space once again, then he needs to wait until it reaches level 50.

However, he can now buy level 45 seeds and can now buy level 31 animals. Although he can buy animals like Platypus, those he purchased could only have 6th rank strength, like an ordinary Platypus in the continent. It was just like what Zhao Hai expected, it was impossible for 9th rank Magic Beasts to produce 9th rank offsprings.

Because of the combination of the Ranch and the Farm, Cai’er can now assume the tasks assigned to Mu’er as well. Now, Cai’er can manage the various Magic Beasts. Mu’er also has 9th rank strength and could now also fight outside of the Space, similarly she could also manage the plants inside the Space.

However, the Bread Trees that Cai’er had planted before cannot be left unattended anymore. Therefore, Zhao Hai had Cai’er control the beasts in order to not attack the Bread Tress.

But Zhao Hai chose to not strictly impose this prohibition. He knew that there were a lot of herbivores inside the Space, some of them would eat grass while some would certainly munch on the Bread Trees as well as their fruits. Zhao Hai decided to just let things happen, after all, this was a World and he already had sufficient area inside the Farming Ground. Also, it would be impossible for the Magic Beasts to eat all of the Bread Trees inside the Space since the Space was now a medium world, having an area no smaller than the Ark Continent.

After the Space transformed, it now has more attack functions. Zhao Hai can use Cai’er, Mu’er, the blood mosquitoes, the Magic Beasts, the Undead, the Profound Glacial Liquid, and the Fly Swatter to attack. Even if the Ranch and the Farm has combined, Zhao Hai can still use these basic functions provided by the two.

For Zhao Hai, this development was very good. These will certainly increase Zhao Hai’s strength. Although he still wasn’t a 9th rank expert, he was sure that even if he didn’t use Zhao Wen, Platypus, and Cai’er to attack, he can still contend with 9th rank experts.

Laura and the others were looking at the changes that were happening outside and were too surprised to speak. They didn’t think that the Space would change this much, it was really very mysterious. However, they already experienced several of these transformations before, so they just stayed still and didn’t disturb Zhao Hai who was still understanding the Space.

Chapter 440: Deception Squad

While they were waiting for Zhao Hai to fully comprehend everything in the Space, Laura and the others waited in of the villa while discussing the various Magic Beasts present outside.

At this moment, Zhao Hai looked at them and faintly smiled, “Why are you watching inside? Go out and see them, those Magic Beasts wouldn’t be afraid of you.”

This was also a function of the SPace. Those who Zhao Hai deemed to be his people would be tagged by the Space as friendlies. Because of this, all Magic Beasts inside the Space not only were unafraid of Zhao Hai’s group, they would even get close to them.

When Laura and the others heard Zhao Hai’s voice they turned their heads to look at him. Zhao Hai noticed that on their arms were Magic Beasts. Laura held Platypus on her arms, Megan hugged Little Jin, while Meg had Zhao Wen on her shoulder. Seeing these women holding 9th rank beasts as though they were plushies would certainly make an ordinary person go crazy.

Zhao Hai gazed at Platypus, at this point, its size was reduced, it now looked very cute and lovely. It was no wonder that Laura liked it.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, are you sure that those beasts wouldn’t run away when we go approach them?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They won’t, they will even be intimate with you. So go out and play with them.” Laura and the others cheered and then ran outside.

Zhao Hai smiled and then turned his head to Mu’er, “Mu’er, since the Space really didn’t need you to manage it anymore, how about exiting the Space and coming along with me? You can transform into a type of clothing, my belt would be good.”

Mu’er didn’t oppose. He was an obedient child, otherwise he wouldn’t be bullied by Cai’er. Mu’er transformed his form and slowly turned into a golden belt before coiling around Zhao Hai’s waist. Although it seemed low-key, the belt’s appearance fully expressed noble elegance, it was very attractive.

Zhao Hai looked at the belt that Mu’er has turned into and gave a satisfied nod. Then he walked outside and couldn’t’ help but smile. Laura and the others were playing with small Magic Beasts who didn’t grow up yet. The adult Magic Beasts seem to not mind and just continued grazing around on the grass.

This image showing the harmony between man and nature was something Zhao Hai had only seen on television. But Zhao Hai knew that compared to television, what he was seeing was real, in this world, man and nature could truly exist harmoniously.

Zhao Hai suddenly remembered that he could name the Space. He didn’t think too much and directly named it Haven, a homage to how this place was a paradise.

After playing around the Space for the whole day, the group returned to the villa when evening came. Zhao Hai had also invited Green and the others to the Space and told them the changes that happened.

WHen Zhao Hai invited Green over, he also experienced another difference in the Space. After the Space got upgraded, the Transmission Points were also upgraded. But this upgrade wasn’t an addition of one or two point, but instead a qualitative upgrade. As long as Zhao Hai had been to a place, then he could establish a Transmission Point there at any time. In other words, as long as that place was recorded into the Space’s monitor, then Zhao Hai can go there anytime.

This function was too formidable, it added to the usefulness of the Space’s monitor. At this point, Zhao Hai even felt that the massive Ark Continent had turned into the Ark Village.

Naturally, the number of places that Zhao Hai had been to wasn’t a lot, but this wasn’t a huge disadvantage. No matter what, as long as he had been to a place, and had the place recorded into the monitor, then Zhao Hai can go there. With these, he can still go to quite a few places.

Upon hearing the changes that happened to the Space, Green and the others were very happy as well. For them, this was very good. The more formidable the Space becomes, the more advantages they would have.

Looking at Green’s happy expression, Zhao Hai also smiled, then he said, “In fact, Zhao Wen’s method today gave me a reminder. We can actually get the 9th ranks without resorting to violence. Instead, we can just trick them into going inside the Space and have it subdue them. Now that we have Zhao Wen and Platypus on our side, inviting those 9th ranks would be much easier. Grandpa Green, what do you think?”

Green thought for a moment then nodded, “We can try that. Now that the Space is strong and has five 9th rank experts, it was better if we refrain from using violence. Otherwise, if we suffer any damages, then it wouldn’t be very good.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I also think that we need to try tricking them into the Space first. If we can do that, then we’re fine, but if we can’t, then we have other choices than to take them by force.”

Green agreed, “Also, we should finish this matter in the Carrion Swamp as soon as possible, or else the day when the Magic Beasts rampage to the Black Wasteland would come. When that happens, the losses that we’ll suffer would be too great. Additionally, if the 9th rank Magic Beasts come, then it would be more troublesome. It would be better if we do take care of this matter right here.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, we will certainly solve that problem this time. We don’t want to worry about this hidden problem in the future.”

After resting for a day inside the Space, Zhao Hai released Zhao Wen and Platypus. This time, their target would be Skylark.

Platypus and Zhao Wen stopped just right outside Skylark’s territory. They knew that if they were to directly enter, Skylark would think that they came to attack him. From Skylark’s cowardly nature, he would certainly run away immediately. When this point comes, it would be very difficult for Platypus and Zhao Wen to catch up to him.

Therefore, as long as they don’t enter Skylark’s domain, Skylark won’t run away. After they stopped, Platypus opened his mouth and said, “Skylark, come out and meet me.”

Platypus’ status was higher than Skylark, because of this he didn’t include respectful words like when Zhao Wen talked to him before. Also, if he was too polite, it would certainly alarm Skylark.

Before long, a small petite Skylark drilled out from the poisonous mist. Although Skylark wasn’t that small, when compared to Platypus, she really looked very small.

However, even if Skylark was small, in exchange, she gave people a sense of dexterity. And with its shape, it appeared very cute.

Skylark stared when she saw both Platypus and Zhao Wen. With a calm tone, he asked, “What matter made the two of you come here?”

Her sound was very clear, and from the tone, one could hear a feminine voice, it seemed very fragile. It sounded like the tones that birds sing in.

Platypus looked at Skylark and smiled, “Younger sister Skylark, we came this time because of Little Wen. She obtained a Magic Staff which turned out to be a Spatial Item with a very huge space inside. Both of us had already checked but we weren’t able to see its boundaries. Therefore, we thought we could approach you for help in finding the edge of this space. Is younger sister Skylark willing to help?”

Skylark stared, she didn’t think that Platypus would go find her for this matter. She looked at her visitors and said, “Is what you’re saying true? But even if we do find the edge of this space, what use can we get out of it?”

Platypus smiled faintly and said, “To tell you the truth, we’re planning to occupy the space inside. But since it was too large, we’re afraid that there are other experts present inside. If we manage to offend some experts, then we wouldn’t be able to peacefully practice inside. Therefore, we thought about surveying the entire space first and make sure that there was nobody else inside. This way, we can peacefully comprehend the heavenly laws inside and maybe even break through.”

Skylark stared, she looked very moved by Platypus’ words. All 9th rank experts strive in understanding the laws of the heaven. If one manages to succeed, then they would definitely become a supreme existence. If what the space really did provide even has smidgen of possibility, then it was definitely worth it to look inside.

But Skylark still has some worries, “Why did you look for me? Why not somebody else?”

Platypus smiled, “Naturally because you’re the one closest to us. When Little Wen got her staff, the first thing she wanted to do was approach you. But since she needed to pass through my territory, we decided to check the inside together. However, neither the two of us managed to find the space’s boundaries. Therefore, we wanted to look for help, so even if there really was something inside, we can deal with it much easier. You’re the one closest to my territory, so we came to you first. So how about it? Do you agree? If you agree, then we’ll go and see the space right now. If we still can’t do it, then we’ll go find another one. But if you don’t agree, we can also go away and find someone else.”

Even if she sees that they seem to be telling the truth, Skylark still couldn’t help to hesitate. She was very timid and cautious, but she also understood that Platypus was stronger than her and that Zhao Wen’s speed was not much worse than her. If these two really wanted to deal with her, then they wouldn’t need to spend too much trouble. After looking at their appearances for one more time, Skylark began to believe them.

After thinking for a moment, Skylark said, “If it is true, then I will naturally agree. But I need to go inside first, right, you should accompany me in.”

Platypus smiled, “Alright, no problem. Little Wen, open the space.” Zhao Wen nodded then help up the Magic Staff as a spatial rift appeared. Zhao Hai was already prepared for this, as long as the Magic Staff was held high, he would immediately open up a spatial rift.

When the rift opened, Zhao Wen didn’t immediately go inside. Platypus turned to Skylark and said, “Younger sister Skylark, I’ll be going in first” Then his body flashed into the space. Zhao Wen stayed outside, she looked at Skylark and said, “Elder Sister Skylark, I shall wait for you here, If I go in as well, the rift would vanish.” Then she stood at the rift.

Looking at the two’s performances, Skylark didn’t hesitate. Her bad immediately flashed as it entered the Space. After Skylark entered, a prompt was heard.

In the end, Skylark was graded as a level 45 Magic Beast. Before she can be raised inside the Space, naturally the Space still needed to subdue her. But to say that Platypus and Zhao Wen deceived her was not totally right. This was because inside the Space, the elemental energies were indeed quite strong. And because of the plants inside the Space, the energies were becoming stronger and stronger.

Plants absorb nutrients from the soil. After they die, they would rot and become nutrients themselves. Their fruits, however, can become food for animals and people. Because of this, plants can be considered as the most selfless creatures.

In the Space, this principle stays true as well. The Space would be providing the plants with nutrients and in turn they would be giving back some energies into the Space, making the Space upgrade. Which in turn, allows more plants to be grown in the Space. And now that it has become its own world, the energy released by the plants became even more powerful. Animals release energies as well, this made the elemental magic present in the space stronger and stronger.

Since Zhao Hai’s group spent time inside the Space in a daily basis, they weren’t able to detect this small change. But for Skylark and Platypus that were just introduced to the Space, they could clearly feel the difference. This also made them want to continue staying inside the Space, they didn’t want to return to their territories anymore.

After subduing Skylark, Zhao Hai proceeded to their next target, now with Skylark added to the squad. This made the deception squad increase by one, additionally, this also made their story much more credible, making Zhao Hai’s plans more likely to succeed.

If this plan was used against 9th rank Human experts, then it may not succeed. This was because 9th rank human experts have experienced a lot of things in their life, they were already acquainted with various schemes and plots just like today’s action. They would certainly be on guard and wouldn’t trust anyone very easily, this would make it very impossible for them to enter the Space.

But the 9th rank Magic Beasts inside the Carrion Swamp aren’t quite the same. They lived in a world where plots and schemes were basically non existent, the only matter that they cared about was protecting Flower City as well as cultivating. Because of this, even the cautious Skylark was deceived into entering the Space.

As more and more 9th ranks enter the Space, the Space was also getting stronger and stronger. At the same time, the success rate of the plan became higher and higher. The other 9th ranks just didn’t believe that these group of 9th ranks would scheme against them, there was no need to. If the deception squad really wanted to deal with a single 9th rank, it would be very easy, a roundabout way was just too impractical.

Stemming from such thinking, there was no battle that happened since all of the 9th ranks were deceived into entering the Space and become its fighting strength. At the same time, they also became Zhao Hai’s subordinates.

But Zhao Hai didn’t excessively restrict their freedom. He allowed them the choice of cultivating inside the Space or in their territories inside the Carrion Swamp. Zhao Hai also made it clear that he wouldn’t force them to do anything.

However, these Magic Beasts weren’t fools, they knew which one brought them great benefits. Because of this, they didn’t go back to the Carrion Swamp to practice and instead stayed inside the Space. In any case, the Space was truly big, they can just pick a place where they would practice and stay there.

Chapter 441: The New Swamp

But Zhao Hai also found out that these 9th ranks from the Carrion Swamp had a special habit. They had to absorb the Seven-colored poisonous mist in their bodies in order to practice. They would slowly circulate the mist within their body and make it part of their  attack.

However, even if the Space didn’t’ have a poisonous fog, Cai’er’s main body was here. And with the addition of the Space’s pesticide, Cai’er’s poison was still sufficient for them, this made it possible for the 9th ranks to continue practicing inside the Space.

When the Space became a World, it didn’t worsen, conversely, it instead became better.

When Zhao Hai was on earth, he heard someone saying that the there was one thing that Humans can be described as, Viruses. Viruses don’t have any purpose other than to destroy the place they live in. It was the same with Humans, every place they settle in would most definitely be destroyed. For Earth, Humans acted like what viruses do to bodies they stay in.

On the other hand, even if the Space had a lot of animals, it had no man-made destructions inside. One could say that this was a completely closed up world, everything all goes according to nature. Although the Space can digitize, which was an exception, it still can’t do any large effect on the Space.

Now, Zhao Hai was considered to have subdued the entire Carrion Swamp. He didn’t know in the beginning, but upon checking, he found out that there were thirty-six 9th rank Magic Beasts in the Swamp. Adding Cai’er, Little Jin, and Mu’er, Zhao Hai now had thirty-nine 9th ranks. With this amount of 9th rank experts, Zhao Hai can now be considered to be one of the most powerful forces in the continent.

However, Zhao Hai was not planning on using these 9th ranks. Even if this amount of power was terrifying, Zhao Hai had no plan of world domination. What he only wanted to do was protect the Black Wasteland as well as the Carrion Swamp. He really didn’t want to do any other things.

To be honest, Zhao Hai knew that this was quite selfish. Back on earth, because of the different times, people pursue material things. If you ask them if they have any great ideals, then they wouldn’t have anything. People generally aren’t very nationalistic since they all wanted to think of their income, to have an easy life. Zhao Hai knew that there was something wrong with this. He also knew understood that he needs to be one thing, which was being responsible.

A man who knows his own responsibility and was responsible is a real man. Although Zhao Hai has some shortcomings, he recognizes his responsibilities and is trying to be more responsible. For him, this was his biggest merit.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to kill people just because he wants to, he didn’t want to start wars either. Therefore, even if he’s very powerful right now, he only yearns to protect this little part of the continent that he calls home. He doesn’t want to bully others, he doesn’t want to dominate the world. Doing such things can only evoke war, and during wars, it was the commoners who suffer the greatest. Zhao Hai didn’t want this outcome.

…

Now that he has increased his 9th ranks, the Space’s level has become level 45, which was the Farm’s level before the transformation.

Zhao Hai was quite unsatisfied with this, but he knew that there was nothing he could do. With the Farm and the Ranch becoming one, levelling up became even harder, especially in higher levels.

Level 45 was already very good, but this has no substantial effect on the Farm. At most, Zhao Hai can now plant level 45 plants, not much improvement.

But even if the Ranch also had no good improvements, Zhao Hai was content with. After all he only needs 5 levels until level 50, when he reaches that level he can then breed Divine Beasts.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that reaching these 5 levels will be very difficult. More than 30 9th ranks allowed the Space to reach level 45, and all of them didn’t even advance the Space’s level by 10. Zhao Hai didn’t know how many more 9th ranks he needs to subdue in order to fulfill the requirements for these 5 levels.

In the end, Zhao Hai placed this worry on the back of his mind. He prepared to finish up in Carrion Swamp so that he can return to Sky Water City.

God’s Grace Day was less than 10 days away, so he wants to return to Sky Water City and take a look. Not only does he want to go back to Sky Water City, he also wants to take a look at Jade Water City.

Also, it has been a long time since Megan joined Zhao Hai. At this point, the Calci Family should have been quite worried. Moreover, it wouldn’t good for Calci Family’s little princess to be absent during God’s Grace Day. The family dotes heavily on Megan, because of this, Zhao Hai must give the family some face.

There wasn’t much problems left in the Carrion Swamp. What Zhao Hai needs to solve at this point was the matter about the swamp’s poison. For those inhabitants who hadn’t become strong Magic Beasts yet, they needed to expel the toxin from their bodies. In the past, what they did was to run towards the Black Wasteland and expel it there.

Zhao Hai also thought about this problem in the past. The place between Iron Mountain Fort and Carrion Swamp had a small river. The water from that small river was from the lake inside the mountain. That water has been upgraded by the Space and can be used to detoxify the beasts.

But there were a lot of beasts inside the Carrion Swamp, and some of them wouldn’t be able to make it to the Black Wasteland. Because of this, they had no choice but find other places inside the swamp to expel the poison. This caused the poisonous mist inside the swamp to become stronger and stronger, making the time between expelling poison for the beasts even shorter as time goes by.

It would be great if this poison was removed, however, at the same time, it wouldn’t be good. If the poison inside the swamp were to vanish, the Magic Beasts inside would be disadvantaged. If those Magic Beasts loses their poison, their overall attack strength would be seriously affected.

So if Zhao Hai doesn’t think about this carefully, he would be hurting the swamp’s Magic Beasts. Upon hearing from the other 9th ranks, Zhao Hai found out that other than Zhao Wen, there hadn’t been any new 9th rank Magic Beast appearing in the Carrion Swamp lately. And this has been for a long time. This was because at this point, most Magic Beasts inside the swamp cannot survive the swamp’s poison anymore. Since the toxicity of the mist got stronger, the expelled poison returned to their bodies. Because of this, most Magic Beast would die, they simply cannot survive long enough for them to reach 9th rank.

After discussing with the 9th ranks, they had reached an agreement that Zhao Hai would set up several springs inside the swamp. These springs would contain the Space’s water. After setting the springs up, the 9th ranks would lead the other beasts to drink from the spring, this way the problem about the toxin would be solved.

Now that Zhao Hai’s Monitor had recorded the entirety of the Swamp, this wasn’t a big of a problem. From Zhao Hai’s calculation, the area of the Carrion Swamp and the Black Wasteland is not smaller than Aksu Empire. Instead, it was actually much larger.

One must know that when the Buda Clan obtained this territory, it was already their permanent domain. This bestowment was recognized by the Radiant Church as well as the other empires. Even if Empires change from one ruler to another, the Buda Clan would forever hold this territory. Because of this Zhao Hai hoped to increase their lands.

In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t dare improve both the Black Wasteland as well as the Carrion Swamp since he didn’t have the strength to protect these two places.

But now, it was different. Zhao Hai currently has enough strength to defend these two places. Even if other people becomes envious of his property, they can just try and face his numerous undead.

However, Zhao Hai had no plans of revealing the state of the Black Wasteland at this time. After all, he still needs to construct more infrastructure here and he needs to acquire a lot of resources in order to do so. If the other powers were to find out, they would certainly impose limitations for Zhao Hai, and this wouldn’t be good for him.

Zhao Hai wanted to slowly accumulate his wealth, therefore, after receiving the 9th ranks, he immediately went and established those detoxification springs. In the future, the 9th ranks can just lead the other beasts on order to help them remove their accumulated poisons.

After doing this, the problem with the black soil was finally solved. Later on, they wouldn’t worry any longer and Zhao Hai be assured that he could open his lands to the outside world in the near future.[1]

Solving the matters inside the Carrion Swamp took them almost one month, now, God’s Grace Day was only 5 days away. The Calci Family has also sent a letter to Zhao Hai, asking him to return to Sky Water City as soon as possible.

It was not only the Calci Family, Charlie sent a letter as well, inviting him to check Jade Water City. Naturally, Charlie was not in Jade Water City, so he asked Zhao Hai to visit his place back on Carson City.

Zhao Hai didn’t decline, not matter where he was, he can still return to Iron Mountain Fort in a flash. Regardless of where he stayed, it was still like he’s in Iron Mountain Fort, so there was no reason for him to not accept the invitation.

After making his decision, Zhao Hai immediately prepared himself to head towards Sky Water City. Megan was also missing her home. Although she didn’t tell Zhao Hai about it, one could clearly see it from her expression.

Zhao Hai told Green about their plan to leave, to which Green didn’t oppose. Green and the others knew that since the Buda Clan has revealed their banner, Zhao Hai’s responsibilities became even more. Moreover, the eyes of the continent were now staring at them. At this time, Zhao Hai should maintain his good relationship with the Calci Family as well as the Third Prince Charlie.

Although it can be said that the current strength of the Buda Clan wasn’t any less than those at the top of the continent, and they didn’t even need to fear the might of the entire Human race, Green and Zhao Hai didn’t think about this. This was because Zhao Hai didn’t like war, and Green loved the Human Race.

* * *

That thing that made the Black Wasteland Black.. Poisoned soil

Chapter 442: Grandly Opening the Main Entrance

Zhao Hai and the others appeared outside Sky Water City. This time, they weren’t in a tight schedule so they first looked for a remote place before ZHao Hai released his bull-pulled carriage and slowly headed to the city.

The giant horned bull-pulled carriage, the Wild Dragon War Banner, and Alien, were the three things that identified Zhao Hai. No matter which three were present, people would know that it was Zhao Hai who arrived.

It was because of this that when Zhao Hai’s bull-pulled carriage entered Sky Water City, he was immediately escorted by the city’s garrison troops as it headed toward the City Lord’s Mansion. Even if these garrison troops didn’t give Zhao Hai face, they still had to give respect to Megan. They were very clear about how Smith loved Megan.

After nearly a month of constant exchanges of information, Zhao Hai’s reputation had spread throughout the continent. People on the continent now knew about this Dark Mage as well as the Buda Clan.

Major powers in the continent didn’t think that the Buda Clan, who vanished for one year, would actually return stronger than ever.

If one really counted, the time before the Buda Clan regained its power wasn’t long. Shortly after they were reassigned to the Black Wasteland, Zhao Hai appeared on the continent and then continued to slowly spread his reputation, attracting the interest of major forces. It was just that people didn’t realize that Zhao Hai was actually the head of the Buda Clan, the famous crippled child from the Aksu Empire.

What was even more noteworthy was the fact that Zhao Hai had managed to get his hands on the cure for the Water of Nothingness. This made him the center of attention of the entire continent.

The Water of Nothingness have been pressuring the powerful experts of the continent. They were afraid of being plotted against and unknowingly drinking the Water of Nothingness. If they reach this point, then no matter how loud the complain, nobody would listen to them.

But now that Zhao Hai appeared, it was like having a huge obstacle being removed out of their way. For him to be able to solve the toxin of the Water of Nothingness meant the others who were affected could get cured as well. For the various experts, this was certainly good news.

It can be said that Zhao Hai’s status on the continent became something that wasn’t much worse than a Patriarch from a Great Family. This was because he has the capability.

People knew that during the war in Casa City, not only did Zhao Hai obtain near 100 thousand new undead, he also managed to exterminate several 9th rank experts of the opposing party.

The 9th rank experts weren’t only attacked, they were exterminated. What did this mean? It meant that Zhao Hai himself also had 9th rank experts up his sleeve, and their numbers should be quite large.

When they heard about this, the people of the continent were startled. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have such method. They knew about the Buda Clan’s demise, this was mainly because they didn’t have any 9th rank experts. But the Buda Clan surprisingly acquired several of them this time, can 9th ranks be this easily obtained?

But while the others were surprised about this information, the Calci Family, on the other hand, were rejoicing. In the past, Zhao Hai told them that as long as they don’t send four 9th rank experts after him, then those they send wouldn’t be able to return. But neither Smith nor Randolph actually believed this. The only reason the Calci Family let go of their grudge with Zhao Hai was because the situation had gotten a lot more complicated.

Ever since they received word that Zhao Hai eliminated several 9th rank experts in Casa City, Smith and Randolph both felt a wave of fear after their initial surprise. Although they knew that the Purcell Family had a powerful 9th rank expert, Origin Sword Saint, the other part had four 9th rank experts, as well as two Advanced Divergent Ability Users. For Zhao Hai and Origin Sword Saint to destroy that lineup meant that Zhao Hai wasn’t lying to the Calci Family before.

Under such circumstances, Smith and Randolph had formally accepted Zhao Hai. They knew that even if it was the Calci Family, the four 9th ranks wouldn’t be killed that easily. If they were to be attacked by four 9th rank experts, they would still win, however, it would be a bitter victory.

And from the looks of it, Zhao Hai seemed to not have lost that much even after killing those experts, this made Smith very startled.

In the past, they always interacted with Zhao Hai as though they had the higher position. If it weren’t for Megan marrying Zhao Hai, it would be hard to say where the family’s relationship with him would end up.

Even if Megan still wasn’t married to Zhao Hai, Randolph was still planning on renouncing their engagement. In his opinion, Zhao Hai’s identity was in no way comparable to Megan.

But now it was different, Randolph and Smith now regarded Zhao Hai as someone of equal status. They currently weren’t thinking that Zhao Hai was not worth Megan, they also placed Zhao Hai in a special position in their minds. They decided that the way they interact with Zhao Hai must be changed.

Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about any of these. The reason why he participated in the Purcell Duchy war was to reveal to the continent the strength of the Buda Clan. He wanted to let the continent think twice about underestimating his clan.

Zhao Hai and the others quickly arrived at the City Lord’s Mansion. When they arrived, the group couldn’t help but stare, this was because the direction that they were led to was the main entrance of the mansion.

No average person can walk through the mansion’s main entrance. If your status wasn’t up to par, then you don’t have the right to pass through here. Therefore, Zhao Hai only passed through the side entrance in the past. Because of his good relationship with Smith, as well as his engagement to Megan later on, he was allowed passage to the side entrance, otherwise he wouldn’t even be able to pass through.

But when Zhao Hai returned this time, Smith actually gave the command to receive them through the main entrance, and more importantly, Smith was there waiting for them.

Zhao Hai came down from his carriage and immediately walked towards Smith before giving a bow, “Uncle Smith, why did you come personally? Right, why did you open the main entrance this time? I’m not familiar with this arrangement.’

Smith looks at Zhao Hai, he saw that there seems to be no changes to the young man’s demeanor, he couldn’t help but feel happy, he smiled and said, “This is my father’s orders, in his own words he said that you have the qualifications to walk through the mansion’s main entrance. We, the Calci Family, recognize your status in behalf of the continent.”

Zhao hai nodded, then walked together with Smith towards the Mansion with a smile. Zhao Hai knew what Smith meant.

When a Clan becomes a Great Clan, they need to have the recognition of some other Great Clan. The Calci Family greeting Zhao Hai with the opening of their Main Entrance meant that they recognize the status of the Buda Clan, for Zhao Hai and his clan, this was a very important matter.

The influence of the Calci Family on the continent was very huge. Although they were suppressed by the Radiant Church, Great Nobles aren’t that easily pressured. Even if the suppression from the Church did have an effect to the Family, the impact was not that great overall.

For a high profile Family like the Calci Family to recognize the Buda Clan, this would certainly affect how the continent views the Buda Clan in the future.

Smith didn’t become polite with Zhao Hai and invited him directly into the living room. Inside, Randolph was waiting. The living room wasn’t a place where anybody can just enter. Since Zhao Hai was engaged to Megan, him and his people were allowed entrance, the others were invited out of the room.

Randolph didn’t keep appearances this time, he stood inside the living room while waiting for Zhao Hai and the others. When he saw Zhao Hai arrive, Randolph showed a smile, and went forward to greet Zhao Hai himself. Although Randolph didn’t say anything warm, compared to how he interacted with Zhao Hai in the past, this time was much better.

After the group entered the living room and sat down, Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Good, Little Hai, what you did was really fantastic. You’ve shown the power and prestige of a Dark Mage, good job. Let’s see if those other fellows in the continent dare underestimate us Dark Mages again.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It was also time to let them know. There were no major wars in the continent for these past years, and they had forgotten what Dark Mages can do. This greatly contributed to the success of the Radiant Church’s suppression in addition to the bribes that the church sent. With what I revealed this time, those Nobles would know that the battlefield is a Dark Mage’s domain. The Radiant Church may have given them benefits, but they would still have to use these benefits to build their army. And since they needed to carefully manage their armies, they would now consider adding Dark Mages to their roster knowing how effective the profession is during wars. I believe that a lot of people would change their views of Dark Mages after this.”

Randolph nodded and said, “Right, these years, those who wanted Dark Mages become fewer and fewer. Some nobles think that raising Dark Mages wasn’t worth it. This time, you made them understand that Dark Mages are worth the resources.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “ God’s Grace Day would arrive in a few days. I’m afraid that we only have today to spend time here. Tomorrow, we have to head towards Jade Water City. Does Grandfather have things he wishes to request?”

Randolph shook his head and said, “I don’t have any. Tomorrow, I must also prepare to head towards Carson City, Smith will also be there. Little Hai, time is tight, will you be able to catch up to the capital if you go to Jade Water City?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Third Prince wanted me to go to Carson City, I’m also preparing to give him a visit. When I arrive at Jade Water City, I will immediately head towards the capital after taking care of a few things.”

Randolph nodded, then he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, recently the Third Prince seem to have acquired a lot of marine products. Does this have anything to do with you?”

Zhao Hai didn’t hide the truth from him, he smiled and said, “A couple of days ago, I went to the deep seas and had my undead scour the waters. You should know about the properties of the undead, so I had no qualms about having them get marine resources for me.”

Randolph nodded and didn’t talk anymore, he knew that these marine products weren’t something that he could get his hands on. This was because those had already become the Third Prince’s business. If he meddles, the might offend the Third Prince, and that would be too disadvantageous to the family.

Chapter 443: Important Matter

Randolph didn’t want to offend Charlie not because he was afraid of the Third Prince. It was just that he didn’t want to offend Charlie right now. The struggle for the throne was still going on. Randolph didn’t want to support any of the Princes as well as offend any of them. This was a matter that Randolph didn’t want to get involved in.

Zhao Hai didn’t tell Randolph about the beer and rice wine. This was because they still hadn’t made a method to mass produce them, also, Zhao Hai didn’t want to reveal them too soon.

The beer and the rice wine was a unique product in this continent. Zhao Hai wasn’t planning on cooperating with another person, he already has Charlie and the Calci Family.

Zhao Hai turned to Randolph and said, “Grandpa Randolph, does me supporting the Third Prince have any effect on you? If I stop supporting him now, then I would be offending him. This wouldn’t be good for us.”

Randolph nodded and said, “It won’t affect us. You cooperating with Charlie wouldn’t have a great impact to the Calci Family, rest assured. In fact, in the continent, Great Clans also participate in succession battles, however, they do it indirectly. This way, if they fail, there won’t be any repercussions. But if they succeed, the benefits they get would be substantial. When you joined the Third Prince’s side, you and our family were still enemies. We only reconciled after you got engaged to Megan. You supporting the Prince before that was already known by the people. This would assure that the Calci Family wouldn’t be affected.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “But even if doesn’t affect you, I’m still engaged to Megan in the end. From here on out, I need to consider the Calci Family in my decisions. This time, I revealed our Buda Clan because I wanted to show the continent what kind of clan Megan is getting wed to. I want them to know that that I have the strength to do so. I don’t want Megan to be made into a joke.”

Megan sat beside Randolph, when she heard Zhao Hai, her eyes couldn’t help but redden. She didn’t think that Zhao Hai also had that reason.

Randolph nodded, “Very good, Little Hai, you did very good. Megan didn’t make a mistake. You will certainly be a one of my Calci Family in the future. Right, no need to eat at another place, I’ve already prepared a meal for you. Let me show you my hospitality.”

…

After eating their meal, Zhao Hai and the others rested inside Sweet Plum Courtyard while Megan returned to her own place. She actually wanted to stay in Sweet Plum Courtyard, however, the madam asked her to stay with them. She had no other choice but to comply.

When Zhao Hai arrived at Sweet Plum Courtyard, he immediately went to the Space along with Laura and the others. More recently, they have been staying in the Space more. If they don’t have any special thing to do, then they would stay inside the Space.

When the madam and Megan arrived at her room and sat down, the madam looked at Megan and said, “Megan, how was this time’s journey with Zhao Hai? Were you in danger during the battle?”

Megan shook her head and said, “No, mother, how could I possibly be in danger? I didn’t even get to go somewhere, we’ve just stayed inside a safe area inside Casa City. I didn’t even get to see the battlefield.”

The madam nodded and then asked more, “Did four 9th ranks really attack Casa City? Are there two Divergent Ability users present as well?”

Megan nodded, “Yes, four 9th rank experts, one Light Mage, three Warriors. The other two were Divergent Ability Users and should be quite famous in the continent. I asked Elder Brother Hai and he said that the two of them were known as the Wealthy Twin Stars. Did you hear about them, mother?”

The madam stared, then she nodded, “I did. These two were Metal element Divergent Ability Users. They’re highly skilled. Moreover, they hadn’t been caught even after several years.”

Megan nodded, “I also heard about that from Elder Brother Hai. But those two people were already turned into Advanced Level Undead. Brother Hai also said that those two should have accumulated a lot of coins. If we get to have them, then we shall acquire quite a fortune.”

The madam smiled, “Little Hai really knows how to get money. Indeed, it would be quite a fortune. Those two have been desperately acquiring money all these years. And they only want gold coins, nothing else. This time. Little Hai would surely get a lot of gold coins.”

Megan smiled and said, “But we haven’t gotten it yet. These days we had a lot of things to take care of after the war. It hasn’t been very easy.”

The madam looked at Megan’s face and smiled, “Really? Right, Little Hai’s marine products, did he really acquire them himself? Where does he get them?”

Megan already thought about the excuse along with Zhao Hai. So when the madam asked her a question, Megan immediately replied, “Naturally, there’s no use in deceiving people. He got those items from the area around Ape Island. There were almost no people there, so there are a lot of good products to be harvested. But for the magic beasts, Brother Hai didn’t want to get a lot of them. He didn’t want to have the area be like the coastlines, where there aren’t any good items left.”

The madam nodded then asked Megan, “Where did you go after the sea? Did you go to the Buda Clan’s place? Where is it?”

Megan looked at the madam and said, “We did go to the Buda Clan’s place, but mother, I cannot tell you the location right now. Brother Hai trusted me and told me that I can’t reveal the location of the Buda Clan. So I cannot tell anyone, so please don’t ask.”

While looking at Megan, the madam couldn’t help but sigh. She knew that it would be like this. She understood Megan’s character, if the didn’t want to open her mouth, then there was no use in further asking.

The madam sighed and said, “Alright, I won’t ask anymore. Has Zhao Hai been kind to you these past few days? Was he good to you? Are you treated the same as Laura?”

Megan smiled and said, “Elder Brother Hai has been good to me, and he treats me the same as Sister Laura. We are usually very free, and when we do, we always spend time and talk together. Brother Hai said there’s still a lot that they could do in the sea. I also want to contribute to the family, so I also find things that we can cooperate with. Right, since we talked about this, I remembered something that I have to tell Grandpa.” Then she got up and left.

When the madam looked at her daughter leaving, she pulled her over and said, “What happened? Why do you have to talk to your Grandfather? Can you tell me?”

Megan smiled, “Telling this to you would be no good, it would be useless, you can’t do anything with it. Only Grandfather can find this useful, come, mother, let’s go quickly.” Said Megan as she pulled her mother and walked out the room.

Randolph and Smith were in the study, they still didn’t go rest. In truth, when they met Zhao Hai today, they were quite happy. Not only did Zhao Hai’s attitude toward them remain unchanged, but also because of his attitude towards Megan.

Zhao Hai’s manner towards Megan was very good, he looks after Megan very well. This was what they always wanted to see. If Zhao Hai’s feelings towards Megan were very good, then their princess would have a good home to return to. And with Zhao Hai’s good relationship with Megan, this also meant that he would be closer to the Calci Family and will give them enough face. This was definitely a good thing for the family.

Now, all the large forces in the continent knew that Zhao Hai’s strength wasn’t that much less from an established noble clan. He was even stronger than old nobles like the Purcell Family. The only weak point to the Buda Clan were their connections.

But Zhao Hai’s personal connections cannot be said to be weak. His relationship with the Purcell Family was quite substantial. The Purcell Family wasn’t among the oldest nobles, but their connections to the continent cannot be underestimated. Now that Zhao Hai had helped them deal with their recent matter, they would certainly give him help. This wasn’t a small matter for Zhao Hai.

Moreover, Zhao Hai was also the Calci Family’s son-in-law. If Zhao Hai needs something, they cannot just ignore him. He also had strong connections with others, like the Third Prince Charle, as well as the Shelley Family. At this point, Zhao Hai was an existence that cannot be ignored by all the great powers in the continent.

Facing with this Zhao Hai, the Calci Family was unable to pick out his flaws. At this point, Randolph had truly treated Zhao Hai as one of them. This was also a Great Nobles’ way of doing things. If you consider someone to be one of you, you should support them fully and protect their well-being. On through this way could they be rewarded in the future.

After Randolph and Smith discussed for a while, Randolph sighed and said, “Smith, I’ve been very hard on you lately. I’m now old, I only stay at the headquarters everyday. My judgement about the matters of the continent aren’t as good as you. Your big brother and your fourth brother are quite good, but they actually lacked the vision to be the Patriarch of our big family. We cannot count on little three as well, he was fully concentrated on cultivation, let’s just hope that he can reach 9th rank one day. Then there is little five, oh!”

Randolph sighed, he was not a fool. As a Patriarch of a Great Noble Family, how could he not understand? He just liked Juwan too much that he made a mistake in his judgements. But now, he knew what he needed to do.

To be honest, Randolph was very disappointed in Juwan. Juwan’s vision was absolutely low, he was very short sighted. If Randolph hands the family over to him, then the fall of the Calci Family wouldn’t be far off. So how could Randolph just allow this to happen?

Smith looked at Randolph and didn’t know what to say. He was bent on wanting the best for the Calci Family. But to say that he didn’t strive for the position of Patriarch was impossible. On the contrary, he really wanted to be the Patriarch. He believed that as long as he had the position, then he could certainly make the Calci Family greater than it is now.

At the same time, this was also the first time that Smith saw this side of Randolph. This was the first time he saw his father admit his mistake in front of him. This was really strange for Smith, but it dawned on him that his father was now very old, he will only get weaker with time.

Smith sighed lightly and comforted Randolph, “Father, it’s alright, it’s not as serious as you think. Although little five looks useless, but you have to recognize that he has his uses. Look, if the Calci Family were without flaws, then the troubles that he’s caused wouldn’t have reached this far.”

Randolph smiled and sighed, “My vision is not as good as little Megan, haha. Alright enough talking about this, Little Hai is very good. At this time, he revealed his clan in a way that the continent wouldn’t dare make a move on him while startling them with his might at the same time. He did things orderly, and wasn’t very anxious. He is soft when he can, and be ruthless when needed to. And from what I saw earlier, he seems to like Megan. This made me relieved. We must treat him very well as a part of our family. I understandd that he’s a very sentimental person, let’s support him fully and our Calci Family would surely obtain benefits.”

Smith smiled and said, “Father, rest assured, I already seen this part of Little Hai. Otherwise, why would I wed Megan to him?”

Randolph nodded and said, “With the support of Zhao Hai, the Third Prince’s chances for the throne would surely increase. This is also good for the family. I think, if necessary, we must give our full support towards Charlie. After all, Little Hai is now one of us. If he fails, there wouldn’t be any benefits for us.”

Smith nodded. At this time, Phil’s voice was suddenly heard. “Madam, Young Lady, why did you come? Old Master and the Young Master are discussing inside.”

When Randolph heard that Megan and the madam has come, he quickly said, “Megan and Gemma? Let them in.” Gemma was the name of the madam, but the people prefer to call her madam.

Megan couldn’t wait for too long and directly pushed the door open. When she saw Randolph. She immediately ran over to his side and said, “Grandpa, I remembered something, so I came to you.”

Randolph looked favorably at Megan and said, “Little Megan, you’re already getting married. You shouldn’t keep acting like a child.”

When Megan heard Randolph, she pouted and said, “Grandpa, you must listen to me. This matter is related to the future our Calci Family. If you won’t listen, then I won’t tell you.”

When he heard his granddaughter’s words, Randolph and the others couldn’t help but give a smile. Megan hadn’t been like this before. But now, she seems to be thinking about the future of the family. Naturally, they would find this amusing.

Randolph smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll listen to what little Megan has to say. For it to surprisingly affect our Calci Family’s future. Hahaha. This isn’t the same as being engaged, your words seem to be very big.”

Chapter 444: Running Water

Megan looked at Randolph and snorted, “If it really wasn’t important for our Calci Family, then I wouldn’t be telling you. Grandpa, I know that the family has a lot of factories. But I can say that the output of any of our factory wouldn’t hold up to one of Brother Hai’s. Producing the same product, even if Brother Hai’s factory had 100 people, it can still beat the output of our Calci Family’s factory with 300 people. It’s output wouldn’t be able to beat Brother Hai’s factory.”

When Randolph heard Megan, he couldn’t help but stare. Then he immediately understood what Megan was getting at. With a straight face, he said, “Little Megan, do you mean to say that Little Hai has a way to increase production? And that you know about this method?”

Megan looked at Randolph, and with a proud expression, she said, “I know Brother Hai’s method. Hehe, I must say that Elder Brother Hai is really intelligent. We haven’t thought of this method.”

Randolph looked at Megan and said, “What method? Megan, tell me quickly, you know how much Grandpa gets anxious.”

Megan smiled and said, “Elder Brother Hai called it the Assembly Line Production. Let’s take our family’s ceramic factory as an example. Right now, if a potter wants to make a piece of ceramic, the time it takes from taking the soil to making the ceramic would take several days. But Grandpa have you ever thought about it? How about we divide the acquisition of the soil, separating the clay, making blanks ceramics, and then the drawing of the flowers into their own separate tasks. Someone would dig the soil, then pass it over to the one who separates the clay, then to another worker who will make the blanks, and lastly onto the person who will draw the designs. This way, the work would flow smoothly from worker to worker like running water. With this, their degree of efficiency would be increased.”

Randolph and Smith were smart people, so they immediately understood Megan’s words. They still need to try it, but they already imagined that this would be possible.

Randolph became excited as he stood up and repeatedly praised, “Good, fantastic, this is fantastic. Right, right, what Megan said could really increase the output of our ceramics. Hahaha. Little Megan, you really didn’t lie, this will really affect the future of our Calci Family.”

But suddenly, Randolph stopped, he turned to look at Megan and said, “Megan, did Little Hai agree to tell us about this matter? If he didn’t, then this would affect your future relationship. You must know that this matter isn’t something that could just be spread around.”

Megan smiled and said, “Be relieved, Elder Brother Hai agreed.”

Randolph gave a satisfied nod and smiled, “Does Little Hai really have factories? Who mans those factories?”

Megan smiled, “Some human slaves, he also brought over some slaves from the Beastman Prairie. Currently, there are over 1000 slaves working in his factories.”

Randolph nodded, he didn’t ask about the Buda Clan’s location, he knew that they couldn’t be inside the Black Wasteland, that place was already a forbidden place in the continent. Zhao Hai’s home must have been in a secret place, and Zhao Hai would surely refrain from revealing it.

Seeing Randolph not asking about the Buda Clan’s location, Megan relaxed, then she said, “Grandpa, Elder Brother Hai said that the Buda Clan’s present location is a secret. He said that I cannot tell you for now, please don’t get angry.”

Randolph looked at Megan and smiled, “What? Just because he tells you not to tell Grandpa, then you won’t tell Grandpa?”

Megan strenly replied, “Grandfather, Elder Brother hai trusted me, so how can I be unfair to him. Therefore, I will not tell you, I would have to be unfair to Grandpa.”

Randolph laughs and patted Megan’s head, “Silly thing, how can Grandfather get angry, this is something you decided to do. Little Hai has no obligation to tell the Calci Family about his clan’s location. You are now engaged to Zhao Hai, him trusting you is a blessing.You are now a member of his Buda Clan. Naturally, you would be anxious for them, Grandpa wouldn’t be angry because of this.”

Megan held Randolph’s gentle hand, her eyes were red and she didn’t speak nor made any noise. Then after a moment, she said to Randolph in a soft voice. “Grandpa, Elder Brother Hai trusted me, he also treated me very well, just like how he treats Sister Laura and Sister Meg. Meg grew up with Brother Hai since she was little, so Brother Hai was her heaven. Laura gave up all of her property and had her family members transfer to Brother Hai’s domain. It was no question that Brother Hai trusts them very much. But I belong to a Great Clan who stood among the top of the continent. For Brother Hai to trust me despite this fact is really huge to me. So I cannot tell Grandpa about their location. But I can say that Brother Hai’s strength is leagues higher than what you imagine. You must know that what Elder Brother Hai showed at this point was but a small part of his strength. I hope that the Calci Family wouldn’t get in conflict with the Buda Clan, because I’m very sure that the one who will suffer in the end would be the Calci Family.”

Randolph stared with a surprised expression at Megan, “Megan, are you sure? Is Little Hai really that strong? You should know that the Calci Family didn’t just have one or two 9th ranks, does he really have the strength to make our family suffer a loss?”

Megan smiled bitterly, Randolph will never think that Zhao Hai would possess a thing such as the Space. With only his 800 thousand 8th rank undead army, not to say the Calci Family, even the Rosen Empire would find it hard to stop him. And adding his close to 40 9th rank experts, let alone making the Calci Family suffer, Zhao Hai could completely exterminate it without a sweat.

Randolph looked at Megan’s expression and didn’t need her to say anything before he understood. He just nodded and said, “Alright, be relieved, Grandfather knows what to do. Right, Megan, will you come with me to Carson City tomorrow or will you join Zhao Hai to Jade Water City?”

Megan smiled, “I’ll go to Jade Water City to take a look. Brother Hai also has a shop there, he wants to check it out. The Manager is Sister Laura’s subordinate. And because of the previous urgent matter, Brother Hai had to delegate a task over to him. This time, Brother Hai wants to see how it is doing.”

Randolph nodded, “Alright, you can go with Little Hai since he’ll also be heading to the capital. Oh, I really hope that things go wrong. This way, the marine products would go our way, those bring huge profits, what a pity.”

Megan smiled and said, “Don’t worry Grandpa, we’ll have our share of those marine products in the future. It’s just that the supply is quite low, there was no way for us to get some.”

Randolph smiled, “Little Hai really does have an innate skill for business. He already has Laura on his side, but it seems like the Buda Clan is having quite some difficulties in other aspects. No wonder little Megan wanted to learn so much about business, hahaha.”

Megan became embarrassed as her face turned red, “Grandpa, don’t talk nonsense. The Clan is doing very well. You didn’t know what they were in the past, but they are much stronger now. There was also Elder Brother Hai’s battles, he was really amazing.

Randolph smiled and said, “Come on, no need to touch up your Elder Brother Hai’s face. Haha. Alright, you’ve been working hard these days, go and take a rest. Didn’t Little Hai say that he would head to Jade Water City tomorrow? Go get some sleep so that you can wake up on time.”

Megan nodded, and said her goodbyes with a smile, “Alright Grandpa, then I would be taking my rest.” The she stood up and went back to her own room.”

After Megan left, Randolph turned his head to Smith and said, “Smith, do you think that what Megan said was true?”

Smith forced a smile and said, “I’m afraid it is true. Even if that girl had her heart taken by Zhao Hai, she still wouldn’t joke around when it comes to our Calci Family. It seems like there are still many cards that Little Hai didn’t reveal, this youngster isn’t very simple.”

Randolph nodded, “The most terrifying thing is the intelligence of this kid. He may have thought that people would come to find his place so he didn’t say anything and just let those people go to the Black Wasteland. I already heard that the poisonous fog there has already reached the same level as the Carrion Swamp. Those who came in didn’t manage to return. I heard that the Purcell Family’s Buffy went to the Carrion Swamp and hasn’t been heard from since. It is clear that he had met an unfortunate fate. Those Great Clans that sent people to the Black Wasteland in order to find Little Hai would surely find nothing while losing their people. It was clear that the young man has led them there.”

This thought wasn’t unique to Randolph, in fact, most of the people on the continent believed that Zhao Hai cannot be inside the Black Wasteland. His current action was only meant to distract the Great Clans from finding his true location.

This idea wasn’t strange, after all the Carrion Swamp’s poison mist already filled the entirety of the Black Wasteland. For the neighboring territory of the Carrion Swamp to be invaded by this mist wasn’t a huge mystery. It was also known to everyone how lethal the Seven-colored poison mist was. For Zhao Hai to set up his home right inside that hazard was something that the people found to be absurd.

However, they clearly forgot about another thing about Zhao Hai. They forgot to recognize that the Water of Nothingness was in itself, a poison. If Zhao Hai managed to find a way to cure this poison, then there would be no reason for him to be unable to solve the Seven-colored poisonous mist.

Currently, the people of the continent cannot associate the Water of Nothingness and the Seven-colored poisonous mist together. For them the Water of Nothingness was something they see as great, while they see the Seven-colored mist as dreadful. Therefore, there was no way for them to connect the two together.

Randolph also shared that thought, in his mind, Zhao Hai must have known that the poison mist of the Carrion Swamp was going to engulf the Black Wasteland. So he left the place and found a secret location. He settled there and got the support of a powerful hidden power, otherwise he wouldn’t be able to reach his current height.

But because Zhao Hai didn’t want anybody to know about his present location, he didn’t divulge the fact that he left the Black Wasteland. This gave the people the illusion that his clan was still inside.

Chapter 445: I’ll Hand it Over to You

Zhao Hai didn’t know about any of these, he wasn’t monitoring them, it wasn’t necessary. After Megan returned to her room, Zhao Hai immediately took her in to the Space.

Megan liked staying inside the Space now, this was because the air inside the Space is very good. There were also a lot of animals that would accompany her, making her very happy.

Additionally, Megan had the lowest level among the group. So Zhao Hai wanted Megan to practice inside the Space. Megan was a Water Mage, and was found to be compatible with the Goldmetal Fruit. But her current level was too low, therefore, Zhao Hai had her work hard inside the Space to reach a high enough level to eat the Goldmetal Fruit. No matter what, she needs to reach 8th rank.

Megan entered the Space and told Zhao Hai about everything that happened. Looking at Megan’s scared face, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s okay, I already agreed to it. You telling me this right now actually made me happy, after all they are your family. Right, do you really want to go with me to Jade Water City tomorrow?”

Megan nodded and said, “Of course, at this point I wouldn’t be able to sleep outside the Space. I blame you for this.”

Zhao Hai and Laura couldn’t help but laugh, the environment inside the Space was truly fantastic. After someone spent a long time inside, they would find it awkward to go out again.

After they laughed, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, I expect to not have any troubles in Jade Water City, we can just go to the Capital afterwards. Also, after we reach Carson City, when will you plan to visit His Highness Charlie?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “I’ll head to Charlie after we arrive at Carson City, then to the Calci Family. We belong to the family, so they should give us some room to be polite. But Charlie on the other hand needs special attention, that’s why I’ll be visiting him first. Moreover, if we visit Charlie first, nobody would think that the Calci Family had any part in our partnership.”

Megan just looked at Zhao Hai and didn’t speak. Her current experience regarding these things was too low. There were a lot of things to consider in this matter, so at this time she can only listen.

Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, do we have anything to harvest? It’s God’s Grace Day, it’s certain that those marine products will sell well in the capital. We also need to have some for the Clan.”

Cai’er nodded and said, “Yes, we have some in the sea, river, and the hot springs. This time, we can take them all to Carson City.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, we should leave behind some good products for Mu’er, he’s unfamiliar with Jade Water City. He needs to do great these days.”

Laura smiled and said, “It’s alright, no need to worry. Recently, their lives in Jade Water City is very good. Although the city wasn’t as good as Sky Water City, it is still an important port city of the Rosen Empire. Since you gave them enough money as well as products, there isn’t anything worth worrying about.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s great. They’re working very hard as well. They are now one of our tentacles outside. Also, I think we should open up our shop in Sky Water City. What do you think?”

Laura nodded, then she turned her head to Megan and said, “I think we should ask Megan about this matter. Megan hasn’t been talking much lately, that’s no good.”

Megan stared, then she immediately replied, “No, no, I don’t know any of these matters. I cannot just speak irresponsibly. I dare not talk.”

Zhao Hai looked at her and faintly smiled, “It’s alright, so do you think we should open up a shop in Sky Water City?”

Seeing that there was no way for Zhao Hai to let it go of the matter, Megan looked down and thought for a moment, then she said, “I think it should be okay. You’re now engaged to me, and Daddy likes you, moreover, I already talked about you to Grandpa. So I don’t think the Calci Family would be opposing you any longer. But if we want to gather intelligence, it isn’t good to rely on the Calci Family, so I think we should get a shop.”

Laura and Zhao Hai nodded. Hearing Megan say that made them think that she has truly regarded herself as a member of the Buda Clan and not the princess of the Calci Family anymore. This was good for them.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, then we’ll open a shop at Sky Water City. But I think this would have to wait until the next year. At that point, we’ll have to rely on Megan.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Megan shook her head, “That’s not good. Although I grew up in Sky Water City, I don’t really know much about the things happening there. If we open a shop, I wouldn’t be much of a help.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Just give it a try. Among us, you are still the most familiar with Sky Water City. In the end, you’re still the princess of the Calci Family. There wouldn’t be anyone in the city that won’t dare give you face.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and saw that he really wanted her to give it a try. She didn’t say anything more, just nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll try.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It won’t be too soon anyway since we have a tight schedule. Tomorrow we still need to head towards Jade Water City, although we don’t have much to do there, we still need to see Trezebo.”

Laura and the others nodded, then they went to rest. The Space was quite good right now, Zhao Hai didn’t need to worry so much.

The next morning, after having breakfast with Randolph, Zhao Hai’s group left for the seas again. Zhao Hai released the Haven last night so now it was docked at Sky Water City waiting for Zhao Hai.

But Randolph and the others already knew that this ship was just an act that Zhao Hai did. Although they didn’t know how Zhao Hai travels around, they were sure that it definitely wasn’t by ship.

After Zhao Hai and the others embarked, the ship quickly left the harbor. Zhao Hai didn’t immediately head to Jade Water City via the Space. If people knew that they arrived at Jade Water City just as they left the harbor of Sky Water City, they would be quite sure that Zhao Hai had a Spatial Ability, there was no other way of travelling this fast other than Spatial Teleportation.

ZHao Hai and the others didn’t go to the Space and just stayed on the deck and smelled the scent of the sea. It was quite while since they got to sail so they just sat down and enjoyed the view.

While sitting on the ship and watching the other boats coming and going, Zhao Hai sighed, “I really hadn’t thought about it while we were at sea back then, but now, I noticed that the continent is actually really cold.”

Laura also sighed, “The continent is indeed very cold, it was good that Cai’er was present in Iron Mountain Fort. Otherwise, the place would be cold as well, unlike the likeable Iron Mountain Fort that it is now.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then turned to Megan, “Megan, do you like it here? You grew up here as a child. To be honest, I don’t like the cold here.”

Megan smiles, “I actually got comfortable with Iron Mountain Fort, I prefer being there now. The comfort there is incomparable with Sky Water City, the winter in Sky Water City is too repugnant.”

Zhao Hai smiled and then looked at the time, “We’ll wait for a while and then go to Jade Water City. When we reach there, we must finish our matters as soon as possible then go to Carson City. We have a little time to spare in order to prepare for the holiday.”

Megan and the others smiled as well, then continued chatting on the ship. Two hours unknowingly passed by, when Zhao Hai’s ship left Sky Water City he immediately entered the Space. From there they went to Jade Water City,

The place where they chose to appear was somewhere outside Jade Water City. When they arrived outside, they didn’t ride the Bull-pulled Carriage and instead rode horses to enter the city.

They went to Mu’en’s shop first. The shop was very busy since God’s Grace Day was approaching. This was the best time to sell items on the continent and Mu’en’s shop capitalized on this. Although Haven products weren’t very popular in the Rosen Empire, it gradually became recognized by the people because of its quality.

And since the people wanted to eat good food in God’s Grace Day, and since Haven products were inexpensive and good, it was very popular with those who didn’t have much money.

When Zhao Hai saw that the shop was very busy, he couldn’t help but smile. Then he turned his head to Laura and said, “Looks like Mu’en works pretty well. When we sell expensive stuff later, the income surely wouldn’t be low.”

Laura smiled and said, “It wasn’t all because of Mu’en, the products from the Space are also very good. And adding on to the fact that Charlie favors you, people wouldn’t dare not give you face. All of these are the reasons why business is doing very well.”

Zhao Hai smiles, “No matter what, if Mu’en wasn’t that skilled, the shop wouldn’t be able to reach this far. Let’s go talk a bit with Mu’en, then we’ll go to the City Lord’s Mansion and see Trezebo. After that, we’ll head to Carson City.”

The group then went to the back courtyard. When Mu’ern’s family saw them, they immediately went and fetched Mu’en. At this point, except for some important figures, Mu’en wasn’t required to man the counters.”

The group headed to the living room after Mu’en arrived. Zhao Hai looked at Mu’en and smiled, “Mu’en, you did really good, very good. Right, the recent batch of marine products, did they get taken care of?”

Mu’en nodded and said, “They’re taken care of. I gave them personally to Trezebo, it has been recorded as well. I can show them to the Young Master.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t need to see them, I’ll be handing the marine products business over to you. From time to time, show the accounts to Laura, I don’t like to look at those things.”

Laura smiled and turned to Mu’en, “God’s Grace Day is approaching, what are you planning to do? Is everything in your family ready?”

Mu’en was stunned as he looked at Laura and Zhao Hai. He understood that if Laura asked about it, it certainly came from Zhao Hai.

Chapter 446: Pure Iron Armor

Mu’en quickly replied, “Prepared, rest assured. How about the Young Lady, are you prepared for the holidays?”

Laura smiled, “We’ve already prepared well. We’ll be accompanying Megan along with the Calci Family in God’s Grace Day. Of course, we’ll also go to Divine Grace Fort.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Well, let’s not talk about these anymore. I’ll leave you some marine products for your family to enjoy for God’s Grace Day. If I find out that you sold them as well, then I will be angry.”

Mu’en understood Zhao Hai, he faintly smiled and said, “Young Master can feel relieved, I’ll promise to not sell them. Don’t worry.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Laura and then to Mue’n, “We’re going to see Trezebo. Then we’ll be heading for the capital. We won’t be going back here for a while. If anything happens, send a message through the Blood Hawk.”

Mu’en nodded, “Alright, Young Master can feel relieved, If anything happens, I will immediately send you a message.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ll leave you ten thousand undead, but don’t reveal them as much as possible. The troubles wouldn’t be small if people find out.”

Mu’en nodded, then exchanged some words with Zhao Hai. After that, Zhao Hai led Laura and the others to the City Lord’s Mansion. There were also a lot of people outside the mansion. Carriages came and went one after another. They looked like they contained gifts. The line was very long.

Seeing this scene, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile faintly. For him, it seems very intriguing. He can remember back on Earth that if an officer blatantly gives a gift, they might not get killed, but the next day they would certainly be dismissed. But in Ark Continent, they would give their gifts personally and also the most noticeable manner as possible.

When the people saw Zhao Hai, some of them immediately went over and gave him greetings. Zhao Hai also smiled and chatted with those people before he headed to the City Lord’s Mansion.

Once Zhao Hai passed by, a man beside one who greeted him asked, “Old Friend, who was that person? Why do I see that you’re more respectful to him than you did with the City Lord?” There were also people around them who didn’t know about Zhao Hai. When the person heard the question, he laughed, those who didn’t know Zhao Hai just stayed quiet.

The man scolded the person who asked and smiled with disdain, “Of course you don’t know, you don’t have any qualifications to do so. Let me tell you why I gave him more respect than the City Lord. It is because he’s a member of the Buda Clan, his name is Zhao Hai, the patriarch of the Buda Clan. He’s also very favored by the Third Prince Charlie. With his undead, he managed to kill 200 thousand soldiers as well as six 9th rank level experts. Now you ask me why such a person deserve such respect?”[1]

When the person asking heard the man, he froze, with a shocked face he said, “That was Zhao Hai? I heard that he’s been called the most powerful Dark Mage in the battlefield. I didn’t think that he would be so young. That man has several women on his side, was one of them Megan?”

Those around them who didn’t know about Zhao Hai were shocked as well. They knew about Zhao Hai’s present status on the continent. Their status among nobles weren’t very high, but they were still well-informed. Naturally, the news that they received were exaggerated. Instead of killing 100 thousand people, they heard that Zhao Hai killed 200 thousand. And instead of killing four 9th ranks and two Divergent Ability Users, they heard that he killed six 9th ranks.

Although this was the case, they still managed to grasp Zhao Hai’s standing in the continent was higher than them. This was why they were very surprised when they knew that it was Zhao Hai who just passed by.

ZHao Hai didn’t know about any of these. When he arrived at the main entrance of the City Lord’s Mansion, Trezebo came out. The City Lord didn’t care about those in front and immediately went to Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, you came back, I didn’t think you’d come this time.”

Zhao Hai stared at Trezebo’s manner. To others, this seems to be nothing, but this showed Trezebo’s wisdom. First, it was said to make their relationship closer and the second was to gauge Zhao Hai’s reaction.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Why wouldn’t I come, isn’t it going to be the holidays? I’m going to visit Megan’s home and then stop by to see His Highness.”

When Trezebo heard Zhao Hai, a flash of happiness was seen on his eyes. Then he immediately replied, “Alright, come in quickly.” After he brought Zhao Hai inside the living room, Trezebo gave out a few crystal cards to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, this are your share of the profits from the first batch of marine products. You can tell me if you’re unsatisfied. Do you want to see the account books?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No need to read the books, there’s no reason to deceive me over some small money because I may not cooperate with you later. Right, in the future, you can hand these money over to Mu’en, no need to wait for me.”

Trezebo smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll give the money to Mu’en in later transactions. You can just ask him to look at the books.”

Zhao Hai nodded and smiled, “I’m here to see you during the holidays and give you some seafood. These things are what I recently obtained. These are the finest seafood, don’t give them to His Majesty, they’re yours. I already have some for myself as well as His Highness.”

Trezebo smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll accept it. Right, there’s also something I need to give you.” Then he went back and before long he came out while bringing a set of clothes.

The garments looked very ordinary, just like something that a Noble would wear. Not like the kind of traditional noble clothes and was instead quite casual. It was something that would make one at ease when worn.

Trezebo gave the clothes to Zhao Hai and said, “This was something good I acquired before. I heard that Dwarves made it. Don’t underestimate clothes made by dwarves, they’re known to be very good. This was made of some light metal, it has good defensive strength as well as magical resistance. There are only a few of them on the continent. When I obtained this, I intended to give it to his highness, but now I’ll give it to you instead.”

Zhao Hai stared, then Laura’s alarmed voice said, “Pure Iron Robe! This is Pure Iron Robe!”

Zhao Hai didn’t understand, he turned to Laura and said, “Pure Iron Robe? What is Pure Iron Robe?”

Laura looked at the clothes and said, “The given name of this item is the Pure Iron Robe. There were initially five of them made by the Dwarves. Right now, there are only three of them left, two were destroyed. And it were 9th rank experts who destroyed the two. This weaved iron garment is a treasure even to the Dwarves. I heard that the Dwarves had one while another on is in the hands of the Radiant Church, perhaps the Pope. I didn’t expect the last one to be here.”

Trezebo apparently didn’t know as much as Laura, he turned to look at her and said, “Miss Laura, I actually don’t know what’s special about this robe.”

Laura nodded, “This iron robe was made from a kind of metal that Dwarves rarely used. This item isn’t just as tough as iron, it also has formidable defensive power. The most important thing about this was that it can actually cleanse the body, expelling dirt that attaches to it. It is a rare treasure that is warm in the winter and cool in the summer. Another great thing about this was that it was made from something called Pure Iron, some people call it Mother Iron.”

Zhao Hai and the others were still confused as the looked at Laura. Seeing their expressions Laura knew that further explanation was needed, “Mother Iron was a rare ore used by the Dwarven Race. When this metal is surrounded by stone, the stones would turn to iron. The Dwarves researched this metal for a long time. At first what they got was poisonous iron. So they made their Mother Irons into weapons, but they soon found out that the weapons were very light, the metal wasn’t easily melted either. In the end, they stopped making weapons out of it and stored the made weapons away. Even the iron that the Mother Irons produced were kept away.”

Laura stopped for a while. Zhao Hai and the others still didn’t understand. According to Laura’s description, then the material wouldn’t be susceptible to be a dress, right?

Laura looked at the others and then added, “But afterward, a talented Dwarf appeared and found a method to remove the toxicity of the Mother Iron. Now, the Mother Iron cannot infect its surroundings and was turned into a normal metal. But the dwarves called this metal Pure Iron, it meant that it was the purest form that iron can be. The more Dwarves found it difficult to process a metal, the better metal it was, and the more they wanted to turn it into useful things. The Mother Iron has already been turned to weapons, so they already know how to do that. And also, after many years of research, they finally found another method of processing it. They would let a Metal Silkworm eat the Mother Iron and then process the silk produced after into cloth. Afterwards, they finally were able to make this Pure Iron Armor.”

Zhao Hai and the others knew that this Metal Silkworm aren’t one of the very famous Magic Beasts in the continent. They have a very mild temper, and never attacked people since they had no means of attack. But their defensive capabilities are very strong. Their diet solely focuses on metals. No matter what kind of metal they eat, they can digest it, which was the main reason for their great defensive abilities. Even an average 9th rank expert would find it hard to take them away. Also, if they eat a certain metal, they would produce silk of the same type. If you let it eat gold, it would produce heaps more. It somehow produces more than what it ate.

They didn’t think that the method to produce this robe was actually like this. This was really not so simple, Trezebo regretted slightly, he didn’t expect this garment to be very precious. If he knew this information beforehand, he wouldn’t have given it to Zhao Hai but to Charlie instead.

When Zhao Hai saw Trezebo’s expression,  he smiled faintly and handed the Pure Iron Armor back in Trezebo’s hand and said, “Trezebo, I don’t want these, you should give it to His Highness. This is too precious, if His Highness knew that you gave such a thing away to anyone else, then he wouldn’t’ feel so good. It’s fine, its not something I want anyway.”

Trezebo gave Zhao Hai a grate ful look and said, “I’ve been unfair to Little Hai. I really didn’t know that this would be that precious. You should understand my difficulties.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Of course I understand, here take it. Right, make sure to tell nobody about this, or else people might steal it.”

When Trezebo heard Zhao Hai, his expression couldn’t help but change. With clenched teeth, he handed the Pure Iron Armor to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, I’ll leave these clothes to you. When you arrive at Carson City, please give it to His Highness in my behalf”

Zhao Hai smiled, “No need to be polite. Rest assured, I will hand it ot His Highness personally. I wouldn’t dare covet this item.”

Trezebo laughed, “You’re mocking me. Hahaha. Right, since I didn’t get to gift you something, please stay for a meal and some drinks. We’ll drink since you’re leaving tomorrow. Are you able to make it on time?”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Able? Of course. Let’s go and drink.”

At this point, Zhao Hai was naturally happy. This was because when he received the Pure Iron Robe into the Space, a prompt was heard, “Unusual Radioactive Material detected. May affect environment, can transform surroundings into metal. Has Metal element Origin energy. Metallic ore output of Space increased. Space upgraded to level 48.”

This prompt made Zhao Hai incomparably happy. He really didn’t think that this Pure Iron Armor would still have it s original ability from the Mother Iron, but just reduced. People didn’t detect it, but the Space surely did. As long as it still held its ability, it didn’t matter how strong it was, it can still upgrade the Space and use it to strengthen themselves.

Now that the Space had obtained a new ability, Zhao Hai was happy. He believed that the Pure Iron and Mother Iron in the Space would get more and more. As long as he obtains them, he can make as many Pure Iron Armor as he can. Therefore, he really didn’t think about this Pure Iron Robe that Trezebo had.

Laura and the others didn’t know about these. But they weren’t very greedy. For them, the Space was the most important thing. A robe like this wasn’t very special.

On the other hand, Trezebo really commended Zhao Hai in his mind for being not greedy regarding items that weren’t his. He now thought that even if a pile of gold was placed in front of Zhao Hai, the young man wouldn’t even bat an eye. This was the type of person that one wanted to be friends with. Trezebo was very honored to know such a person.

Chapter 447: Arriving at Carson City

When their meal with Trezebo came to an end, it was time for Zhao Hai’s group to leave. After leaving some seafood to Trezebo, Zhao Hai went to Mu’en’s place and took a rest before taking their ship out to sea.

The reason why Zhao Hai chose to travel by sea was so that nobody would know his whereabouts. It would make people see him as though they are looking at a deep well. Only then could he have his security.

Of course, with Zhao Hai’s current strength, he didn’t need to fear the Radiant Church anymore. But he also knew that if he shows off too much he won’t be able to live a good life. On the contrary, it may even lead the entire continent allying up against him because of this strength. For those rulers, Zhao Hai would become a threat much worse than the Radiant Church. Therefore, Zhao Hai chose to wait until the final moment, when he is sure that his strength was already too formidable for the other empires to deal with.

People always harbor a conflicting feeling for something that is too powerful, because at that point they wouldn’t be able to even hold a rebellious idea at all. This was the reason why strong forces always find ways to eliminate any threats that they come across, in order to ensure the safety of their benefits.

And Zhao Hai didn’t want to be one of those existences. He would rather have people guessing his strength and maintaining a mysterious feeling. People always regarded mysterious things with curiosity, they may become vigilant, but they wouldn’t think to eliminate them.

Zhao Hai believed that there weren’t a lot of people on the continent that would still dare make a move on him. He even managed to clean up a group of 9th ranks. So even if those people did have any ideas against Zhao Hai, they would still need to think about it. This was the advantage of strength, with enough strength, one could make his enemies think twice before acting against them.

While sitting on the ship, Zhao Hai let out a long breath. Then he drank some of the Space’s water. Now, he didn’t smell of alcohol.

Laura and the others were on Zhao Hai’s side. When they accompany Zhao Hai, the atmosphere becomes peaceful, as well as very warm.

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the others’ eyes and said, “The Space has already reached Level 47. I didn’t think that the Pure Iron Armor would actually give this much. Although it doesn’t belong to us, it still brought us some benefits.”

Laura smiled and said, “It is a good outcome every time the Space gets upgraded. Now we only need two levels before reaching level 50. I really want to know what changes happen to the Space when it reaches that level.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled, “That’s easy to say. Pure Iron is definitely a treasure in the continent. But these things can only be found, not sought. However, even with how precious this thing is, it only brought three levels to the space. This time, it will become hard to raise the Space’s levels.”

Then Laura chuckled, “I don’t think so. Our luck is very good. Did you see how fast we managed to raise the Space’s levels? I think it won’t take too long before we fulfill those three levels.”

Zhao Hai just smiled and didn’t speak anymore. When it became dark, the Haven finally left Jade Water City’s region. Zhao Hai looked around to see whether there were other ships present. After that, they went to the Space and took their rest. At this time, even if they arrived at Carson City, they still wouldn’t be able to enter since the gates would be closed.

Zhao Hai has never seen Carson City, so he could only release a Blood Hawk and had it fly towards Carson City’s direction while carrying the Ghost Staff. When it arrives then they will go out.

Megan told the Blood Hawk Carson City’s direction then told Cai’er about how it looks like making her pay attention to it before she proceeded to sleep.

The next morning after they had their breakfast and went to the living room, the Blood Hawk finally reached Carson City. Zhao Hai was glad when he knew about this.

Outside Carson City, then looked for a desolate place before coming out. Zhao Hai released his Giant Horned Bull-pulled carriage and slowly headed to Carson City.

Zhao Hai planned to see Charlie first before heading to the Calci Family. Megan didn’t object, she also knew the direction to Charlie’s Mansion. Although she didn’t come to Carson City quite often, she still went there every year and lived there for a month or two. Because of this, she knew about the notable mansions in Carson City as well as their owners.

When they arrived outside Carson City, Zhao Hai learned how majestic the capital was. The walls of the City had reached an unimaginable height of 60 zhang(~200 meters) as well as a thickness of 100 meters. No wonder the books that Zhao Hai read stated that the city walls of Carson City took five years to build. Know that this construction used countless manpower as well as the cooperation of Mages.

There was a moat outside surrounding the whole city as well as bridges as wide as 100 meters. The bridge that they ran along lead to Carson City’s east gate, called the Sea Gate. The gate had 12 openings, with the middle three openings being the widest and highest, height of 30 meters and a width of 20. According to Megan, these three openings cannot be used by average people, only nobles can pass through. The remaining 9 openings were for commoners and merchants.

Since God’s Grace Day was approaching, the gate was jam packed with people waiting to enter the city. Only on those three openings did the lines became quite lax. Commoners and Merchants needed to pay entry tax as well as undergo a strict inspection in order to pass through while nobles didn’t, which explains the short lines on the middle openings. The nobles only needed to register, making their passage much quicker.

Zhao Hai and the others went to the three middle openings since they already have status. Hung on the carriage was the proper emblem of the Buda Clan. Although it only showed the status of a Count, nobody in the Continent would dare to underestimate this Count.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage stopped in line, it brought attention to those around it. There was no other person in the continent that used a bull-pulled carriage aside from Zhao Hai. Because of this, it would be impossible for people to not notice him when he stopped in their vicinity.

The group slowly advanced and arrived at the gate before long. There was a dedicated recorder on the gate of the city. He held the task of recording every vehicle entering and leaving the city. He also listed who the vehicles belonged to.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the gate, the recorder listed their carriage under the Buda Clan’s name. Then he asked Shue and Shun, who were driving the carriage, a few questions before allowing them passage to the city.

Zhao Hai drove through the gate and entered the streets of the city. Once they were on the street, Zhao Hai saw how lively the place was. People came and went along the shops in the street, they were even more lively than Zhao Hai’s shop back at Jade Water City. Other places simply aren’t as lively as this, even Sky Water City. This was truly the capital of the continent’s most powerful empire, truly extraordinary.

While Zhao Hai and the others were driving along, they saw a group of knight heading towards them. The knights were wearing heavy armor and had badges on their bodies. They were all from the Calci Family and wanted to meet with Zhao Hai.

Sure enough, when the carriage met with them, a person went forward and said, “I just want to ask whether mister Zhao Hai is sitting inside the carriage.”

Zhao Hai opened the carriage door and showed a faint smile, “Yes it is. Why did these gentlemen come meet us?”

The knight immediately bowed and said, “I have seen mister, the Patriarch has given us orders to meet mister and invite him over.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No need to hurry, I’ve been asked by a friend to deliver something, this time I need to head to Third Prince Charlie’s mansion first. You could help me by leading the way.” The knight couldn’t ignore such request and immediately gave a command to his team before they headed towards Charlie’s mansion.

At this time, another group of knights appeared in front of them. These knights were also wearing heavy armor, but they were golden. The badges worn by this group showed the emblem of the Rosen Imperial Clan.

When the team arrived in front of Zhao Hai’s carriage, a man bowed and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, His Highness has asked us to meet and escort mister over to his Mansion.”

Zhao Hai went out of the carriage and looked at the Knight and said, “You people are from His Highness’ Mansion?”

The knight answered, “Exactly sir.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It just so happens that I’m heading towards His Highness’ Mansion. Well then, please go lead the way.” The man stared for a moment before issuing a cry and went to the front of the procession while the men from the Calci Family retreated towards the back of the carriage.

Zhao Hai’s convoy arrived outside Charlie’s mansion quickly. The outside of Charlie’s mansion was very stylish, it looked very impressive. It wasn’t any worse than one held by a Grand Duke. In fact, Charlie’s status was that of a Grand Duke.

All Empires on the continent have the same custom. Only Princes who held the status of Grand Duke can compete for the throne, otherwise they wouldn’t be given the opportunity to do so.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage stopped outside the mansion, Charlie was seen walking out of the door. Just as Zhao Hai got off from his carriage, Charlie laughed and gave his greetings. “Little Hai, surprisingly, you came to me first instead of the Calci Family. Aren’t you afraid that Miss Megan would get angry?”

When Megan who was inside the vehicle heard Charlie, she couldn’t help but smile and said, “Your Highness, I’ll only get mad if Brother Hai greets you with more energy than he does with me.”

At this moment, there were a lot of people outside Charlie’s Mansion. When they saw Charlie’s enthusiasm towards Zhao Hai, even coming out to meet him personally, they immediately understood Zhao Hai’s standing in the Third Prince’s heart. Those people cannot help but be envious, but they knew that they cannot be jealous of Zhao Hai, they just didn’t have his strength.

When Charlie heard Megan, he laughed and said, “Miss Megan doesn’t need to get angry, I’m just cracking a joke. Right, let’s head inside quickly.” Then he pulled Zhao Hai to enter the mansion.

Chapter 448: Dark Soldier Fort

In the living room, after everyone was seated, Charlie smiled to Zhao Hai and said, “Why did you come this time? RIght, I’ve heard about what you did in Purcell Duchy, hahaha. Very good. With your reputation, there’ll nobody in the continent who would dare underestimate you even if you’re still a Count. Right, I was actually thinking of giving you a higher title in Rosen Empire.”

Zhao Hai knows that Great Nobles have a lot of titles in various empires, they may even have territories on those empires. This matter wasn’t rare, so Charlie’s offer was understandable. After all, even if the Buda Clan was a Count in Aksu Empire, their territory was in the Black Wasteland, something people can consider as having no territory at all.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then I’ll have to give my thanks to Your Highness. Right, there’s a gift that Trezebo sent for me to give you. Please accept it.” Then he placed the Pure Iron Robe on the table.

Charlie looked at the Pure Iron Armor and nodded, he already received word about it from Trezebo, so he already knew the background of this matter, making him quite calm when seeing it.

Charlie also knew that Trezebo meant to give the Armor to Zhao Hai but Zhao Hai didn’t accept it. Thinking about that, Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you can take this robe.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Highness, I have no use for this robe. You should keep it for yourself. Right, I’ve also prepared a gift this time. There’s some seafood here, I picked them out myself, they’re much better than those we sell.”

Charlie also knew about this matter, he smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll be impolite then, but those seafood are really welcome. The marine products that you’ve brought out last time really gave us huge profits, Little Hai, I really need to express my gratitude to you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Your Highness is too polite, it wasn’t only you who profited so much, I also did get lots of money. I came this time to greet His Highness for God’s Grace Day in advance since all of us would be very busy later. After the new year, our liquor will be available for market. At the same time, my business with the Beastmen would begin. I hope Your Highness has prepared yourself as well. We don’t want too much confusion, or else Your Highness will be losing money.”

Charlie laughed and said, “Rest assure, I can guarantee that there will be no problems. How could I possibly let the possibility of losing money happen to me?”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at the skies and said, “Your Highness, I should be leaving for the Calci Family. After all, I’ve only just arrived, it won’t be too good If I take too long in giving my greetings. When I find some free time, i’ll be visiting you again and have a meal together.”

Charlie smiled and said, “Alright, I know about how busy you are. You’re welcome here at all times.” Then Zhao Hai nodded and walked outside along with Megan and the others.

Charlie escorted Zhao Hai towards his carriage as well as having a team of Knights guide him towards Dark Soldier Fort. The Calci Family was a Great Clan of the Rosen Empire, but their main residence was actually not inside the city, but on a small mountain outside. Their residence was on a place called Dark Mountain, and the castle that they built there was called Dark Soldier Fort. The Calci Family actually had a small mansion inside Carson City, but that was mostly occupied by servants and extended families. The core of the Calci Family all congregate and live inside Dark Soldier Fort.

Zhao Hai and the others had to ride their carriage from Carson City towards Dark Soldier Fort. But fortunately, the fort wasn’t that far from the city, it only takes a bit more than an hour to arrive there.

While on the way, Zhao Hai noticed the many castles constructed on the mountains surrounding Carson City. All of those who resided on those castles were Old established Nobles of the Rosen Empire. These castles was also the first line defense of the capital. If one wanted to attack Carson City, they still need to break this line of defense.

Moreover, there was also a symbolic meaning to this arrangement. Because of their close vicinity to the capital, any of those nobles can also quickly amass an army and occupy the city and overthrow the current monarch. Because of this, those who resided on the mountains outside the Capital were seen as the most loyal vassals of the crown.

Dark Soldier Fort was built on the summit of Dark Mountain. Connecting the foot of the mountain and the summit was a cyan stone road. Its width was about ten meters. The mountain also had a lot of trees, and with how old some of the trees here were, one could see the mystery and elegance in the way they obscure the view towards Dark Soldier Fort.

In front of the road to the mountain was a bar blocking entry with a small house beside it. The house was meant to receive and list the guests.

Two servants went out of the small house and removed the bar to the entrance just as Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived. Apparently, they already received word about Zhao Hai’s arrival, they stood respectfully at the side and let Zhao Hai’s carriage pass through.

The team of Knights that Charlie sent left after delivering Zhao Hai to the foot of the mountain. They also knew that there were another team of Knights that would escort Zhao Hai towards the summit of the mountain. Since the members of the Calci Family still needed to get to the capital and back needed escorts, a team of Knights were always present on the family’s mansion inside Carson City.

Under the escort of the Knights, Zhao Hai’s carriage quickly arrived outside Dark Soldier Fort. Upon arriving there, Zhao Hai was quite shocked. This was because the fort looks like Iron Mountain Fort. The only main difference between the two of them was that Iron Mountain Fort was constructed on Iron Mountain while Dark Soldier Fort was constructed on Dark Mountain.

What can be seen outside the fort was a moat as well as walls, clearly showing that the place was very ready for war and was not meant to look good.

At this moment, the big gate to the fort was opened. Two heavy armored soldiers were seen in front of the gate as well as an old man. The old man wore a housekeeper’s robe. Although he was already quite old, he still held a straight body as well as a strong temperament.

When Zhao Hai and the others went out of the carriage, Megan immediately rushed to the old man and said, “Grandpa Gan, why did you come out personally? Is it alright for you to specially come and see us?”

A smile arose from the serious face of the old man, he looked at Megan and said, “Little Megan has come back, of course I’ll go meet you. Otherwise, you might think that I don’t love you anymore.”

Although the man wore housekeeper’s clothes, he was very casual when talking to Megan, he didn’t follow customs at all. On the contrary, he acts like he was Megan’s senior.

Megan had also become accustomed to the old man’s way of talking and didn’t’ mind it at all. Instead she took at the old man’s arm in a spoiled manner and said, “But do you really love me? If you don’t, I’ll go on and tell Grandma.”

Gansu smiled and didn’t say anything more. He turned his head to look at Zhao Hai as Zhao Hai was inspecting the old man’s appearance. He saw that Megan had a good relationship with this man and knew that he couldn’t be ignored, so Zhao immediately gave a bow to Gansu and said, “Zhao Hai has met Grandpa Gan.”

Gansu sized up Zhao Hai and nodded, “Alright, young man, I’ve heard about all things that you’ve done, you’re very good. You’ve done them well and beautifully. I actually dislike that boy Juwan. And I also agree that those Radiant Church really think of themselves as god while dipping their hands into a lot of people’s businesses. Good thing you’ve made a big hit on them, so satisfying, hahaha.”

The old man’s words made Zhao Hai unable to speak anything. For this housekeeper to criticize Juwan, this gave Zhao Hai a vague idea about this old man’s identity and status. It seems like this old man wasn’t an ordinary housekeeper.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and replied, “I was forced that time, I wanted to live peacefully but they didn’t want that. They just wouldn’t let me go, so I could only rise up and resist.”

The old man laughed and said, “Boy, you speak the truth. Let’s go, the family members are waiting for you.” Then he lead the group into the fort.

This castle was divided into three sections, the soldier’s area, the servant’s area, and then the main area. The group entered the main area of the castle.

When Zhao Hai and the others were entering the courtyard, a person came along with a carriage. This carriage was specially meant to receive guests who arrived at Dark Soldier Fort. One must leave their personal carriage outside the fort and ride a specially prepared carriage to enter it. This was an old custom of the family, and it has stayed to this very day.

The carriage that the family had was very big, its interior decorations were also luxurious. Zhao Hai’s carriage simply cannot be compared to this. Moreover, the carriage has space for many people, one simply couldn’t feel that they were being packed inside.

Gansu looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you must prepare yourself. Elders from the family are waiting for you in the living room, Juwan is present as well. The losses that guy suffered was all because of you, he will certainly give you some troubles. Make sure to be mentally prepared.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and asid, “Grandpa Gan, rest assured, there won’t be any problems. After all, he is Megan’s fifth uncle, so he’s also my elder. I’ll never go too far, you don’t need to worry.”

Gansu looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, he was very satisfied with the young man. He wasn’t soft but he wasn’t dry either. He was very polite, and was respectful to his elders.

Gansu didn’t know that deep within Zhao Hai’s bones were very traditional Chinese teachings. The Chinese heavily respects their elders. Respecting the elderly while loving the young were traditional virtues of the Chinese people. This was the type of teachings that Zhao Hai grew up on, thus the reason why he gave his utmost respect to Gansu. Naturally, if you’re old, but you’re very disrespectful, Zhao Hai wouldn’t’ tolerate it.

They aren’t arrogant, but they are proud. Zhao Hai was exactly like this, he will not look down on anyone but if someone looks down on him, he will not be respectful and polite anymore.

The carriage slowly moved on. The carriage had little vibrations, but Zhao Hai was still quite nervous. After all, he was still facing the core of a Great Family. Zhao Hai hasn’t experienced this kind of thing ever.

Chapter 449: Disregard

When the carriage came to a stop, Zhao Hai took a deep breath before going out. He was someone who didn’t like to evade. When he encounters something, he would think of ways to deal with it. It was the same this time.

Zhao Hai looked around and saw that they were currently inside a courtyard. This was the inner courtyard where only the people closest to the family were allowed to enter. And all of them would need to ride the family’s carriage, even Randolph, the family’s patriarch, needed to do it.

Zhao Hai followed behind Gansu and walked to the front courtyard. The place looked very simple and in the middle was a single statue. The statue was of a Dark Mage, and under it was a carved name. It seems like this statue was of the first Generation patriarch of the Calci Family, the person responsible of building and sustaining the earlier period of the family.

Megan told Zhao Hai that no matter who they are, everyone who came here must give a bow to the statue first. Only then can they enter the main fort, this was also a custom of the family.

When Zhao Hai heard this, he immediately thought about how much customs a Great Family had. With this much rules, it’s a wonder why people can still listen and remember them.

After giving respects to the statue, Zhao Hai entered the main palace lobby. When he entered the lobby, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. The inside was filled by people and the youngest seemed to be Juwan. The others were middle-aged and elderly.

Randolph was sitting in the Patriarch’s seat with a flat expression. Smith sat beside him but not too close. With Randolph were a few old people, they looked like they held great power inside the Calci Family.

Zhao Hai looked at their arrangement and gave it a small glimpse. After that, he went forward calmly and first gave Randolph and Smith greetings before giving respects to the other people in the room.

Then Zhao Hai just stood there without making any noise, only staring at the people inside, looking as though he was watching a play. Randolph looks at Zhao Hai and can’t help but laugh inside. He had been dealt with this move from Zhao Hai before. Even if he already made a decision regarding Zhao Hai, the family’s elders were still unconvinced. Randolph had accepted Zhao Hai, but it was not the same for the others. This was the reason for today’s arrangement, they wanted to place Zhao Hai in a position where he would get pressured by the family.

At this time, Juwan was sitting not far from Smith and was staring viciously at Zhao Hai as if he had just killed his father.

Zhao Hai also noted Juwan’s stare, but he didn’t care. At present, his strength was something that Juwan cannot touch. And also, Zhao Hai just didn’t have much interest in people like Juwan.

Megan, Laura and the others weren’t allowed to enter the lobby, and were instead lead to rest on the backyard. Because of this, they didn’t know about any of these.

The people in the room also stared at Zhao Hai but they felt uncomfortable. They thought that Zhao Hai would budge under the gazes of so many people. If Zhao Hai says even a single line, these people would make use of it to judge his character. However, Zhao Hai didn’t say a single word, his expression was also quite calm. He just stood there quietly, as though he didn’t care about anything around him. This left the family members with no idea about what they needed to do next.

Randolph came to appreciate Zhao Hai more and more. In truth, he was also very sick about the attitudes of family. But he had no choice, in the end, they were all on the same side. They were all of his loved ones, he didn’t want to go too far. This current situation was good, seeing Zhao Hai give those people zero face gave Randolph a feeling of satisfaction, instead of being angry, he was instead quite glad.

Both sides didn’t speak, they continued on with this stalemate. The people of the Calci Family began to feel unease, they didn’t want to speak first and give Zhao Hai the upper hand. They wanted to overwhelm Zhao Hai with pressure. And if they talked first, this was the same as losing to Zhao Hai. But they had no choice but to continue on, it really gave them the feeling of riding a tiger and unable to get off.[1]

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these, while the other people in the room weren’t feeling well, he was communicating with Cai’er about how Laura and others were treated. He found out that they were doing well, they were currently inside a room in Smith’s courtyard.

For a Great Clan like the Calci Family, the number of their branches were quite plenty. This was the Patriarch’s dwelling place, as well as the place he does all his work. Since the other branches are not from the capital, they naturally have their own courtyards inside the fort. Naturally, Smith also had one.

Zhao Hai was technically part of Smith’s branch, that’s why his fiance’s were sent there.

Seeing that Laura and the others were settled down, Zhao Hai felt relieved. However, he still didn’t take note of the expressions of everyone in the room as he continued on and switched to looking at Dark Soldier Fort.

Zhao Hai can see that the fort had underwent extension and reconstruction several times, but he also noted that the main fort remained just the way it was before. Moreover, he can also see the defensive strength of this place, so long as they had enough defenders, this castle can withstand an attack from an army containing 150 thousand soldiers.

Zhao Hai studied the castle to use it as reference when he expands Iron Mountain Fort. He also wants to make other castles in other places in his territory to form a defensive system. He wants to futureproof the Black Wasteland, otherwise, if they get attacked in the future, the commoners would surely suffer heavily. The villages alone cannot stop an army from advancing.

While Zhao Hai was looking all around, the other people in the room couldn’t’ remain sitting still anymore. From the peaceful setting in the beginning, there was now sounds of whispered discussion in the room. In the lobby, a small humming sound of collective discussions echoes. Although nobody said anything, they already knew that they lost this battle.

Randolph also thought the same, he gently coughed twice and said, “Alright, this is Little Hai’s first time in coming to the family. He’s already engaged to Megan, later on, he would be one of us. I think it would be better if we let him go back and take a rest.”

Zhao Hai also raised his eyes and looked at the others. But he still didn’t say anything, he believes that these people wouldn’t just let him off easily.

And just as Randolph voice fell, an old man sitting beside him opened his mouth, “No need to be anxious. Since Zhao Hai is a newcomer, then we must ask him some questions. I believe Big Brother won’t oppose?”

Randolph looked at the man, this was his third brother who struggles for the position of Patriarch with him in the past. In the end, Randolph won. But this brother has always opposed him. This time, he would surely give Zhao Hai a hard time. Randolph didn’t stop him, he just gave a nod and didn’t say anything.

Seeing Randolph agree, the elder’s eyes couldn’t help but reveal a smug look. Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai, I’m Megan’s third grandfather, why didn’t you give me any respects?”

Zhao Hai looked at this third grandfather’s eyes and faintly smiled, “Third Grandfather, this is the first time that I came to the family, so I’m not very clear about everybody’s status. But I’m quite sure that I gave my respects to Third Grandfather earlier. Did Third Grandfather not see it?’

Third Grandfather’s face sank upon hearing Zhao Hai, “Do you talk to your elders this way? You dare be disrespectful?  Do you think that the Calci Family didn’t have rules?”

Zhao Hai looked at Third Grandfather with a faint smile as he replied, “I don’t know if the Calci Family has rules, but I’m quite sure that my Buda Clan has. My family’s first rule was : whoever dares slander our reputation will become the clan’s enemy. Punish according to the severity of the offense. But I think that my clan’s rules doesn’t apply to the Calci Family. Is Third Grandfather satisfied with my reply?”

Third Grandfather stared, he was speechless. He knew that Megan was engaged to Zhao Hai. And according to the rules in the continent, she was already part of the Buda Clan. And since Zhao Hai was the patriarch of the Buda Clan, the rules of the Calci Family naturally didn’t apply to him. Third Grandfather only used this move to put pressure on Zhao Hai.

What Zhao Hai said made the other people from the family uncomfortable, they now looked more displeased with him. But they also have the feeling like when a dog bites into a porcupine, dealing harm only to be harmed itself. What Zhao Hai implied was basically, since he was still engaged to Megan, and were still not married, he didn’t have much of a connection to the Calci Family. And since he is the Patriarch of the Buda Clan, the Calci Family should receive him according to him status, and should have not treated him in such a manner.

Juwan wanted to watch Zhao Hai’s face turn ugly. But he didn’t expect him to not only act calm in face of pressure, he also made Third Grandfather speechless. This made Juwan mad, he stood up and looked at Zhao Hai, “Zhao Hai, you don’t get it do you? You’re just relying on Megan, what is there to be proud of? Do you think that we can’t end your engagement?”

Zhao Hai saw Juwan as though he was a mad dog, he only showed a faint smile and said, “I don’t” He said that with a calm manner while not even turning his face towards Juwan. This made Juwan quite irritated.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s actions, the people in the room became angry, the humming sound became louder. They were the elder of the Calci Family, Great Nobles of the Rosen Empire. When did someone have the guts to act like this in front of them?

Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and cannot help but smile. When he came to Sky Water City and met Zhao Hai, it made him reflect on the family’s situation. Currently, Randolph held negative feelings about the elders of the family.

The people in the room spent a long time speaking with each other but still didn’t come up with how to deal with Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s current status was something they cannot easily snuff out, he had the strength to resist. Even if they are dissatisfied with Zhao Hai, they actually wouldn’t dare to go too far. After all, this young man in front of them can cause the family great trouble if they ever go into conflict. Ultimately, this man was able to kill several 9th rank experts.

When the others still couldn’t find out what to do next, Randolph coughed twice and said, “Do you people still have any questions for Little Hai? If not, we can let him take his rest.”

Gansu issued a sound at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and gave Randolph and Smith a bow each while giving the other people in the room another one. Then he turned away, with how courteous he was, nobody could find fault with him.

After leaving the lobby, Gansu suddenly laughed and said, “RIght, Zhao Hai, what you did was very good, hahaha. You’ve really showed those guys some character, hahaha, good job.”

Zhao Hai was sure that Gansu voice can be heard by the people inside. But Gansu still dared to say it, this made Zhao Hai more curious about this old Gan’s identity. He wore a housekeeper’s clothes, but not acting like one, this was really very strange.

Gansu looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Do you want to know why I can dare to not give them face and still come out alive?

Zhao Hai gave an honest nod. Gansu laughed and said, “Boy, if you shook your head, I will not tell you. You nodding showed that you have real courage. Well then, let me tell you how I came to the Calci Family. I was adopted by the Calci Family’s precious generation. At that time, the family had no single heir. From the rules of the continent, I have the right of inheritance. Moreover, my military exploits in the army were quite high. If we really did calculate everything, then I should be having the position of Patriarch. Foster father also liked me very much and was prepared to let me take charge of the family since he needed to concentrate on breaking through to 9th rank. However, I know that I have a worse temperament than Randolph, I’m too easily angered, too stubborn, not really suitable to become a Patriarch. Because of this, I took initiative to tell Foster Father that I’ll become a housekeeper and have Randolph become the Patriarch, father agreed. In the end, father broke through to 9th rank. Since I have father’s greatest favor as well as having the most ability to reach 9th rank, none of those guys dared offend me. Don’t think that this place is Randolph’s home, in front of father, he still needs to act accordingly.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he now understood why Gansu could be impolite. He actually had that identity, his foster father was the former generation’s Patriarch, and was a 9th rank expert, only a crazy person would dare offend him.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived at Smith’s courtyard. The courtyard was very big, it was also named Rustling Tree Courtyard. There was an ancient tree towering inside, it had a very elegant atmosphere, Zhao Hai liked it very much.

Gansu led Zhao Hai to the door and told the servants about who Zhao Hai was. Then he tapped Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Young man, I’ll leave you here. I’ll find you in the evening and drink a couple cups with you, I’m quite busy right now.”

Zhao Hai respected this frank old man, he gave him a bow to Gansu and said, “Alright, when you’re done, I’ll pay respects to you with Megan.”

Gansu laughed and then waved as he walked away.

* * *

riding a tiger and it being hard to get off of (qí hǔ nán xià – ) – used to describe a situation in which one is stuck in a difficult position with no way out.

Chapter 450: Banquet

When Zhao Hai entered the courtyard, a servant immediately came and guided him towards the place that Smith prepared. Smith’s place was very large. Inside were a lot of small courtyards intended for resting.

The servant left after leading Zhao Hai to his courtyard. Zhao Hai pushed the gate open and saw Shue. When Shue noticed who entered, he immediately announced, “The young master is back.”

When they heard Shue, Laura and the others went out. At this point, they were already wearing their home clothes, they looked very casual. Zhao Hai was surprised when he saw Megan.

Zhao Hai gave the group a greeting before entering the living room. When Megan saw that Zhao Hai had sat down, she immediately said, “Big Brother Hai, did the family embarrass you?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s alright, I’m fine, they didn’t manage to embarrass me. Right, if you have time, lead me to see Grandpa Gan. I have some seafood from the Space, I’ll go give some to him as our gift.”

Megan nodded and said, “Right, we’ll go to Grandpa Gan later. Big Brother Hai, what did you experience in the lobby today?”

Zhao looked at Megan and knew that if she didn’t get to know what happened today, then she would be uneasy. So Zhao Hai had no choice but to tell Megan and the others about what happened earlier.

When Megan heard Zhao Hai, she said, “Third Grandfather has always been like that. In the past, he already wants me to marry. Thankfully, Father and Grandpa managed to stop him, but it was not without pressure. Third Grandfather has strong relationship with a lot of elders, so they pressured Father and Grandpa all the time. The reason why Grandpa didn’t oppose to our engagement that much was precisely because of this matter.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that these things tend to happen in Great Clans. Because of a human’s greed, people will always want more. They would resort to doing various things in order to sate their thirst.

Then Megan said, “With Fifth Uncle being on bad terms with you, he already lost Grandpa’s favor. At this point, he should be holding a huge grudge with you. But since he doesn’t have Grandpa’s support, you don’t really need to worry.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “I have nothing to worry about. With my current strength, even if the whole Rosen Empire deals with me, it would be impossible. There’s no need to worry about.”

Megan sighed and said, “I’m not worried about your safety, I’m worried that Fifth Uncle would annoy you to the point that the Calci Family would pay for it. The Calci Family wouldn’t be able to resist your attacks.”

As soon as Zhao Hai and Laura heard Megan, they couldn’t help but laugh. Megan also chuckled, but what she said wasn’t a joke. The people from the Calci Family didn’t know how strong Zhao Hai was. But Megan knew that if Zhao Hai would seriously deal with the Calci Family, then the family would certainly cease to exist.

After laughing, Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you should still prepare yourself for the following days. I think you would be invited to several banquets.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he frowned and said, “Banquets? Can I not participate?”

Megan forced a smile and said, “That would be difficult, the Calci Family aren’t the only ones who would hold a banquet, other nobles would do so as well. The Princes will also hold a banquet. Even if you don’t participate in the other noble’s banquet as well as the Calci Family’s, would you dare decline Charlie’s invitation? Also, I think you should attend several banquets since it would benefit the Buda Clan. Establishing personal connections is extremely important for the clan right now.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he sighed. This was a nerd’s nightmare, they really didn’t want to socialize. For Zhao Hai, these banquets were surely a pain in the ass.

But what Megan said was also true. For a noble, banquets were a normal occurrence, which were also the bane of Zhao Hai.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai’s appearance and smiled faintly, “Elder Brother Hai, don’t worry, if you really don’t like participating on those banquets, then you can choose to not go. After all, the Buda Clan’s strength is already quite high. Even if you don’t go to those gatherings, other nobles would still take the initiative to approach you.”

Megan didn’t oppose, but she still said, “With the current strength of the Buda Clan, we can surely opt not to attend those banquets. But the problem with this is that our current strength is still not clearly known to other people. We may have killed 9th rank experts in Purcell Duchy, but the majority of the continent gave most of the credit to Origin Sword Saint. If that wasn’t the case, people would have already reached out to the Buda Clan. Therefore, I think that we should attend some of the banquets.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura who nodded. At its current state, the Buda Clan really did need visibility in the banquets of other nobles, especially in those hosted by Great Clans. This would slowly make the Buda Clan known to the higher ranked nobles, which may lead to partnerships in the future.

Seeing Laura agree, Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll go participate. But we should choose which ones to go to. I don’t want to spend all of my time attending banquets.”

Laura smiled and said, “Don’t worry, you won’t waste much time on those banquets. When God’s Grace Day passes by, it won’t take too long for us to become busy. There’s a lot of things waiting for us back at the Beastman Prairie. Even if you want to participate in a banquet, it would be impossible.”

At this time, Shue sound was heard, “Grand Duke Smith.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t know what Smith came for at this time. But he still stood up and walked outside along with Laura and the others. Seeing Smith and the madam enter the courtyard, Zhao Hai immediately welcomed them inside the living room. After having sat down, Laura and the others served them some tea.

Smith took a sip of tea and looked at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, you really performed well today. Not only did you not smear the face of your Buda Clan, you’ve made father proud as well. I’ll be having a family dinner this evening. I will be inviting eldest brother, third brother and fourth brother along. You should also come, they really want to meet you.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I will go when the time comes.”

Smith nodded, then he sighed, “You going against Third Uncle earlier isn’t a big deal. In the past, when you are still in conflict with the family, Father went to Sky Water City to confront your engagement with Megan. But in the end, he came back to the headquarters with a positive impression of you, which made the family elders dissatisfied. Today, I want my brothers to go meet you. We brothers can now be considered to be the core of the family. If all of us were to agree with each other, the family would be able to do anything. Otherwise, the family may keep on giving you weird looks in the future.’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You don’t have to worry about that, I won’t be staying here for long. After God’s Grace Day passes, I would have to leave. But in these days, there should be no problems, I could just leave the fort for the time being.”

Smith sighed, he didn’t know what else to say. He knew that the people of the family had a general dislike for Zhao Hai because of the good he has. Almost everyone wanted to offend him, but they didn’t want to be the first since they didn’t want to suffer consequences.

Smith was afraid of this matter, although he didn’t know Zhao Hai’s true strength, he was sure that it wasn’t very weak. If those people from the family really did offend Zhao Hai, then the family would surely find themselves in a bit of trouble.

When Megan saw Smith’s expression, she couldn’t help but smile, “Father, there won’t be a problem. In the fort, Grandpa Gan will look after us. Outside, there’s no need to worry about it as well. Right, Father, can you pay attention to the banquets happening in the capital and see which ones suit the attendance of Big Brother Hai?”

Smith stared for a moment, then he immediately understood what Megan meant, he turned to Zhao Hai and sadi, “You plan to attend banquets? Considering my reputation, no noble would dare not send me an invitation.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “If I could choose, then I’d rather not attend any of them. But Uncle knows that with my Clan’s current status, we really need to make a few more connections. Therefore, I have no choice but attend those gatherings.”

Smith smiled and said, “Right, it’s as you said, not participating in any of them is not good. Alright, I’ll pay attention to some nobles who have good relations with our Calci Family and see which ones can provide you with benefits.”

Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t talk anymore. He knew that with the Buda Clan’s status, not many people would go and take initiative to invite him to a banquet. For Smith to seek those who are close to the Calci Family is also good, at the very least, for those people would have some sense of familiarity with him. If he went to those where he was relatively unknown, some ugly scenes may occur.

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Alright, let’s stop here, I’ll go back and get ready. When everything is prepared, I’ll have someone come and fetch you.” Zhao Hai nodded, then Smith, along with the Madam who was talking with Laura, left.

Looking at the departing Smith, Zhao Hai then turned his head to Megan, “Megan, what kind of persons are your eldest, second and third uncles? Are they like Juwan?”

Megan smiled and said, “They’re not, rest assured, my other uncles are really easy to get along with. Especially my third uncle, he doesn’t think of anything aside from cultivation.”

Chapter 451: Story

After Megan’s introduction, Zhao Hai now had a general idea of the several heirs of the Calci Family. It should be said that there heirs were very good since they had their own special talents. With the exception of Juwan, each one of them are definitely capable of acting alone.

The eldest child Peter always stayed in the clan and acted as the head of the League of Dark Mages, his status within the league was quite high.

The second child was Smith, the one who held the family’s purse. Although the Calci Family also had fiefs on other places, it was without a doubt that the one who made the most money was Sky Water City. Because of how much money he made for the family, his status within was also quite high.

The third child Dillan was a cultivation freak, he was the one with the least interest in becoming the Patriarch. In his opinion, the position of Patriarch was just something that would impede his progress. He practiced since he was at a young age, he was now an 8th rank expert and may even break through to 9th rank one day.

The fourth child Mike was the diplomat of the Calci Family. He was a smooth talker, the help he provided for the family wasn’t small either. Without his help in making connections here and there, the Calci Family might not have retained its current status with the suppression of the Radiant Church.

They were all very important for the Calci Family. Although Dillan didn’t serve the family, he was the person that was closest to becoming a 9th rank expert. As long as his strength becomes 9th rank, Randolph can just sit comfortably in the position of Patriarch, nobody would dare oppose him then.

Just as Megan finished talking to Zhao Hai, a servant came with a message from Smith saying that everything was ready. Zhao Hai nodded and was followed by Megan to the meal. Laura and the others didn’t come with them, but Laura and the others didn’t seem to be excited. They knew that Zhao Hai really didn’t want to go, but he had no other choice.

Zhao Hai and Megan went to the main area of Rustling Tree Courtyard and headed to the living room where Smith and his wife are waiting. He didn’t see any other person, so Zhao Hai can only greet Smith and the madam this time. Smith asked Zhao Hai to sit on the opposite end of the table and said, “This can be considered as a family banquet. I’ve already asked Kristen and Diya to invite their uncles. They should arrive soon. Since you are from the younger generation, I had to call you ahead of time.”

Zhao Hai didn’t object since he was truly a younger generation with regards to Peter and the others. So in today’s banquet, it was right for him to arrive earlier than the older generation.

He can now be regarded as from Randolph’s line, so there should be rules that need to be followed, especially during meals. Although he doesn’t need to follow the customs strictly like Kristen, he should still respect their rules from time to time.

Naturally, this also comes with exceptions. If he faces Juwan, then he certainly wouldn’t be following the family’s custom. If he gives me a foot of respect, the he’ll return it with a zhang(~10ft) of regard, this was Zhao Hai’s principle.

Before long, a servant’s voice announced, “The First, Third, and Fourth Young Master has arrived.” When his voice finished, three people entered the courtyard.

Zhao Hai and Smith immediately stood up to give their greetings. Zhao Hai looked at the appearances of the three people in front of him. The middle one was a person who had a normal noble’s appearance. There wasn’t any special feature to him aside from looking like an older version of Smith. This should be Peter.

The one on the left of Peter wore a Magic Robe. This magic robe was a traditional garment worn by Dark Mages. It looked very secretive. The person was very thin, but one could still see some fat here and there. He had a pale skin and looked very much like a sick scholar. This should be Dillan.

On the right of Peter was a person who wore magnificent noble clothing. Even if he looks a bit fat, he wasn’t very big. But if you compare him to both Peter and Dillan, then you could clearly see how much fatter he was. But even though he had more weight, he wasn’t unsightly at all. He had a fair complexion and wore a smile on his face, looking very approachable. This should be Mike.

Smith immediately went forward and gave salute to the middle person first, “Elder Brother”. Then he turned his head to the two other people and said, “Third Brother, Fourth Brother, you came.”

Zhao Hai also went forward this time and gave the newcomers his greetings. When Zhao Hai was in the lobby, he also saw the three of them. But since they didn’t speak and just sat the entire time, Zhao Hai didn’t know their identity.

Peter also took notice of Zhao Hai’s presence, seeing Zhao Hai give his greetings, Peter couldn’t help but smile and said, “Zhao Hai? Hahahaha, I already heard of you, very good. You actually have some spine, not bad.”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “I don’t dare, how can I accept Uncle’s praise when I’ve been impolite.”

Peter laughed, then he patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and didn’t talk anymore. At this time, Dillan suddenly said, “Zhao Hai, do you really have 10 thousand undead Beastman Cavalry?”

Zhao Hai already know that Dillan was a cultivation maniac, so he wasn’t actually surprised for his first words to be like this, so he immediately replied, “Answering to Third Uncle, I do. In the past on the Beastman Prairie, I got to help the Cow-headed Race’s Herculean Bull tribe in their matters. These undead Beastmen that I have are Fighting Bull Tribe’s cavalry.”

Dillan quickly replied, “Release one for me to see.”

Zhao Hai stared, then with an awkward face he turned to Smith. Smith smiled and said, “Go on and let Third Brother have a look, he likes to look at these things.” Zhao Hai nodded, then with a wave of his hand, an Undead Fighting Bull Cavalry appeared.

Dillan stood before the undead and carefully inspected it. At this moment, the undead had the appearance of a skeleton. After Dillan fully looked at the skeleton, he knocked a bone with his hand. And then with a shocked face, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “This is an Advanced Level Undead?”

Zhao Hai knew that he cannot hide the truth from an expert like Dillan, so he didn’t hide it as he nodded and said, “They can also transform into Zombie form.” Then he wielded his magic staff at the undead Beastman before it turned into a Zombie Cavalry. Not only was Dillan intrigued with this, Peter and the others were also surprised.

What they were seeing was really different from a normal Zombie, it was no mystery why Peter and the others looked surprised. They had studied and researched Dark Magic ever since they were young, so they were extremely familiar with Dark Magic. However, they had not heard nor read about a Dark Magic spell that can transform an undead between a Skeleton and a Zombie.

One must know that in the system of Dark Magic, the branches of skeletons and zombies are different. When a Skeleton progresses, it would go from Iron Skeleton, Bronze Skeleton, Silver Skeleton and then Gold Skeleton. This progression was the same for Zombies, Iron Zombie, Bronze Zombie, Silver Zombie, and Gold Zombie. They had not heard of a Skeleton turning into a Zombie, as well as a Zombie turning into a Skeleton.

Dillan had also studied for a long time and even he had not heard of such scenario. Smith was the first to recover, he knew that he cannot make Dillan continue to inspect the undead, or else there would be no dinner that will happen.

Smith turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, store it first, then we’ll head inside to talk.” Zhao Hai nodded, and then received the Undead. Dillan actually wanted to inspect Zhao Hai’s undead more, but he was blocked by Smith. Then the group entered the room and sat down.

After they sat down, Smith turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what was that? Why is your undead different?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “This I don’t know. This may have something to do with my Magic Staff.” Then he showed his Ghost Staff. At this point the staff reverted to its original form, with the Skull and the gloomy atmosphere surrounding it.

Zhao Hai handed his staff over to Dillan while he said, “I got this Magic Staff from the Black Wasteland. Back when I drank the Water of Nothingness, I was totally depressed. I wanted to run to the Carrion Swarm and kill myself. I didn’t expect that when I entered the swamp, this staff suddenly appeared. I became curious and took it to see what it was. And then I was surprised when the skull’s mouth opened and nipped my finger, taking along a drop of my blood with it. After that, I fainted and was ultimately saved by Grandpa Green. At that point, the Magic Staff had always followed me, there was no way to discard it. It also surprisingly cured me of the toxin from the Water of Nothingness. Most importantly, it was also a very good conductor for casting Magic. When I cast Dark Magic using this staff, it would also increase its potency. The undead created with the staff would have upgraded abilities, the lowest undead that it could make was Advanced Level Undead. It also had the ability to convert the undead from one form to another. Another good thing about this staff is that it can’t be stolen from me. If I get too far from it, it would just directly fly towards my direction. This staff is truly mysterious, even I don’t know its origin.”

Zhao Hai already had this excuse prepared. Nobody can also debunk his story since it was impossible for Green and the others to betray him. He went all out on this story with his novel writing skills, one could say this reason was very airtight.

When he heard Zhao Hai, Dillan couldn’t help but try using it to replicate its effects. But unfortunately, nothing happened. The staff seemed just like a piece of useless wood in Dillan’s hands.

Zhao Hai’s excuse was also believed by Smith and the others because the Carrion Swamp was truly mysterious. All these years, the number of 9th ranks who lost their lives inside were numerous. Nobody can survive in that place but who knew that Zhao Hai would actually find such a treasure there. All of them sighed when thinking about Zhao Hai’s good luck. They didn’t suspect Zhao Hai even for a bit, they knew that the Buda Clan had been transferred to the Black Wasteland, everybody knew it. Other than the Black Wasteland, Smith and the others cannot think of any other place where Zhao Hai could have acquired his current strength.

Chapter 452: Homely

Dillan played around with the Ghost Staff for a while, when he finally got tired of it, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, didn’t you say that no matter where this Magic Staff is, it will always return to your hand? Go try and let me take a look.”

Zhao Hai smiled and nodded. When he saw Dillan gripping the staff tightly, he faintly smiled and with an intention Dillan’s hand suddenly felt light. Then the staff disappeared from Dillan’s hand as it appeared on Zhao Hai’s.

Smith and the other two who were observing couldn’t help but stare. They just saw the staff vanish from Dillan’s hand and then suddenly appearing on Zhao Hai. They had seen a lot of things, but this was something that they had seen for the first time.

After some time, Smith and the others recovered at looked at one another. Then with a surprised expression, they turned to Zhao Hai. Seeing their faces, Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “How this thing happens is a mystery, even I don’t know what’s going on. I still haven’t seen the full capability of this staff, but I’m slowly exploring it.”

Smith nodded and said, “So this is it. No wonder your strength rose in such a small period of time. It was actually because of this Magic Staff.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Mike, who sat next to him, turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what level of strength have you reached right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I should be 8th rank, I can cast 8th rank magic spells.”

Smith and the other’s eyes went bright, an 8th rank expert can already do whatever they want in the continent. Smith was amused even more, “No wonder the Third Prince is very polite to you, so it was this.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “The Third Prince knows my strength, that is why he wanted to win me over. Although I agreed, I am actually not his subordinate. What he have is a simple partnership, he helps me, I help him, you could say that I’m more like his adviser than anything else.”

Advisers were also quite common among Noble Clans. These people were like Foreign Elders, but they are more free. They and the host Noble would only have an employment relationship, if a disagreement occurs, the two could just go on their own separate ways.

Advisers in the Continent were typically well-known people. Not only do they need to be strong, they should also be quite talented enough to give ideas and advice to the Nobles. Advisers receive very high respects inside a Noble Clan.

Smith nodded, “Right, it’s good that Little Hai chose to not sell himself off to the Third Prince, otherwise, matters would get troublesome. Alright, no need to talk about this anymore, let’s go have some drinks.”

Then the group headed to the dining room. When they arrived, Smith invited them to sit down. The madam and Megan actually drew back, leaving the dining room to the men.

After the servants provided the food and wine, Smith, who sat in the seat of honor, smiled and held his wine glass, “God’s Grace Day is near, we brothers rarely have the time to eat a meal together. I actually invited Fifth Brother, but he has a grudge with Little Hai, so he refused. I cannot do anything about that. My invitation this time doesn’t have any other purpose. I just want you to meet Little Hai and also introduce you to him. This way, we might avoid offending each other in the future.”

Zhao Hai also held his wine glass up, he looked awkwardly at the other people. When Peter and the others looked at Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but laugh. Although they struggle with each other for the seat of Patriarch, they were smart people and knew that they cannot harm the Calci Family, unlike Juwan. This was also the reason why Juwan was quite distant with his brothers. Juwan rarely came to gatherings with his other brothers.

Mike looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Even if I only met Little Hai today, I’ve already heard a thing or two about him. I’m very sure that if younger brother didn’t provoke Little Hai before, then there would be no conflict that would happen. And if Third Uncle didn’t send those ships off to Little Hai, then the family wouldn’t have lost all those ships.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said to Mike, “Fourth Uncle overpraises me. This one is just an inexperienced junior, I don’t deserve your praise.”

Mike smiled faintly, “Little Hai, no need to be too polite. You’re quite commendable, otherwise the Buda Clan wouldn’t have reached its height in such a short time. And even if you don’t use your strength, oh well, no need to talk about that, come, come, let’s drink.”

Smith and the others held their wine glasses and drank the wine. It was good wine since what they were drinking was Zhao Hai’s Milk Wine. This Milk Wine was roughly manufactured, so it wasn’t that strong, therefore they can down an entire glass in one go.

Peter and the others didn’t discuss the matters of the clan too much, they just idly talked about their daily lives, like how brothers did. This made Zhao Hai confused, he didn’t understand the purpose of this gathering, are they just here to discuss their feelings?

Only after a while of talking about their daily activities did Zhao Hai slowly understand. Even if these brother were very polite to each other, in the end, they were still fighting with each other for the seat of Patriarch. So naturally, they wouldn’t go deep into their matters and risk giving the others a chance to get ahead. This would affect their relationship, so this shallow conversation was the best thing that they could do.

While sitting there, Zhao Hai looked at the Smith and the other who were calmly chatting away. He couldn’t help but sigh, these people acted very kind to each other right now, but he knew that when this ends, they would go back to contesting with each other. This made Zhao Hai think of hypocrisy.

After having eaten their meal, Zhao Hai and Smith lead the three others to the exit. After which they returned to the living room along with Kristen and the others. When the group sat down, Smith looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “From what I’ve seen, it’s been very good. Everyone fights with each other, but it must be based of ability other than outside intervention. This is the essence of healthy competition. I think this is very good, only with such talents can the Calci Family become better in the future.”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “You’ve observed well, Little Hai. Actually, in addition to the family’s elders, there is also the family’s law enforcement group. This group is directly controlled by the family’s 9th ranks, the Patriarch held no power over them. Because of this, even if the core of the family’s functions are in a fight over the seat, they couldn’t go far in the face of the law enforcement group. Little Hai, your Buda Clan is still struggling despite its strength. Emerging Clans perish in the continent every day. You have a lot to learn in our Calci Family, this way, in the future, you won’t be going blind when going forward, understand?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I understand, Uncle, rest assured I will study hard.”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Your Buda clan is connected to the Aksu Empire in the past, if you continue on this way, your clan won’t become great. But because of your disaster this time, an opportunity to cut your ties with the Aksu Empire has arrived. Then your family can survive for a thousand years.”

Zhao Hai stared, he really didn’t think about this, he also felt that he lacked confidence. He was only a nerd, now someone told him to build a Thousand-year Great Clan. Although he had the Space, he still wasn’t convinced.

Smith saw Zhao Hai’s hesitation and said seriously, “Little Hai, don’t blame me If I lecture you too much. You’re very talented, a capable leader, competent, and also a good natured person. The only problem with you is that you don’t have a lot of confidence. You always make the worst moves and just fix the consequences afterwards. Although you can fix them later, you will still lose opportunities, and that is not right.”

Zhao Hai looked at Smith and forced a smile, “I know that, but I have no other choice, that’s just my character. You may not know this, but the Buda Clan doesn’t really have much right now. We don’t have that much people to farm. Outside the 100 Human slaves that we bought and the 1000 Giant Horned Bulls we got from the Cow-headed race, we really have too few people in the Clan. Moreover, these few people cannot walk the continent openly. Otherwise, I wouldn’t be running around right now.”

Smith nodded then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Your assembly line method is very good. Father is preparing to use it in the family. Your factory should be using them, yes?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I won’t hold anything from you. Although the assembly line method gives efficiency in production, the products made are all of standard quality. There are some things that doesn’t need assembly line production, and are much better produced the old way. Although they are produced slowly, the quality is better and are generally more durable, giving you the leverage to charge a higher price for them. People may not feel it, but they will slowly understand, they might even prefer those produced in the old method. It was only because I have no other choice that I had to resort to the assembly line method.”

Smith smiled, “That’s quite a good method. But you’re right, there’s no way for our Calci Family to produce high quality goods like you because of the numerous products we make. This made it even more applicable to use the assembly line method for our factories.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It’s because of that point why our Buda Clan cannot have the same arrangement as you have right here. I can say that the advantage of our Buda Clan is that point, thus I don’t dare take any risks.”

Smith nodded, “What you said is also right, don’t worry, you can work on it slowly. After all, you’re now 8th rank, you still have a lot of years left in you. As long as you make the right moves, the Buda Clan would do well.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he sighed, “I really didn’t dare think of these things before. I don’t know for how long I can live with the Water of Nothingness. Now that the toxin has been cured, I can now feel relief.”

Smith naturally knew how fierce the Water of Nothingness was. How its effects trickle down even to your descendants, thus he didn’t feel any wrongs from Zhao Hai’s words.

Zhao Hai then shook his head and said, “Uncle, after celebrating the new years, I’m preparing to head back to sea and get some more products for Charlie. After that, I’ll be heading to the Prairie, I still have a lot to do there.

Smith nodded and then said, “I don’t mind, but if you have any good business, you shouldn’t forget about Sky Water City.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Right, we were thinking about opening a shop at the city after the new years as well. I’ll have Megan handle this matter, I’ll make her discuss it with you later.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Smith couldn’t help but stare, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You really want Megan to handle your shop in Sky Water City? She has no prior experience in this matter.”

Kristen and Diya were also giving Zhao Hai a surprised expression, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to give any responsibilities to Megan. In the past, Megan was a tender young lady, the family just let her go eat, play and wander around. But now, Zhao Hai actually wanted to have her handle a business? Is this okay?

Zhao Hai looked at the surprised faces and smiled, “It’s fine, I’ve already talked about this with Megan. She had grown up in Sky Water City since childhood, she was the most familiar with the place. Therefore I decided to let her handle the business, moreover, I think she would love doing it.”

Smith smiled bitterly, he didn’t expect Megan to develop such a personality. Her tender young lady who only knew how to look good was now going to handle such a heavy responsibility.

Zhao Hai looked at the time and turned to Smith, “Uncle, it’s already quite late, I must go back.”

Smith nodded, then Zhao Hai gave him a bow before leaving. Seeing Zhao Hai leave, Kristen looked at Smith and said, “Father, Zhao Hai didn’t seem to trust us. Why didn’t he tell us their location?”

Smiled bitterly, “Just like what he said, the Buda Clan is still relatively weak. Because of this, he just can’t take any risks, otherwise their location would be compromised, resulting in their end. However, I think their location shouldn’t be very far from the Prairie, otherwise he wouldn’t just run to the Prairie by coincidence and acquire a lot of Beastman slaves.”

Kristen nodded, “Zhao Hai offended the Radiant Church before, one of the most powerful forces in the continent. There are no other places to relocate his family other than somewhere close to the Beastman Prairie.”

Smith nodded and said, “You pay attention to the Noble banquets happening in the capital. Find one where we have a good relationship with. Little Hai needs to attend a lot of banquets in order to establish himself. No matter what, Little Hai is now engaged to Megan. For the good of Megan, we must help the Buda Clan prosper. If the Buda Clan is doing well, Megan would get to live a happy life.”

The two nodded, then turned around to leave.

Chapter 453: Side Dishes

After returning to his courtyard, Zhao Hai sat down and let out a long breath. When Laura saw Zhao Hai, she immediately gave him a cup of hot tea and said, “Brother Hai, what happened? You seem very tired, what did you talk with Smith about?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “He didn’t say anything wrong, he was very polite. But being with them is very tiring, I feel even more tired than I did while fighting.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Laura couldn’t help but smile, “Of course it’s more tiring than being in a battle. When fighting, you just stay behind and common the troops, it’s really not that exhausting.”

Zhao Hai gave Laura a look which caused him to laugh. At this moment, Megan also came in. When she saw Zhao Hai, she smiled and said, “Big Brother Hai, it seems like they are very impressed by you. It’ll be great if my uncles support you. This way, we won’t be facing any obstacles in the future.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s not really that good. When I had dinner with your uncles earlier, they didn’t discuss any matters of the family and just did small talks. This meant that they are still on guard with each other. If we get into such great trouble, I don’t’ think that they will  be supporting us that much.”

Megan sighed when she heard Zhao Hai’s words. She knew that Zhao Hai’s words were real. She knew that even if his uncles are now friendly with each other, when it comes to the battle for the seat of the Patriarch, they would surely be impolite.

When he saw Megan’s expression, Zhao Hai comforted her and said, “Well, it’s alright, you don’t need to think too much into it. I know that all your uncles still place the Calci Family first. Uncle Smith also told me about the arrangements of the family. You don’t have to worry too much.”

Megan nodded, but one could still see that she was quite unhappy. Zhao Hai couldn’t do anything about this family struggle, this kind of scenario happens in almost all families.

Zhao Hai thought about shifting the topic as he said, “ We’ll send Grandpa Gan some seafood later. God’s Grace Day is in two days, so I’m thinking we should take a stroll around the capital and play around. This period of time, various products should be converging inside the city because of the holidays. We must go around and find some good things to bring back.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Alright, let’s go to the city tomorrow and have a good look. What does Big Brother Hai want to buy?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “At this point I don’t know, but I still want to take a look, maybe I’ll find some things I like. Let’s also go to the slave market tomorrow, I think we still need quite a few more slaves back at the territory.”

Megan nodded and said, “Alright, but Brother Hai, do we really need to buy more slaves? Don’t we have 100 thousand slaves coming from the prairie?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Rest assured, I didn’t forget about that. But those Beastman slaves cannot farm. We need to buy some Human slaves and have them teach the Beastmen the basics of farming. Moreover, Humans can make simple houses, while the Beastmen cannot, they are already quite used to living in tents, it’s a matter of habit. Because of this, I thought that it would be better to get more Human slaves.”

Megan nodded, “Right, but the slave market isn’t inside the city, it’s outside. I think the slave market would be more busy after the holidays and also have more slaves, it would be a good idea to head there at that time.”

Zhao Hai replied, “Why would it be busy at that time? And if it would be busy by then, won’t we be unable to select the good ones?”

Megan smiled and said, “During the holidays, Great Nobles would be too busy to go buy some decent slaves. After the holidays, they would go find some slaves to help them manage their matters. If those slaves do well, then they would be living a good life. Moreover, they also lost a lot of slaves because of exhaustion and sickness, so the nobles would also look for new ones by then. But Brother Hai doesn’t need to worry, there are a lot of slaves in the market, it would be impossible for us to not find some good ones.”

Zhao Hai frowned and said, “Where did these slaves come from, why are there too many?”

Laura smiled and answered, “Brother Hai doesn’t know, but those slaves are commoners who were unable to pay their taxes, some are also those who borrowed money and wasn’t able to pay it back. Some are generational slaves, children of other slaves. There are also some elderly slaves who are not needed anymore. Because of this, there has never been a shortage of slaves in the continent.”

Zhao Hai sighed, he cannot say anything. He knew that with his present ability, he has no way of changing this custom of the continent. He could just do his best in order to help those he can.

Megan also knew about Zhao Hai’s thoughts. When she first heard about Zhao Hai releasing slaves and restoring the commoner status, she was startled. But she was also a good person, when Meg explained to her about Zhao Hai’s intent, she immediately approved of Zhao Hai’s methods. Now that she saw Zhao Hai looking quite unhappy, she shifted the topic to something else, “Big Brother Hai, how about you give Grandpa Gan the seafood right now? This will also give him more time to prepare them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he stood up. Laura stood up as well and said, “We’ll go explore Dark Soldier Fortress in the meantime, I want to see what makes it different from Iron Mountain Fort.”

Megan smiled and said, “Alright, but Dark Soldier Fortress has some areas that are forbidden. Only some places are allowed to be explored, I’ll go lead you there.” Then she went with Laura outside, Zhao Hai smiled helplessly as he followed right behind them.

When they left the courtyard, they were immediately greeted by some servants. Megan asked one of them to lead them to Gansu. Gansu held special status in the family, even Randolph held some sort of respect to him. Gansu is someone who never limits the things coming out of his mouth and was generally quite impolite. But although he had an explosive temperament, he was actually quite kind to the servants. Because of this, the servants in the family gave him very high respect. If they made any mistakes, Gansu would just scold them a bit and then forget about it later.

Zhao Hai quickly found Gansu, who at this time was in the kitchen. Since God’s Grace Day is approaching, there was a massive need to prepare some food, especially in a place like Dark Soldier Fort. Since banquets were happening, it won’t be good for the family’s face if they were to run out of food.

At this time of the year, Gansu was in charge of keeping everything in check inside the warehouse of the kitchen. Gansu didn’t have any impatient expressions, he carefully inspected everything.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he entered at the warehouse. The things inside were simply numerous. There were even some ingredients that he had never seen before. All of them were neatly placed inside the warehouse according to their classifications.

At this moment, the servant arrived at Gansu’s side and whispered a few words. Gansu stared for a moment before he turned to look at Zhao Hai. Gansu’s impression of Zhao Hai was very good, so he immediately stepped forward and laughed, “Liitle Hai, Little Megan, why did you come here? You want to have some delicious stuff? Don’t worry, if some arrive I definitely won’t forget you.”

Megan ran up to Gansu’s side and held his arm, “Grandpa Gan, Big Brother Hai came here to deliver some stuff. You better receive them or else you will certainly regret it.”

Gansu stared, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, you have some good things? What are they? Can I see them?”

Zhao Hai smiled and waved his hand, making a big pile of products appear on the floor. One could see some swordfishes and crabs among other things. Moreover, their sizes aren’t very small.

These are the things that Zhao Hai asked Cai’er to cultivate. With how large they look, they would certainly be eye-catching.

Gansu looked at the products and couldn’t help but be surprised. His eyes turned bright when he saw the swordfishes as well as the crabs. These are very rare in the continent, even if one saw them, they were very hard to catch. If these are made into dishes and shown to others, their banquet would surely have high attendance.

These past few years, there were no new dishes that were served in these banquets. Everyone just ate the same things, there was nothing new. But with these things present, the Calci Family’s banquet would surely be very good.

The things that Zhao Hai took out were all dead and frozen, but it still baffled Gansu. They would generally cool the products inside cold storage areas filled with magic arrays, this way, they would last a long time, and may even allow them to be consumed in the summer.

Gansu stared at the pile for quite some time before he turned to Zhao Hai, “Good, boy, you really have good things. With these seafood, we could make the Buda Clan shine this year. Good job.”

When she saw Gansu’s reaction, Megan smiled, “See, Grandpa Gan? I said that Big Brother Hai has some good stuff. Go get some people to take them away quickly, or else they would melt. Alright, we’ll be going now, I’ll go lead sister Laura and the others to explore the fort.”

Gansu didn’t stop them, he nodded and said, “Go, go. Little Hai, since you won’t be joining the ladies, come with me. Let’s have a drink between grandfather and grandson.”

Zhao silently nodded and stayed. Megan and the others chuckled as they went away. Gansu wasn’t polite with Zhao Hai as he directly brought him to the kitchen. He had the cook make some side dishes for them as he took out a pot of wine and sat with Zhao Hai to drink.

In the past, Zhao Hai would drink some wine with his old friends. He wouldn’t drink too much and would just enjoy the chat and the company, it felt great. But when he arrived in the Ark Continent, he wasn’t able to experience such opportunity. And now, Gansu made him remember the old times, this gave Zhao Hai a warm feeling.

Gansu and Zhao Hai leisurely drank wine and ate some of the side dishes, they had a very good time. Even if it was the holidays, and everyone in the fort were quite busy, Gansu was an exception. He would just delegate the tasks to his subordinates and would just check their progress from time to time. Because of this, he wasn’t that busy. Moreover, the servants that were under him were the children of the slaves, they didn’t have much negative feelings towards him, making Gansu’s life quite at ease.

Chapter 454: Two Types of Liquor

Gansu initially thought that since Zhao Hai was a child born of a Noble family, he would be unfamiliar with this set-up of drinking and eating side dishes, and would be uncomfortable while being with him. However, he didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would actually have a very happy expression, he chatted with him, drank some wine while munching on some food. Seeing how Zhao Hai was more comfortable than he was, Gansu’s impression of Zhao Hai cannot help but raise two points.

After drinking a glass of wine, Gansu said, “Little Hai, I can see that you’re a good kid. But I want to tell you that I’ve watched Little Megan grew up. Although this little girl is noble born, she is good natured, she’s pure as water. If you dare not treat Megan well, then even at the cost of my life, I will teach you a lesson.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Grandpa Gan, you’re thinking too much. I have a very good relationship with Megan, it would be impossible for me to not treat her well. Rest assured, Zhao Hai isn’t that bad of a person.”

After hearing Zhao Hai, Gansu nodded and said, “If something happens in the future, go have someone send me a letter. There are a few people in the Calci Family that I can’t handle, there are also a few people in Rosen Empire that would dare not give me face. Those fellows in the Family, you don’t need to care about them. If they give you trouble, I’ll take care of it.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, although he didn’t fear the Calci Family, he still didn’t want to fall out with them because of his relationship with Megan. Because of this, he was happy with what Gansu said.

Gansu looked at Zhao Hai and seemed more satisfied. He smiled and said, “Little Hai, you’re a talented fellow, you’re future won’t be small. But do remember to not forget about your grandfather when you get some good stuff. Your Grandpa Gan doesn’t have any other hobby other than drinking. Your Milk Wine is very good, if you have any other nice liquors, do remember to give some to me.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect Gansu to ask for nothing else other than some nice wines. This surprised him, he admired this old man in front of him. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and with a wave of his hand, two bottles of liquor appeared. One bottle was black beer, while the other was good rice wine.

These two bottles weren’t fermented by Zhao Hai’s group, but were instead produced by the Multipurpose Processing Machine. Of course, Zhao Hai didn’t plan to produce his liquor through the processing machine. He only had the machine produce the liquor so that the people researching them could have a reference. After countless experiments and finally producing the liquor, these two bottles were the only ones that remained.

Gansu looked at Zhao Ha’s two bottles. The bottles were transparent, so he can see the color of its contents. One of them was transparent while the other was black, which made him very confused.

Zhao Hai opened the black bottle first. Naturally, this black liquid was black beer. The beer’s foam was very rich. Zhao Hai intentionally got a big glass, filling half of it with beer while the other half was filled with foam.

Zhao Hai raised the glass to Gansu and smiled, “Grandpa Gan, have a taste, this is a new liquor that I’ve been researching. But this one doesn’t have any means of mass production right now, this bottle is from the most successful batch.”

Gansu looked at the half-filled glass. He smelled it and got a mild smell from it, but despite this, he couldn’t help but be more curious. He took a small sip and tried to taste it, only to find out that he only drank the foam. Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Grandpa Gan, this liquor isn’t too strong. Just drink the entire glass so that you can taste it.”

Gansu didn’t blame Zhao Hai, instead he followed his instruction and downed the glass in one go. He couldn’t help but stare before his eyes lit up, “Good liquor, fantastic! The taste of this liquor isn’t very strong. It has a different kind of taste, but it isn’t something I’m used to.”

Zhao Hai looked at Gansu, he knew that the old man liked strong liquor. He didn’t say anything and just handed Ganus a cup of rice wine.

Rice wine was divided into many types, rice wine produced by peasants were generally not distilled. Because of this, the liquor wasn’t very strong, even children can take one or two cups of it.

But those produced by most farmers have been distilled, giving the liquor quite the strength. Although it was slightly sweet and does not go to one’s head, it was still strong. What Zhao Hai took out was the latter type, a fierce rice wine, which was also something that a northerner like Zhao Hai liked.

Because the weather in northern parts of China were generally cold, people liked to drink strong liquor. Because commercial rice wine aren’t very strong, families in the north decided to brew their own liquors in their backyards. They didn’t like drinking those weak liquor, even drinking a jin of it would still make them unhappy. Northerners want to drink strong liquor, something over 40 degrees and along the lines of 60. Let along one jin, an average person would get drunk in just half a glass. Even if you’re quite an experienced drinker, you would still feel tipsy.

The rice wine that Zhao Hai took out was over 40 degrees. For those in the north, it was still considered to be on the low side. Adding on to its sweet taste, people who drink it wouldn’t get hit that hard by its intensity.

Gansu looked at the cup, he lifted it up and smelled it. This wasn’t Milk Wine, it didn’t have that milky fragrance. Instead, this rice wine had the smell of regular wine.

After smelling the liquor, Gansu tasted it, then his eyes turned bright, he immediately downed the entire cup and swirled the liquid inside his mouth. He wrinkled his brows, the strength of this wine was higher than Milk Wine, a liquor known for how strong it was.

After savoring the alcohol, Gansu laughed and said, “Nice Wine! This is really nice wine, Little Hai, If you have any more of this liquor, you must leave some here for me.”

Zhao Hai gave a forced smile and said, “We still didn’t have any way to mass produce this liquor right now, we only have this bottle left. I’ll leave this bottle to you, when we find a way to make a lot of them, I’ll go and send you a batch.”

When Gansu heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “Good, I’ll wait for your delivery. Come, come, this bottle still has some left in it, today we drink.”

Seeing how the other person was very enthusiastic, Zhao Hai didn’t decline. He and Gansu continued to eat some side dishes while drinking liquor. Before long, the bottom of the bottle can be seen. With Zhao Hai’s current capacity, he was now feeling dizzy. He stopped drinking and said his goodbyes before returning to Rustling Tree Courtyard.

Zhao Hai immediately drank some Spatial Water upon arriving at the courtyard. To be honest, even if the liquor that he drank was very simple, it was the most enjoyable drink that he had in a long time.

Blockhead and Rockhead were present, Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Tomorrow we’ll go to the city and buy some things and have them delivered to Iron Mountain Fort. No matter what, we have over 1000 people in the fort, this God’s Grace Day, we need to help them celebrate.”

Blockhead and Rockhead nodded, then Zhao Hai said, “When you go back to the fort tomorrow, you don’t need to return here. The place should be very busy, you two can go help Grandpa Green and the others. Although the Beastmen doesn’t celebrate God’s Grace Day, they are still in human territory, let’s make them experience our festivities.”

Blockhead and Rockhead nodded again, these more than 1000 people can be considered to be part of the Buda Clan. Naturally, they would treat them properly.

After some time, Megan and the others came back. When she saw Zhao Hai, Megan cannot help but smile and said, “Big Brother Hai, I didn’t you we’re very strong. I just saw Grandpa Gan earlier with a reddened face. There is no way that his capacity for liquor is that low, what type of wine did you drink with him?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “No need to tell me that, you’re Grandpa Gan’s alcohol capacity isn’t a joke. I almost couldn’t head back here, I only managed to feel well after drinking some Spatial water.”

Megan also knew that the Spatial Water can sober one up. When she heard Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but chuckle. Zhao Hai didn’t care about it as he looked at the skies and said, “The sky has already turned black, I’ve been drinking with Grandpa Gan all this time. Wouldn’t your family be looking for us? I didn’t do anything else today other than eat.”

Megan and Laura smiled, then Megan replied, “It’s alright, I already had Grandpa tell Mother and Father to not prepare any meals today.”

Zhao Hai nodded then he said, “That’s great. I’m quite tired as well, I’ll go back to the Space and rest for a while. You go play outside and when you’re done, you can just talk to Cai’er if you want to go to the Space.” Then his body flashed and entered the Space.

Laura turned her head to Megan and smiled, “It looks like Brother Hai is really very exhausted. Megan, we’ll go to the city tomorrow to buy stuff. Iron Mountain Fort will also be celebrating the new year. We must prepare something for them.”

Blockhead smiled, “Miss Laura can feel relieved, the young master already told us that we’ll buy some items for the fort tomorrow. Then I will go back there to help along with Rockhead.”

Laura nodded, “It looks like Elder Brother Hai already thought of this. Right now, Iron Mountain Fort doesn’t need to worry about food and water. I think it would be good if we get some things that aren’t produced there.”

Megan nodded, “Right, we’ll go to the eastern market tomorrow. The eastern market sells rare goods. We can go there and take a look at the various goods used in the continent. I’m thinking of buying some things for the people of Iron Mountain Fort. This is the first year that our Buda Clan reappeared on the continent, we must make this celebration lively.”

Laura looked at Megan and smiled, “Little Megan is quite good, now starting to say ‘our’ Buda Clan. It seems like she’s very impatient to marry Brother Hai.”

When Megan heard Laura, her face couldn’t help but redden, she turned to Laura and said, “Why are you saying that to me? You’ve been with Big Brother Hai for longer, aren’t you more impatient than me?”

Laura’s face also turned red, she turned to the sneering Meg and couldn’t help but tease, “I can’t compare to Sister Meg, she has been following Brother Hai since they were children, she must be the most impatient among us.”

Then Meg’s face turned red, she looked at the other two and said, “Hmph, I’ve been with the young master since I was a child. I’ve already become quite used to waiting. Right, how about I tell Grandfather and Grandmother to delay the wedding by two years.”

Laura and Megan immediately threw themselves to her, playfully beating her while saying, “You dare!” The group became jolly as Rockhead and Blocked slowly retreated with a smile on their faces.

Chapter 455: Killing Intent

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others sat inside their carriage and progressed towards Carson City’s Eastern Market. The Eastern Market was Carson City’s largest bazaar. It was a market purposely built for selling goods. The City made this for retail, sporting a lot of cheap products sold by small businesses. Because of this, the place was the commoners’ most visited area in the city.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived at the Eastern Market’s vicinity, it couldn’t progress any further. Zhao Hai looked at the amount of people present and shook his head. He suddenly thought about the time when he attended a temple fair back on Earth. Looking at the volume of people here, Zhao Hai thought that the two were the same.

Zhao Hai turned to the group and said, “Let’s walk, the carriage definitely couldn’t progress any further. Shue, you look after the carriage here.”

Shue nodded, then Zhao Hai and the others got off the vehicle and slowly walked towards the market. The people gathered all looked at Zhao Hai’s group with curious eyes.

Zhao Hai looked around and noticed the problem. There were indeed a lot of people on the streets, but none of them wore any noble clothing. Most of them wore civilian ones, even servants didn’t dress up.

Zhao Hai turned to Megan and said, “Megan, why am I unable to see any nobles? Look at those people looking at us.”

Megan smiled and said, “Big Brother Hai, you don’t know but Nobles in the continent don’t buy things personally. They have some people specifically tasked to buy things in this market. The nobles would just tell them what to buy, they don’t need to buy it themselves.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then no longer cared and walked towards the Eastern Market. It was currently still winter. Even if the Rosen Empire was warmer than the Prairie, the four seasons were still quite distinct here. On the doors of shops were piles of goods waiting to be sold. People on the shops were coming and going, the place was very lively.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s group stopped following the crowd and started looking around the shops. Blockhead and Rockhead were on their sides with Shun leading in front. When commoners see them from afar, they couldn’t help but get out of the way.

While walking, Zhao Hai was suddenly attracted to a shop. The shops in Eastern Market were very beautiful, they also have some sort of uniformity between them, and were two-stories. The shop that Zhao Hai saw was a bit different, it was three-stories. And most importantly, this shop was quite alone, no other buildings were nearby. Moreover, there were no people coming and going to this shop.

Zhao Hai looked at the scene and couldn’t help but get curious, he turned to Megan and said, “Megan, which family owns that shop? How come nobody went there?”

Megan looked at the shop and smiled, “This is the shop of the Robert family. Their family is the largest seller of general merchandise in Rosen Empire. They don’t handle retail and everyone knows it, that’s why commoners rarely go to this shop.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Let’s go there and take a look. I want to see what things this shop has to offer.”

Megan smiled and said, “I’d also like to come to this shop. They have the most complete set of products among all shops in the Rosen Empire.” While they were talking, they entered the shop.

Just as they arrived inside the store, one of the servants inside greeted them. The guy loudly gave his respects and said, “Sir, Miss, please come inside.” The servant can see that Megan and the others were still unmarried judging by the clothes they wore, so he decided to just call them ‘Miss’.

Zhao Hai nodded and continued on to enter the store. When they are inside, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but sparkle. The furnishings inside were similar to what Zhao Hai saw in the cities in his previous life. On the shelves were samples of the products along with their description and price. Zhao Hai looked at the products and saw that they were cheaper than those sold outside.

One could see a counter upon entering the door, an old attendant was behind it. When the attendant saw Zhao Hai, he didn’t care too much. But when he noticed Megan, he couldn’t help but open his eyes and immediately left the counter and went forward, “It’s actually Miss Megan, forgive me for being slow and neglecting you. Little Five, go lead Miss Megan’s group to the resting area and send them the best tea in the shop.”

The servant immediately led Zhao Hai’s group along and directed them towards the back of the shop. The attendant whispered a few words to another servant as they followed Zhao Hai to a small room.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai came across this kind of business. These small rooms in the store aren’t like hotel rooms. There aren’t any tables inside but instead there was an ornamental sand pool in the middle of the room. There were also flowers suspended on the walls as well as beautiful oil paintings. The room looked very elegant.

When Zhao Hai and the others sat down, the servant immediately came and served them hot tea. Then the store attendant gave a bow and said, “This one is very glad to see Miss Megan.” Then he turned to look at Zhao Hai and said, “Can I know who this gentleman is?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This one is Zhao Hai. Megan told me that this shop has the most complete inventory of goods in the entire market. Today, I happen to need some things, so I came here to take a look.”

When the attendant heard Zhao Hai’s introduction, he immediately understood who he was. Zhao Hai’s identity wasn’t a secret in Rosen Empire, all of the Great Clans knew about him.

The attendant immediately answered, “Miss Megan really praises us, but we indeed have the most complete inventory of products here. May I know what items Mister Zhao Hai needs?”

Zhao Hai smiled and pulled out a list and said, “These are the things I want, I’ve also listed the quantity. I want to know how long it will take you to prepare them.”

The attendant received Zhao Hai’s list respectfully and gave it a quick scan, then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “We have all of the things that mister needed. If mister wants it today, we can have them ready in three hours.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, please prepare them, in three hours I will come back and take them.” The attendant nodded as he turned around to leave.

Seeing the attendant leaving, Zhao Hai turned to Megan and said, “Megan, the attendant seem to be quite familiar with you, do you know them?”

Megan smiled and said, “We do, the friendship between the Robert family and the Calci family spanned for generations. I used to visit them in the past, so their people should know me. I just don’t know much about them, just like how I don’t recognize that attendant.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then drank his tea before saying, “Since they need to prepare the good for three hours, we cannot just wait in here the entire time. How about we head to the West Market and have a look?”

Megan agreed, “Right, there are a lot of delicious things in the West Market. That’s the gourmet area of the capital. There are dishes there that are unique only to Carson City, no other place served them. We might as well have a try.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then the group went out of the shop after bidding the attendant goodbye. Then they left the east bazaar and headed to the West Market.

The West Market wasn’t very far from the East, it was only quite a ways away from the main road. Because of this main road, the city was divided into East City and West City. Which also gave the two markets their current names of East Market and West Market.

Since the East Market held priority to selling goods, there weren’t a lot of restaurants present in the area. There weren’t a lot of choices for those who wanted to eat a meal here.

On the other hand, the West Market gave priority to the food sector. The place was divided into the snack street, the food street, and the kitchenware street. There was needless to say that the food street would have almost all of the ingredients on the entire continent. They even had some seafood, but compared to those that Zhao Hai supplied, their quality was naturally much worse.

Aside from kitchen-related products, the kitchenware street also sold some goods. However, their selection wasn’t as diverse as those found in the East Market. Additionally, one could see that those sold here were much more expensive. In fact, many of those goods sold here were just bought from the East Market and resold here for a higher price.

Zhao Hai’s group weren’t interested in kitchenware. They first went to the food street and bought some ingredients that weren’t present in Zhao Hai’s Space. Of course, Zhao Hai bought some living creatures, for example some magic beasts that he still didn’t have. But after those things were transferred, Zhao Hai became disappointed since they didn’t manage to nudge the Space’s upgrade requirement.

The food street wasn’t short, from beginning to end, one needed to walk one hour to completely walk along it. Zhao Hai and the others bought no less than 100 beasts. But all of them didn’t manage to upgrade the Space, further disappointing Zhao Hai.

After finishing their trek along the food street, they immediately went to the snack street, where their initial purpose was. The food in Carson City were all very famous, and all of them were concentrated on this snack street. With all of these foods present, naturally, Zhao Hai and the others decided to give some of them a taste.

There were a few people walking the streets bringing along some snacks with them. But in this area, the sight was very common, therefore, the group didn’t seem so strange.

Zhao Hai not only ate some food, he also bought a lot to save them for later, these things are only available here, not anywhere else. After that, they strolled around for another hour before taking their carriage and returned to the East Market.

Zhao Hai’s carriage stopped in front of the Robert family’s shop. At this moment a young man stepped out of the store. He didn’t seem to see the others as he headed straight for Megan, “Megan, you came. Why didn’t you tell me? When did you come back?”

Megan looked at the young man and smiled, “Big Brother Terry, I just came back yesterday. I accompanied Big Brother Hai today to buy some things.” She said as she slightly leaned her body towards Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai stared and looked at Megan. Currently, even though Megan had a smiling face, the smile seemed to be quite distant. If one looked closely, they could even see a disgusted mood on her eyes. It was obvious that she wasn’t very glad to see the young man.

Zhao Hai understood what happened, then he turned his head to the young man and smiled, “Hello, this one is Zhao Hai.”

The young man looked at Zhao Hai, still wearing that smile on his face. Although he looked quite charming, his eyes flashed a small killing intent, something that Zhao Hai was very keen on noticing.

Since Zhao Hai had fought a lot of battles, he was very sensitive to any hostility towards him. He can immediately feel from Terry the sense of not only opposition, but also a murderous aura.

Zhao Hai’s mood couldn’t help but sink. He understood what the other party was thinking, but he didn’t express his discontent with the situation. Terry also didn’t feel a change in Zhao Hai’s mood, he continued to smile to Zhao Hai as he said, “Hello, Mister Zhao Hai. Your name surely is a thunder to the ears. Sir is very young and is already very promising. Even I have heard about my uncles talking about you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Mister overpraises, this Zhao Hai is still a very small character. How could I compare to the enormity of the Robert Family’s assets. This one is ashamed.”

Terry smiled and answered, “Mister is too modest. Right, let’s not talk outside, let’s head to the rooms and continue there.” Then he sized up Laura and Meg, he only glanced at them and didn’t say anything.

Seeing his expression, it was impossible for Zhao Hai to not understand what was going on. It seems like Terry likes Megan, and seeing Megan happy being with Zhao Hai made him express a murderous aura.

After the group entered a private room, a servant served them tea as per usual. Terry didn’t touch his cup, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Is mister spending the holidays in Carson City? I heard that the Calci Family’s banquets are very lively every year.”

His words didn’t sound strange at first. But it seems to be not that simple. Zhao Hai himself was a Patriarch of a Clan, this time, he went to the Calci Family for God’s Grace Day in order to accompany Megan, as well as see Charlie, and also form some connections with the nobility of the Rosen Empire.

However, by the tone of Terry’s words, he made it sound like Zhao Hai specifically went to the Calci Family to smooch off of their food and drinks. It was necessary to know that the Calci Family doesn’t have a lot of relatives. But they still have some distant relatives that would come during God’s Grace Day and present some small gifts and in return, the family would give them some food and wine to consume. Terry seemed to group Zhao Hai along with these people.

Laura and Meg’s expression couldn’t help but change. Megan’s face wasn’t any better either. Zhao Hai acted as if he didn’t hear any of it as he smiled and said, “The Calci family had a lot of people, so it was natural that their banquets would be very lively. But this time, I mainly came to the family in order to discuss with Grandpa Randolph about the matters of me marrying Megan by next year.”

With Zhao Hai’s words, it was Terry’s turn to change his expression. But he quickly recovered as he still wore a smile on his face and told Zhao Hai, “That’s great, I will certainly offer you a toast of celebration when that time comes.”

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “That will be very welcome. Seeing that Megan doesn’t treat you as an outsider, Mister Terry should arrive early.”

Terry’s face couldn’t help but twitch, but the smile on his face remained unchanged, he then laughed and said, “Alright, I will prepare a big gift.”

Zhao Hai miled, “Then we will wait for mister’s big gift. Right, Mister Terry, it looks like it’s already late. May I inquire if the things that we ordered have already been prepared?”

Terry immediately responded and smiled, “They’re already prepared. Mister can come and take a look.” Then he stood up and invited Zhao Hai over with a hand gesture.

Chapter 456: Family Banquet (First Part)

Zhao Hai sat in the carriage with his eyes closed. His face didn’t express happiness nor sadness, he just held a calm expression. However, his heart wasn’t very tranquil.

Megan was looking at Zhao Hai with a somewhat uneasy feeling. Zhao Hai had been like this ever since they went out of the Robert Family’s shop. Seeing Zhao Hai closing his eyes made her restless.

Megan was not afraid of anything else but Zhao Hai misunderstanding her relationship with Terry. In fact, she and Terry were childhood friends. But when she transferred to Sky Water City, their interactions became minimal. After seeing him after some years, she saw that something changed with Terry. Smith also opposed to her meeting up with him. Since Megan didn’t have any particular feelings towards Terry, she also slowly drifted away from him.

Later on, with the exception of relatives and those belonging to great powers, all men who came in contact with Megan had suffered bad luck. Moreover, she also heard that these seem to be caused by Terry.

Megan wasn’t worrying about Zhao Hai’s safety, but seeing how calm Terry was today made her very nervous. She was afraid that Zhao Hai might misunderstand. So she just sat there soundlessly, becoming more nervous as time passed by.

Laura naturally noticed Megan’s expression. She was a perceptive woman so she immediately understood what Megan was thinking. However, she thought that Megan’s worries were all useless. She believed that Zhao Hai’s thoughts weren’t on those matters. In order to not make Megan worry, Laura asked Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, what are you thinking about?”

Zhao Hai opened his eyes and looked at the group before saying, “This Terry isn’t very simple. I can see that this guy looks very enthusiastic when meeting Megan. But when his gaze wanders to me, he would reveal a small killing intent, and manages to hide it quite well. And the fact that he didn’t make any moves while doing business with us made me think that he isn’t a good person to deal with. I think he would use underhanded methods to take a shot at me.”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Megan relaxed. It seems like Zhao Hai didn’t suspect her relationship with Terry.

Megan let out a long sigh and said, “Big Brother Hai, it’s alright, there’s no need to fear Terry. Although Terry is the first in line successor for the Robert Family, he wasn’t someone who can cover the skies with one hand. Those in higher positions in their family are also keeping a keen eye on him. The Robert Family isn’t like mine, the heirs of the family all came from the grandsons, making their status quite high. Even if Terry is indeed a grandson of the current Patriarch of the family, there were a lot of grandsons who held the same right to succession like him. Once he does something wrong, the family wouldn’t hesitate to abolish his status as first in line and would just give it to another one. But their family doesn’t have a testing phase like ours, the family’s heir immediately becomes very powerful.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Naturally, I don’t fear him, but I really don’t want to reveal my strength. Because of this, Terry’s actions might give us a bit of trouble. Don’t forget, even if I’m engaged to you, in the eyes of the Rosen Empire, I am an outsider. If I do reveal my hand just to deal with Terry, those nobles might join up to deal with me. When that time comes, I’m afraid that even Calci Family wouldn’t be able to help me.”

Megan didn’t oppose, instead she agreed. Now that she had more contact with this aspect of the world, she naturally understood the power of the nobles. If those nobles did ally up to deal with Zhao Hai, then Zhao Hai’s troubles certainly wouldn’t be small. Let alone the Calci Family, even the Rosen Imperial Clan wouldn’t be able to do anything about it.

Laura also nodded, then said, “Right, Brother Hai is right to be worried. But I’m afraid Terry knows about this too, so if he decides to begin to move, it would certainly be troublesome.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “This person is very sinister and manipulative. We should take care and pay more attention to his future actions.”

Megan nodded, “Big Brother Hai, I will say this matter to Grandpa, making him take note of this as well. If Terry dares make a move on you, then we wouldn’t spare him.”

Zhao Hai looks at Megan and smiled, “What happened? I thought that you have a good impression with that fellow? Did he offend you?”

Megan shook her head and said, “He didn’t, but I heard about how sinister he was, not just from what I heard from Brother Hai. Father told me that since our families are close friends, the two of us grew up together. In the past, our relationship has been good, and after I moved to Sky Water City, out communications have been cut short. But we still see each other everytime I go to the capital. Afterwards, Father told me that he is too sinister, and to not make contact with him. Because of that, I slowly drifted away from him.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Uncle Smith must have known something. We must seriously be careful with Terry, this person hides too much.” While they were talking, the bull-pulled carriage arrived at the foot of Dark Mountain.

Megan thought for a moment and said, “Brother Hai, I think there would be a lot of banquets in the city. Terry will definitely participate in them, you must be careful whenever you attend one.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Be relieved, if worse comes to worst, I can just exterminate his Robert Family, hmph.”

Megan didn’t think that Zhao Hai was lying, if Terry really does provoke Zhao Hai too far, the Robert Family surely wouldn’t fare very well. Not only the Robert Family, even the entire Rosen Empire can be turned upside down by Zhao Hai.

Before long, their carriage stopped on front of Dark Soldier Fort. After the group changed vehicles, they entered the fort and proceeded to Rustling Tree Courtyard.

When they arrived at the courtyard, a servant immediately greeted them, “Young Master, Young Lady, the Patriarch conveyed a message. Tonight, our Calci Family would be doing its Family Banquet. Everybody must participate.”

Megan nodded and said, “Alright, you can head back.” The servant nodded and then turned away.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I’m going to say it, this feast wouldn’t be better than eating at home.”

Megan smiled, “This Family Banquet isn’t much different than normal banquets. This feast is done by the family every year, even servants participate. When the event comes, people would go to the main square and loosen all tensions regarding their status. Everyone will sit and drink with each other, it is the Calci Family’s most popular party.”

When Zhao Hai heard Megan, his eyes turned bright as he said, “That’s good, I must prepare well. Right, we bought a lot of snacks today. We should contribute those to the banquet, let’s go tell Grandpa Gan.”

Megan nodded and smiled, “Alright, let’s go see Grandpa Gan. While we’re at it, we should also give Grandpa Green the goods that we bought earlier. Iron Mountain Fort will also have their festivities, it would be great if Grandpa Green receives those much earlier.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he looked around and said, “Right, Blockhead, Rockhead, you two also head back to Iron Mountain Fort and help Grandpa Green and the others.” The two nodded, then Zhao Hai led his group as they vanished into the Space and headed back to Iron Mountain Fort.

Iron Mountain Fort will also be celebrating God’s Grace Day. Although the things here were still very crude, Zhao Hai still felt the warmth coming from this place. The people in the fort stopped their work and went busy on cleaning up and getting new clothes for themselves and their families. While they were getting ready to eat, everyone’s face were full of smiles.

This was no mystery, because they were slaves, they weren’t able to experience God’s Grace Day. Although they knew when the day was, their master told them that God’s graciousness doesn’t reach to lowly slaves. Because of this, for them, God’s Grace Day was just any ordinary day.

Zhao Hai looked at the people and became very happy. He found Green and handed the things he bought over. He also left Green a lot of seafood, even a Blade-Scale Whale. This thing was huge, Zhao Hai wanted Green and the others to eat this fish and have a very nice evening.

After leaving the things behind, Zhao Hai and the others returned to Rustling Tree Courtyard. No matter what, they were living inside the Calci Family right now, leaving this place for too long won’t be ideal.

After returning to the courtyard’s living room and sitting down, Megan turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, do you plan on returning to Iron Mountain Fort on God’s Grace Day?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then said, “I think I must go back, but I’m afraid that there would be a lot of things happening. Right, what do you usually do during God’s Grace Day?”

Megan replied, “Actually, God’s Grace Day is the most boring day. Grandpa and Father would be going to the imperial palace to attend a banquet. And they would come back very late. At the same time, we would be having a delicious meal and then after lighting some incense, we were free to do what we want.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes lit up, “I didn’t think that it would be that free. Then after we eat our meal and lighting some incense, we can just return to Iron Mountain Fort, what do you think?”

Laura nodded and said, “That’s also good, but Megan seems to have a lot to take care of during that time. Can you spare some?”

Megan nodded and said, “Rest assured, I also want to go to Iron Mountain Fort and celebrate God’s Grace Day with Big Brother Hai. I want to look at how they will celebrate.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I would also like to see how they’d do it. Among those people, aside from Grandpa Green’s group, it would be everybody’s first time to experience God’s Grace Day. I’m looking forward to it.”

Laura and the others chuckled. Besides Green’s group, there were only human and beastman slaves in the fort. Beastmen celebrate their ten thousand beast festival while the human slaves only experience God’s Grace Day as any ordinary day. Both of them weren’t able to celebrate it before.

Chapter 457: Family Banquet (Last Part)

After reaching an agreement, Zhao Hai and the others came out of Rustling Tree Courtyard. They wanted to look for Gansu in order to hand the delicious snacks over and have them served during this evening’s feast.

Gansu was busy in the kitchen, he was truly busy today because he handled the preparation for tonight’s banquet. All the people in Dark Soldier Fort would be participating, the servants will be participating in the eating and drinking. Therefore, there were a lot of food that were needed to be prepared ahead of time.

Zhao Hai looked at Gansu who was about to drink something and then said, “Grandpa Gan, you’re looking quite busy.”

When Gansu heard Zhao Hai’s voice, he turned his head to Zhao Hai and smiled, “Boy? Why are you here? Want to ask me to drink? Today’s no good, I have a lot to do, let’s do it another day.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Grandpa Gan, do you really see me as a drunkard, wanting to drink everyday? I’m here to do you a favor, you don’t need to prepare a lot of food. When we went out earlier, Megan led us to snack street to have some food. I bought a lot of Carson City’s unique snacks. We can add those to this evening’s feast.” Then he waved his hand as a pile of snacks appeared.

Gansu’s eyes turned bright when he saw the snacks. One should know that the snacks of Carson City aren’t considered to be commoner food. These things are widely famous in the continent, even Gansu liked them. They were a very good pair to liquor.

While thinking of that, Gansu immediately said to Zhao Hai, “Good, but you don’t need to take them out right now. These snacks aren’t proper meals. You can take them away and then serve them yourself in the evening.”

Zhao Hai listened to Gansu’s advice and didn’t disagree. He nodded and received the snacks, then he led Megan and the others to head back.

Time quickly passed as evening came. Smith had someone call Zhao Hai over and then the group headed to the main square.

Usually when a large group of people live together, one couldn’t really fathom the amount of people present. All the people inside Dark Soldier Fort numbered towards several thousand people, this wasn’t a small number.

As soon as Smith’s entourage arrived, the servants and guards present immediately came to greet him, some gave a salute while some gave a bow. Smith was also very polite to these people, he gave well-wishes to these people and also chatted with them for a bit. This made Zhao Hai surprised, for Smith to remember the names of these people was something worthy of admiration.

Zhao Hai then knew that something as small as remembering ones name can make people have a favorable impression towards you. Especially someone with a position like Smith, for a master to remember the name of a servant would surely give him a high evaluation among the servants, making him occupy a special place in their hearts.

Zhao Hai, Kristen and Diya followed beside Smith. However, Megan and the others followed the madam to go greet the women on the other side.

Inside the fort, there were a lot of people who hadn’t seen Zhao Hai. Now that they did, they were somewhat disappointed, Zhao Hai looked very ordinary, in their opinion, Zhao Hai seemed to be unworthy of marrying Megan.

Megan wasn’t only liked by Smith and the other members of the Calci Family. Even the servant in the fort had a very good impression of her because of her good nature. She never treats the servants wrongly and was very kind to others. The servants in the castle liked Megan very much.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about what they thought about him. When Smith introduced him to the servants, he greeted them with a smile along with a salute. Seeing Zhao Hai give them a salute, the servants immediately returned the gesture, their impression of Zhao Hai also went a bit better.

These people are simple, if you respect them, then they’ll respect you. Naturally, to get their respect, you must understand how to respect them. In addition, Zhao Hai was something like a half-master to them. Even though they didn’t exchange some words, the servants were still touched by his gesture.

Before long, the people from the other parts of the fort also arrived. The people in the square became more and more. At this moment, there were already several bonfires made in the square, giving it proper illumination. The normally cold square was given warmth by the fires.

There were large tables placed right by the bonfires. Each table can sit several people, Gansu was also present arranging the seats for the guests.

Almost everyone didn’t need to be led to their seats. After all, the Family Banquet was an occasion that happens every year. It was one of the most important events for the family, everyone already knew where they would be sitting. After having everyone sit down, Gansu immediately had the servants serve the dishes.

After the servants have served the food, they immediately looked for their table and sat down. Then it was time for Randolph to speak, this was also part of the event’s proceedings.

After having all the dishes served, Randolph stood up and scanned the people in the square. Then he said loudly, “This year has brought abundant harvests to our Calci Family. We have gained new stable income sources as well as the most important event where we made those Radiant Church people suffer a loss under our hand. Our Calci Family had finally expelled some foul air.”

After this section of the speech, the square was filed with thunderous applause. These servants were the descendants of the previous servants of the Calci Family. Their honor and disgrace were closely linked with the family. In the past, when the family was overly suppressed by the Radiant Church, they found it hard to stay calm. When the family finally managed to turn the tides of battle over, causing the Church’s influence in the Rosen Empire to be erased, it was natural for these servants to feel excitement.

When the applause subsided, Randolph then said, “This year, our Calci Family’s little princess Megan has also been engaged to the Buda Clan’s Patriarch Zhao Hai. Our little princess has grown up, it is finally time for her to get married.”

After he said that, the square became lively. Many people loudly cried as well. Regarding the Calci Family’s rules, the servants need not follow them this time. Therefore, these people dared to be quite rowdy.

Megan didn’t think that Randolph would actually address her engagement at the family banquet. Her face couldn’t help but redden, but she still stood up. Seeing Megan stand up, Zhao Hai stood up as well. After giving the people in the square a bow, the two of them sat down.

The performance of Zhao Hai satisfied Randolph, he nodded and the continued, “In short, it has been a very good year for our Calci Family. Right, no need for more words. Everyone, let’s eat!” Then he sat down.

Seeing the people starting to eat, Zhao Hai immediately stood up and carried a wine glass towards Randolph’s table. Along with Randolph, the table contained the people with the highest status in the Calci Family, Smith was also in that table. In the table that Zhao Hai sat in were the people from Smith’s side.

While carrying a glass of wine to Randolph’s table, Zhao Hai bowed and then said, “Grandpa Randolph, elders, this is the first family banquet that I attended so I came unprepared. When I went out earlier, I managed to buy some snacks with Megan in snack street. I initially wanted to give them to Grandpa Gan earlier, but he told me to give it to the people myself, so that I can get more acquainted with them. I came here to offer them to your table first and then proceed to the others. I just don’t know if Grandpa Randolph agrees.”

Randolph laughs and said, “Who wouldn’t want Carson City’s snacks, it is very famous in the continent. I’ve always wanted to eat them for quite a long time, good, leave some here.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then waved his hand as two trays of snacks appeared, carrying several types of snacks. The quantity aren’t that many, but the variety was quite a lot.

Zhao Hai placed the trays on the table and then bowed to them and said, “Grandpa Randolph, please enjoy the snacks. I’ll be heading to the other tables to deliver them.”

Randolph nodded and said, “You go, give some to the people.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned around to leave.

Zhao Hai proceeded to send snacks to each table. Although there weren’t a lot, it still held some meaning, especially to the servants. Zhao Hai also chatted with them, gaining the servants’ good graces. Currently, Zhao Hai became even more pleasing to their eyes.[1]

Upon finishing to deliver the snacks, Zhao Hai already knew most of the servants’ names. He also came to know the names of the Calci Family members.

Even if Zhao Hai’s memory was much worse that Smith, he has the Space. If Zhao Hai cannot remember, the Space’s recording function can certainly remind him. The Space can even record the entire continent, much less names of people.

Zhao Hai got this move from Smith. After all, Zhao Hai was a nerd, his social skills couldn’t compare to someone who had noble education since childhood. Zhao Hai gave his best to learn about his deficiencies.

After delivering the snacks, Zhao Hai returned to his own table. The madam looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Little Hai, you really are quite sensible. Right, go sit down and quickly eat something. You seem to be the busiest one this evening.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Wouldn’t it be great to offer some snacks? I just want the family to be more lively, haha. Alright, let’s eat.”

Because the people on the table were all considered to be family members, everyone wasn’t polite with each other. They chatted while eating and drinking, the night’s events became livelier and livelier.

The family banquet continued on until midnight. People enjoyed themselves fully, there were a lot of drunk people by the end. Because of this, the square wasn’t cleaned up, they needed to wait until tomorrow to do so. This was also something of custom that the Calci Family practiced.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t drink a small amount either. Zhao Hai didn’t expect for the servants to come over and offer him some liquor. It was not only him, even Randolph was approached for some drinks. On this event, Zhao Hai managed to cement his foundation inside the family as he ate and drank with everybody. Also, because of the liquor offerings, Randolph was the first to get drunk.

Moreover, Zhao Hai knew that Randolph wasn’t just pretending to be drunk, he was truly intoxicated. This made Zhao Hai surprised, under normal circumstances, old foxes like Randolph would pretend to be drunk so that he wouldn’t be offered more drinks. But at this time, he actually let go of himself and got drunk with the servants. This gave Zhao Hai insight as to how the family treated its subordinates.

* * *

Do the math ladies and gentlemen, how tf can Zhao Hai deliver snacks to several thousand people? *countdown timer sound starts*

Chapter 458: Same Camp

Although it just seems like a normal family banquet, Zhao Hai had learned a lot from the event. Although he was well-read, there were still some things that he needed to learn about management.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others came out of the Space. When he went out to the courtyard, he saw Smith. Seeing Zhao Hai, Smith smiled and said, “Just got up? Didn’t you drink a lot yesterday? Hangover?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Fortunately, I’ve had some soup to sober up yesterday evening so I’m still fine. How about Uncle, are you fine?”

Smith smiled bitterly, “On this day of the year, it’s perfectly fine to go all out. RIght, let’s eat a meal together.”

After breakfast, Zhao Hai and the others prepared to head out and see the situation at Carson City. Suddenly, a servant came outside the door carrying a card. He bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, a letter came from Prince Charlie. It was sent over by his servant.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then received the card to take a look. It was an invitation to a banquet that Charlie was hosting tonight, addressed to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai slightly frowned, he nodded then said, “Alright, tell the servant that I’ll be coming.” The servant gave a nod and turned away.

Zhao Hai stared at the invitation, he wasn’t afraid of meeting anyone, he just didn’t like attending banquets. But on the other hand, he also knew that he cannot dodge them because of his current status.

He sighed and stored the invitation. At this moment, Laura and the others came in chatting and laughing, they just came back from a small expedition to Rustling Tree courtyard’s garden.

The group of women came to see that Zhao Hai’s expression wasn’t good. Laura can’t help but be curious so she asked, “Brother Hai, did something happen?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled as he handed the invitation over to Laura. When she received the card, she smiled and said, “This is great. It seems like Charlie wants to introduce you over to his subordinates. Moreover, this is a formal invitation, this meant that a lot of people will be coming tonight. You might see a lot of people from Great Noble families.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I already knew about the possibility of me meeting Great Nobles. Charlie wanted to brand me as someone from his side, letting people know that we’re on the same camp. Megan, you shouldn’t go this evening, I’m afraid this might have an impact on the Calci Family.”

Megan shook her head and said, “No, I’m going. Brother Hai, with you, everything will be fine. Besides, even if they suspect the Calci Family to be supporting Charlie, what can they do about it? If the prince manages to lose the battle, then with you supporting him from the back, nobody would dare go too far in dealing with him. Also, with you on his side, I think Charlie has the greatest chance of obtaining the imperial throne.”

Zhao Hai looked at Megan, then he smiled and said, “Alright, then everyone will go. Right, we should buy some clothes, we cannot shame the Buda Clan.”

Megan smiled and said, “No need, I can just ask the family to get Big Brother Hai some new garments.” Then she turned around to tell a servant to find someone from the clothes storeroom.

Laura looked at Zhao hai and said, “Brother Hai, it is certain that Terry would be attending this banquet. He may find some opportunities to smear your face. We should be careful this time, that Terry person is sinister. He may not act, but he might have some subordinates doing the deeds for him. After asking Megan, it seems like the Robert Family doesn’t have a low status in Rosen Empire.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I know, rest assured nothing will happen. Right, let’s go prepare.” Laura nodded.

Before long,  a person from the clothes room came and took Zhao Hai’s measurements. An evening black suit was then sent over immediately.

The suit was a very traditional Noble clothing. It had very fine workmanship, it even had the Buda Clan’s crest embroidered over it. Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Calci Family’s people to be so fast. With this point, Zhao Hai can see the difference between new and old noble families.

Zhao Hai’s group tried on their clothes and saw that they were perfect. Because of the small notice, Zhao Hai went to tell Smith about this matter, but he didn’t think that Smith would already know about it. Turns out, the Calci Family also received an invitation.

The skies slowly turned dark, Zhao Hai’s group rode his bull-pulled carriage and headed towards Carson City. Since it was God’s Grace Day season, the gates of the capital weren’t closed during the evening. But the passage in and out of the city were instead heavily monitored.

Shun already knew the way to Charlie’s mansion, so he didn’t need anyone’s guidance. He directly drove the carriage towards the Third Prince’s palace. While on the way, Zhao Hai and the others could see the amount of carriages present.

When the carriages passed by and noticed Zhao Hai’s bull-pulled carriage, some of them stopped and offered Zhao Hai their greetings. Zhao Hai took note of these people, they may be Charlie’s people.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s carriage stopped in front of Charlie’s front door. The servants in charge of welcoming the guests immediately greeted him when they saw his carriage, on of them came forwards and bowed, “Mister Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai opened his door and looked at the servant, “I am Zhao Hai.”

The servant immediately said, “Sir, let me lead you to the backyard. His highness ordered me to inform Mister that you shall enter the mansion’s back door. Whenever mister comes here next time, he can immediately head over there.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Lead the way.” The servant nodded and then walked alongside the carriage as it was lead towards the back door.

The back door of this mansion wasn’t a place that people can just pass through. Generally, except the direct family, no other person can come here. This was because this door has direct access to the main courtyard, the center of the mansion.

After entering the back using the back door, the servant immediately led Zhao Hai’s group towards the living room. Upon arriving, Zhao Hai saw Charlie standing in front of the room’s door along with several people. These people also wore formal clothing, along with their emblems. Looking at them, Zhao Hai found out that their titles aren’t high, they didn’t have the bearing of someone coming from a Great Noble family.

Zhao Hai, along with Laura, Meg, Megan and Nier, came forwards and gave Charlie their greetings. Charlie smiled and said, “Little Hai, you came. I actually had somebody send over a carriage as a substitute to your bull-pulled carriage. Don’t you think that your carriage is a bit too slow?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You’re highness, in all honestly, I really prefer my bull-pulled carriage. I think I won’t be comfortable with his highness’ carriage, it is too fast and less stable. I’m just not used to it.”

Charlie smiled and said, “That’s fine as well, come, let’s go to the living room , I have some people I need to introduce you to.”

Zhao Hai entered the room with Charlie. At the same time, Laura and the others were lead by a servant towards the side halls. There, people of the other Nobles were staying,. Some were like Zhao Hai, bringing along several women to attend the banquet.

After entering the room, Charlie introduced some people to Zhao Hai. In fact, Zhao Hai was already familiar with some of them. When Zhao Hai opened his shop in Jade Water City, these people came over and expressed their well wishes, therefore, Zhao Hai were aware of their appearances.

When their greetings came to an end, they sat down. Charlie looked at the people present and said, “I welcome all of you today and I also express my gratitude in accepting my invitation. I will not beat around the bush and directly tell all of you that everyone present here are all the people that I have placed my full trust in. We’re all on the same side, so I hope that all of you can be more acquainted in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded as he smiled and said, “Certainly, your highness can feel relieved, we’re on your side. If something goes wrong, we surely won’t be bringing the trouble to you.”

A tall person sitting by Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, Mister Zhao Hai is right, Your Highness can rest assured.”

This person was from the Yinmi Family. The family can be regarded as an emerging clan. Their family was a hundred years old and held the title of count. Even if they only had the status of a count, they were actually a military family, a family of generals. Their troops were also very good. But since the Rosen Empire was the continent’s most powerful nation, there weren’t a lot of people who dared to provoke them, making wars quite scarce. Because of this, the family had no chance of displaying their might making it impossible for their title to be promoted.

This person was called John Yinmi, a typical martial artist with a frank temperament. But because of his disposition, the Yinmi Family had been having some bad years lately. John was not good at business, and the income from their territory wasn’t that great.

But Zhao Hai actually took a liking to this person. There were only a few nobles with tempers that are straight just like John. This was because such attribute is very disadvantageous for a noble to have.

The people present also agreed to what Zhao Hai and John just said. Charlie nodded and then said, “Father is still in his prime, but even if he tolerates us having our own groups, he doesn’t like to see us flaunting our influence. Your families don’t belong to the core of Rosen Empire’s power, so I hope you don’t attract too much attention to yourselves. At the same time, I hope you also pay attention to others. But be careful with your actions”

Several people nodded, Charlie continued, “Mister Zhao Hai joining my side certainly brought a huge effect on my standing. My brothers doesn’t have any 9th rank experts, they didn’t even have the capacity to invite one. Thus, mister’s help was truly big. But this also drew jealousy from my brothers, even father may start paying attention to me. So I hope that all of us can stay low-key, do not make any moves that can attract attention.”

When Zhao Hai heard Charlie, he couldn’t help but be apologetic, “I have given his highness some troubles, Zhao Hai has been inconsiderate.”

Charlie waved his hand and smiled, “No, mister is just showing his own strength. Although it brought me small trouble, its effects aren’t really that big, so mister doesn’t have to worry. On the contrary, with Mister’s strength, people who wanted to make a move on us would have to think twice. This is already a huge help.”

Those present also nodded, they agreed with Charlie’s words. Among the Princes, the Crown Prince in the capital city can be said to have the biggest influence. The Second Prince has also been exhibiting his talents these past few years. Charlie handles his affairs quite low-key, to the point that he seemed unremarkable. This made people who wanted to hire themselves to him think that Charlie’s strength wasn’t that big.

However, Zhao Hai joining made thing a whole lot different. Zhao Hai managed to invite a 9th rank expert, moreover, his undead also held formidable fighting strength. Most importantly, he was also the Calci family’s son-in-law. With this status, now many people in the continent dared to underestimate Zhao hai.

Zhao Hai coming to Charlie’s side made people think twice about their evaluation of the Third Prince. Some small nobles who were waiting at the sides already threw themselves towards Charlie’s door. Now, Charlie’s people had already reached quite a substantial number.

But Charlie understood that even if his numbers increased, those who were truly loyal to him were only few. The majority of them were just like tall grass, although their numbers looked menacing, when it came to use, only a few were qualified.

Because of this, Charlie maintained his policy of acting low-key. Zhao Hai admired him for this. Zhao Hai also knew about Charlie’s recent momentum, he was actually afraid that the Third Prince would be swallowed up by this increase of power. It seems that Charlie put much thought into it.

Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled, “Your Highness, I know that you’re just saying that to lift my spirit. But if there really is anything that I can do to help in the future, please don’t hesitate to send a word to me. We are all in the same camp, we ought to help each other. Right, Brother John, since we still have to wait until God’s Grace Day, how about we discuss about a partnership. I have a lot of good products on hand, maybe Brother John is interested in them.”

When John heard Zhao Hai, he didn’t understand what was going on at first. However, he was very clear about Zhao Hai’s Haven Rice. This product has received minor fame inside Rosen Empire. No matter who received the rights to sell those Haven products, they would surely gain good profit. Zhao Hai was clearly doing this to help him.

John was filled with gratitude as he looked at Zhao Hai, “I thank Brother Zhao Hai. I will not lie to brother, His Highness has been keeping my family up these past few years. I’m afraid that I’ve already incurred a huge debt. Brother’s help is surely heaven sent.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “My grain business isn’t something that His Highness wanted to sell. So I don’t have a good distribution point inside Rosen Empire. Since I’m looking for a person to partner with, might as well have someone from my own side, so that good fortune won’t flow towards another person’s yard.”

Charlie laughed and said, “Good, what Little Hai said is was really good. Not making fortune flow into another person’s yard. I was going to say something along the lines of that. Remember, we are all family. If we succeed in the future, then I, Charlie, will vow that i will never forget to treat everybody well.”

The people present immediately gave their thanks to Charlie. People on the continent rarely make any vows. Charlie doing this convinced them that he really valued them very much.

After Charlie asked them to sit down, another person, the head of the Heller Family, Tahl, said, “If his highness want to let others shift their attention away from us, there is a way. We can fake an internal dispute. What does His Highness think?”

Chapter 459: Crown Prince Arrives

Charlie shook his head and said, “No, acting might not deceive those people. It might even draw away those who are determined to join my side. The gains might not justify the losses. What we need to do right now is to be united, and be low-key as well. Just like how Little Hai handles his strength. No matter who needs any help, we must help.” The group nodded.

Charlie turned to look at the sky and said, “Alright, let’s head out, those who ought to come should have arrived.”

Just as Charlie set out, footsteps were suddenly heard. The footsteps were urgent, but they weren’t heavy.

Charlie’s complexion couldn’t help but sink, he already told the servant to not allow anyone disturb them. Moreover, the servants outside were his trusted aides. He was very familiar with the footsteps of those people, Charlie knew that the one who came was surely not one of his people

Seeing Charlie’s expression, Zhao Hai knew that there was something wrong. He immediately stood up and took out his Magic Staff. When the group saw Zhao Hai’s action as well as Charlie’s complexion, they understood and also got ready to move.

Then, a voice came from outside, “Third Brother, Third Brother, you in? The guests have arrived, why did you suddenly disappear? Come out quickly.”

Hearing this sound, Charlie forced a smile and said to the group, “Well, no need to be anxious. It’s just my Ninth sister.”[1]

When Charlie said this, John couldn’t help but ask, “Ninth sister? Is your highness talking about Princess Lizzy?” Charlie nodded, then he smiled bitterly as he answered his sister, “Come in, sister.”

As soon as they heard Charlie, Zhao Hai and the others relaxed. Then the doors was swung open as the hem princess’ skirt appeared.

After he saw the princess, Zhao Hai’s first idea was that her posture was very good. This Princess Lizzy’s figure was fantastic, she was about 1.7m in height, but her poise can only be described as fiery. Zhao Hai can confidently say that Princess Lizzy has the best figure of a woman that he’s ever seen.

At the sight of Lizzy’s face, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but blink. She had big eyes, a thin and exquisite nose. Not too think, but still very sexy lips. She had wheat colored skin, smooth as though it has been oiled. Light brown and shallow eyebrows decorated her green eyes.

However, Zhao Hai staring wasn’t because of these, it was because this Princess Lizzy looked a bit  like a person Zhao Hai wasn’t familiar with, but can still recognize.

Keeley Hazell, a British model an actress. A woman who was both sexy and elegant, one of the world’s most recognizable women. Even Angelina wasn’t able to enter the top 100 sexiest women in the world, goes to show how gorgeous Keeley was.[2]

Charlie’s younger sister was actually called Lizzy, Ji Li, Lizzy, good. Although there was some difference in the name, her appearance wasn’t any different. This surprised him.

Zhao Hai more and more thought about how Ark Continent is related to Earth. Otherwise, how did the same beautiful women on Earth appear here?

Lizzy didn’t expect the room to have these much people, she stared. Zhao Hai and the others immediately bowed and said, “We’ve seen Princess Lizzy.”

Lizzy recovered, she immediately exhibited her princess-ly manners as she bends down slightly and then said, “At ease.”

Then the group stood straight. Charlie looked at Lizzy and said, “Younger Sister, why didn’t you wait for me in the hall? What made you come here?”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and the others’ eyes and then pretended to have a desolate expression as she said, “The guests have already arrived, but you still haven’t shown yourself. So I came to take a look.”

Charlie nodded and then said, “Alright, we’ll be heading out. Little Hai, let’s go out and see.” Charlie calling Zhao Hai didn’t evoke any envy. First, Zhao Hai’s had overwhelming strength among those present. If they had Zhao Hai’s strength, then Charlie would appeal to them as well but unfortunately they did not. Second, Zhao Hai had a lot of good things on hand. Some of these goods might be useless to Charlie, but for those middle to low ranked nobles, they were a once-in-a-lifetime road to huge profit. They need something from Zhao Hai, so how could they be offended by this kind of thing. It can be said that in Charlie’s inner circle, aside from the Third Prince, Zhao Hai held the highest status.

Hearing Charlie specially addressing Zhao Hai, Lizzy couldn’t help but look at him. Zhao Hai’s name wasn’t new to Lizzy, she has also heard about what happened back at Purcell Duchy. She also knew about Megan’s engagement. It can be said that she and Megan were called the Twin Flowers of the Imperial Capital. Now, one of the flowers has gotten herself a man.

Also, Lizzy was clear, whether it be Charlie or Megan, those two had eyes as tall as their status, ordinary people simply wouldn’t enter their sights. But for this ordinary looking, average guy to receive the appreciation of the two meant that he wasn’t a simple person.

Lizzy didn’t stare at Zhao Hai for too long. She was a Princess, she has seen a lot of magnificent scenes. To her, she only held curiosity towards Zhao Hai. [3]

Charlie led the group to leave the room. At this time, Laura and the others were already waiting for them outside. Charlie took this chance to introduce Lizzy to Laura and others. Then Lizzy went to join Megan as Laura offered a gift.

Charlie didn’t manage them as he led Zhao Hai and the others to walk towards the front courtyard. They proceeded forward until they reached a very big hall.  This was mainly used as a place to receive various guests, but with a few changes here and there, it has been transformed into a grand hall.

As soon as Charlie and the others arrived outside the door, a servant in front immediately announced his arrival, “Prince Charlie has arrived!” Along with the echo of the voice, Charlie entered the hall.

Inside the hall were more than a hundred guests, fortunately this hall was big enough. If not, this hall might not have survived to this day.

The servants decorated the hall with water fountains that looked like a butterfly exhibition. In the middle of the hall were long rows of tables containing a variety of foods. There were also clean plates and utensils present, those who wanted to eat can just easily go and pick out something to eat.

There were also chairs on the sides of the hall for those who were too tired of standing. In the innermost area of the hall, an orchestra was continually playing gentle music.

When the people inside the hall saw Charlie came in, they immediately gave him a bow. Charlie also returned to courtesy as he greeted everyone inside. Zhao Hai wasn’t far away from him, he had the Space record each name and appearance of the people inside.

At this time, Laura and the others were dragged along by Lizzy towards the other ladies. The other women were talking with each other about, clothes, jewelry, as well as some gossip. Laura used to talk to people, so she was quite familiar with this scenario and naturally knew how to approach it.

Meg was also quite experienced. She grew up in the Buda Clan since childhood. In the past, the Clan also held frequent banquets. Therefore, Meg also knew how to deal with these women. There was nothing to say about Megan, she lived her whole life along these types of ladies, how could she not possibly know how to interact with them?

Zhao Hai paid attention to Charlie’s banquet. Charlie invited the noblemen but it seems like he didn’t do the same for the other princes. The only person from the Royal Clan aside from Charlie was Lizzy. From this point, one could see that Charlie’s relationship with his brothers aren’t that great.

At this time, the sound of a servant can be heard from the front door, “His Highness Crown Prince, Young Master Terry Robert, and Young Master Jason Crook has arrived.”[4]

When these three names were called out, the room seem to come into a halt. Almost everyone here knew that the relationship between the Crown Prince and the Third Prince wasn’t very good. Because of the succession battle, it was impossible for Charlie to invite the Crown Prince in this banquet. This made things very strange.

But what made it even more strange was the fact that Terry and Jason also came along with the Crown Prince. Terry was the Robert Family’s successor. The Robert Family wasn’t less than the Calci Family in terms of status. This was something everybody knew.

Jason Crook wasn’t a simple character either. The Crook Family was very famous in the continent, although they aren’t on the same status as the Calci and Robert Families, they still had a huge influence inside Rosen Empire.

For these two people to suddenly appear along with the Crown Prince to Charlie’s banquet, what did this mean? Does this mean that the Robert Family and the Crook Family has thrown their lot with the Crown Prince? The servant’s announcement of their arrival was still ringing on the minds of those present.

Zhao Hai slowly headed at Charlie’s side. Charlie was staring blankly right now. Zhao Hai arrived at Charlie’s side and whispered, “Your Highness.”

Charlie recovered, he turned to Zhao Hai and saw him nodding towards the door. Charlie immediately understood Zhao Hai, he gave Zhao Hai a grateful nod as he restored his calm state and walked towards the hall’s entrance with a face full of smiles.

Zhao Hai didn’t follow Charlie and just stood there. It took a short while before Charlie arrived at the front door to see three people walking in. In the front of the trio was a 40-year old middle aged man. He looked very much like Charlie, but he had a small beard that was handled very neatly. This made him look very imposing. One couldn’t help but admire how this man carried himself.

Behind him was Terry. There was another person beside him, he was very handsome and wore a decent Noble’s clothing. His figure wan’t very tall but he carried himself with prestige. Although he couldn’t steal spotlight away from the Crown Prince, people still took notice of him.

* * *

( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°) Zhao Hai, you know what to do

Okay, author, I see you.

Not for long

Ah, Team Rocket

Chapter 460: Foul-mouthed Jason

When Charlie was near the three newcomers, he laughed then gave a salute, “Big Brother, welcome. I didn’t expect brother to come to this one’s small banquet, so I didn’t bother sending an invite. But for Big Brother to actually come here, it’s a great honor.”

The Crown Prince looked at Charlie and faintly smiled, “I also heard that Younger Brother has held a banquet, so I decided to stop by. On the way, I met Terry and Jason, so I decided to take them with me as well. I hope I didn’t trouble Third Brother for bringing additional guests.”

Charlie smiled and said, “No problem, Brother visiting has given me quite an honor. So how can Big Brother possibly bring me trouble? Big Brother, Terry, Jason, come in, don’t be polite.”

Terry and Jason gave Charlie a small salute before heading towards the hall. The other people inside also gave a salute to the Crown Prince, naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t an exception.

But Zhao Hai was surprised when the Crown Prince headed towards him after their eyes met. The Crown Prince smiled faintly and said, “Mister Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I didn’t think that the Crown Prince would know of my name. This is really surprising.”

The Crown Prince laughed and said, “Mister is too modest. There isn’t anyone in the continent who doesn’t know how fierce mister is. May I ask Mister to pay a visit to my mansion?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “If I have time, then I will certainly come visit.”

The Crown Prince smiled and said, “Then I’ll be waiting for mister. By the way, I heard that mister has a lot of businesses in hand, is there a chance for the two of us to cooperate?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled at the question, “I certainly have some businesses on hand, but for cooperation? This is something I cannot say. Currently, I’m in a partnership with the Third Highness. Moreover, we’ve already signed a long-term contract regarding our cooperation. If His Highness the Crown Prince wants to cooperate, then I’m afraid you will need to discuss it with the Third Highness.”

The Crown Prince placed a small play on his words. The reason he asked Zhao Hai about the possibility of cooperation was to assess whether there was a chance for Zhao Hai to change sides.

But Zhao Hai’s reply was very clear, he was now on Charlie’s side, it was impossible for the other camps to recruit him at this point. The conversation between the two was clearly heard by the people present in the hall. All of them were smart people, it was impossible for them to not understand the exchange. When the Crown Prince heard Zhao Hai’s response, his expression couldn’t help but drop, but he still forced a smile and said, “That is regrettable.” Then he turned around and left.

As soon as he heard the Crown Prince’s regretful voice, Charlie’s face changed, it was now quite red. Naturally, Zhao Hai’s answer gave him this much happiness.

Zhao Hai also knew that he had already lost the opportunity to get closer with the Crown Prince. However, he didn’t find it regrettable. One couldn’t always be half-hearted, or else they won’t be getting good results.

At this time, Terry and Jason arrived at Zhao Hai’s location. Terry then smiled to Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, I didn’t expect you to come. If I knew, I would have arrived earlier.”

When Zhao Hai heard how he was called, he couldn’t help but stare. The age gap between the two of them aren’t so large to merit such calling. Terry was obviously doing this to make their relationship closer.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t relax because of this, he became even more vigilant instead. From what he heard from Megan, Terry was a sinister person. Moreover, he also knew that Terry was his love rival. For Terry to be warmer to him meant that he was already planning about how to deal with Zhao Hai.

Although he was thinking about this, he didn’t show it on his face. Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “Big Brother Terry is too polite. Brother should know about my relationship with His Highness Third Prince. So how can I not attend such occasion?”

Terry wants to bring their relationship closer, while Zhao Hai attempted to back away politely. He also addresses Terry that way in order to throw the other party into confusion. Zhao Hai didn’t lower his guard against Terry.

When Terry heard Zhao Hai, he looked delighted as he smiled and said, “I knew that you have a very good relationship with the Third Prince. But since God’s Grace Day is approaching, I expected you to be helping inside Dark Soldier Fort, so I didn’t think that you would come.”

Zhao Hai replied with a smile, “Megan told me to come, so how could I not? Hehe, Megan is also quite close with the Ninth Princess.”

Then Zhao Hai turned his head to Jason and said, “Is this Young Master Jason from the Crook Family? Zhao Hai gives his greetings. I’ve heard about the young master’s name, I didn’t think that I would be meeting you today.”

Jason looked at Zhao Hai and smiled faintly, “I’ve also heard about mister Zhao Hai’s name, but I cannot help but be disappointed by what I have seen today.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that Jason would be this impolite. One must know that in a Noble gathering, one would do his/her best to stay modest. It doesn’t matter if the two of you were life and death enemies, if you meet in a gathering such as this, you better show your full smile and act like how a noble should. But Jason was different, this was far from Zhao Hai’s expectations.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Terry. At this moment, Terry’s face expressed a wronged expression. This made Zhao Hai curious, since Terry and Jason came together. Aren’t they supposed to be in a group? Why did it seem like Terry wasn’t expecting Jason to utter such words? Didn’t they plan this encounter ahead of time?

Thoughts churned inside his brain, but Zhao Hai’s face didn’t show any of it. He just smiled at Jason and said, “I’m really apologetic for disappointing Young Master Jason.”

Jason slyly looked at Zhao Hai’s smiling face, he didn’t seem to be fazed. This gave Jason an incentive to push things further. He commended Zhao Hai to keep his grace and honor after such words. While he looked impressed, Jason’s mouth opened, “You’re really unworthy of Miss Megan. Miss Megan is one of the Twin Flowers of the Imperial Capital. It seems quite a waste for her to be marrying a very ordinary looking person.”

After Terry heard this, he turned to Jason and said, “Jason, you should hold back on your words.”

Zhao Hai actually laughed and said, “Young Master Jason is right. I also think that marrying Megan is such a loss. But alas, I actually wanted to be more attractive, but my father didn’t make me handsome. This is such a disaster, hai.”

Jason and Terry stared at Zhao Hai before they both laughed, Jason patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Brother, I must say, I like the way you speak. Hahaha. Good, you’re someone worth befriending.”

Seeing that Jason didn’t seem to be faking, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as well, “You really have low standards for making friends. Are you looking for a not so handsome guy? I must say, you’ve found the right one.”

The three of them laughed. Jason grasped Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “I didn’t think that you would actually read my thoughts, you’re quite good.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Even if I guessed it right, I think there’s no reason for you to hold my shoulder this hard. I’m a mage, I might suffer injuries.”

The conversation between the two made it seem like they were long time friends. It also seemed like Terry was pushed aside. It made Terry look a bit ridiculous. But he still smiled, but it was a stiff smile.

A person like Terry has always been heavily favored since he was a child. He was already quite used to being in the spotlight, no matter where he was. Even if he stood along with the Crown Prince, he didn’t allow himself to be overshadowed. Because he was a successor to a millenium-old family, his status wasn’t any lower than a Prince.

Zhao Hai and Jason chatting away made him feel like an outsider. He felt like the two of them had already forgotten about him, this made him feel unwell.

At this time, a servant passed to their side. On the tray that the servant was holding were two glasses of wine. Jason immediately took the two glasses and gave Zhao Hai one of them. Then he raised his glass to Zhao Hai and said, “I really thought that this would be a very boring party. But I didn’t expect to meet an interesting person such as you. Come, come, let’s drink, after this, we will become friends.”

Zhao Hai didn’t expect Jason to actually be so refreshing, whether his gesture was true or not, Zhao Hai still returned Jason’s toast and said, “Right, let’s drink this glass, from today on, we’re both friends, cheers!”

Jason raised his glass and bumped it with Zhao Hai’s, “Good, cheers!” Then without any courtesy, the both of them downed the wine in one go.

This scene was very visible to the other guests. When they saw the two, they couldn’t help but stare. There were a lot present that knew about Jason. He wasn’t very popular within the circles of nobility because of his frank attitude. He never gave anybody face, because of this, there weren’t a lot of nobles who wanted to mingle with him.

But with Jason’s status, average people wouldn’t dare to not give him any face. Therefore, in common banquets and parties, the hosts would still deliver an invitation to the Crook Family. However, even if Jason came, there were only a few people who came to talk to him. People were afraid to be embarrassed by Jason’s words.

Just as Jason was about to speak to Zhao Hai, the people nearby couldn’t help but watch in anticipation. They wanted to see Zhao Hai’s embarrassed expression. However, they didn’t expect Zhao Hai to actually carry on with ridiculing himself. This move of embarrassing himself was out of their expectations.

Those who weren’t nearby and didn’t hear them speak still kept an eye out. This was because they also wanted to see how Jason manages to embarrass Zhao Hai. Even if they couldn’t hear anything, they knew from Terry’s expression that Jason didn’t say anything nice.

However, what happened next made them confused. They didn’t hear what Zhao Hai said to make the three people laugh and even make Jason look amused at Zhao Hai. This was too unexpected. They were very curious to the point that they were on the verge of approaching the two just to ask what Zhao Hai said. But unfortunately, there was no way for them to do so.

Chapter 461: What Does He Plan To Do?

Laura and the others were also paying attention to Zhao Hai. When Megan saw Jason come in along with the Crown Prince, she immediately told Laura and the others about him. Because of this, Laura was looking at Zhao Hai’s direction, they were afraid that Jason would embarrass Zhao Hai.

However, what happened next was not what they expected. When they saw Zhao Hai and Jason speaking cheerfully, Laura and Megan couldn’t help but look at each other before faintly smiling. They didn’t say anything, but they knew that the other party was fully confident in Zhao Hai.

At this time, Lizzy arrived by Megan and said, “Megan, did you know what Zhao Hai said? Why did that bastard Jason chat with him? You already know how he doesn’t give anyone face.”

Megan looked at Lizzy and couldn’t help but smile. Jason was truly an odd person, someone who didn’t care about other people’s face. This seemed to annoy Lizzy, which led to her calling Jason a bastard.

Megan shook her head and said, “I also don’t know. However, from what I’ve learned about Jason, he surely didn’t utter any words of praise. On the other hand, I’m quite sure that Big Brother Hai didn’t care. Haha.”

Lizzy looked at Megan, confused, then she said, “Care? In such situation, why wouldn’t he care about being embarrassed? Isn’t he courageous and upright?”

Megan smiled and said, “What’s strange about that? Will refraining from being courageous and upright make the emperor mad? As a person, Jason isn’t bad, he just says things that nobody wants to hear. Think about it, what he always says is the most glaring flaw of a person. At this point, there are very few people who would like to listen to the truth. But unfortunately for them, Brother Hai wants to mingle with people who were quite frank. I think that because of this, Jason got along very well with Brother Hai.”

Lizzy looked strangely at Megan, then she went forward and whispered, “Megan, are you really happy with Zhao Hai? I couldn’t see anything special about him. Although he isn’t ugly, he isn’t handsome either, he’s very ordinary. There are a lot better guys in the world. You’re also sharing your man along with other women, are you really fine?”

Megan smiled and said, “What are you asking that? Brother Hai is very exceptional, outsiders simply cannot understand it. Let’s stop talking about this, let’s go eat something, I’m quite hungry.”

Charlie was similarly paying attention to Zhao Hai. He really cared about Zhao Hai so it was natural for him to give him more attention. Charlie also knew about Jason, so he was worried about Zhao Hai’s reaction.

Aside from Charlie, the Crown Prince was keeping an eye as well. Actually, he was telling the truth before, he really met Jason along the way. Terry and him were together, and when they saw Jason, they decided to take him along as well.

The Crown Prince wanted Charlie to misunderstand Jason. If Charlie starts offending the Crook Family for this matter, the Crown Prince would move in and help the family. Then he could place it as the Crooks owing him a favor.

But now it seems that his plans were destroyed by Zhao Hai. The Crown Prince was clear that Jason’s mouth wasn’t something that a normal person can take. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would only say a few words to deal with Jason. This completely destroyed his plan.

Thinking about this, the Crown Prince’s eyes couldn’t help but show a cold light. He was now somewhat envious of Charlie. Why would such an outstanding person arrive at Charlie’s hands. If Zhao Hai becomes the Crown Prince’s subordinate, then he would surely have 90% chance of inheriting the throne.

But it seems that Zhao Hai cannot be his subordinate anymore. So the only way forward was to exterminate him. He must be eliminated. If Zhao Hai survives, then the threat that he could present would be too great.

Seeing Zhao Hai and Jason’s expressions, Charlie couldn’t help but be surprised. Jason was difficult to get along with. But Zhao Hai actually did it, this was something very unexpected.

Zhao Hai and Jason chatted and drank together, they were enjoying themselves too much that they completely disregarded Terry. However, Terry still stuck with Zhao Hai, he was like honey sticking on skin.

Zhao Hai couldn’t understand what Terry was trying to do, but he knew that the more Terry does this, the more he showed that he had something in his heart. Zhao Hai was now even more certain that Terry wanted to deal with him, probably in this banquet.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown while thinking about this. He really wants to know how Terry plans to deal with him. After all, this is Charlie’s mansion, if he wanted to do something to Zhao Hai, it would be very difficult.

However, Zhao Hai was disappointed, the banquet was already halfway, but there wasn’t any movement. At this moment, there were men and women on the middle of the hall, dancing.

Zhao Hai couldn’t dance, so he just stayed at the sides with a glass of wine in his hand. Jason sat beside him, as well as Terry.

Looking at the dancing men and women, Jason couldn’t help but look disdainfully as he said to Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, I heard that you have three fiancees. Moreover, people said that they are quite the beauties. Is Megan, one of the two Imperial Flowers, the most attractive one?”

Zhao Hai looked at Jason. To be honest, Zhao Hai really enjoyed chatting with the guy. Jason didn’t act like a noble, he was more like Zhao Hai’s friends back on earth; those types who always give you bad influence. This made Zhao Hai feel interested in him.

Upon hearing Jason’s question, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “What? You’re jealous? I tell you, don’t rely on your height, nor your face too much. When it comes to female interaction, you are very far from me.”

Jason scowled at Zhao Hai, “You’re too proud. I don’t believe that with my character and appearance, I would be worse than you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “What’s the matter? Now that you can’t beat me with quality, you battle me in quantity? In that case, you have me beat. However, other nobles already know about you. And since were talking about character, look at that guy over there. If he heard you just now, he would be laughing so hard that his golden teeth would fall off.” Then he pointed to an old noble on the other side of the hall.

In the Ark Continent, having gold teeth was starting to get popular. The man that Zhao Hai pointed to was intently watching the noble women dancing on the hall with an open mouth. Saliva was flowing out, enough amount for 100 people to watch in their entire lives. He looked very dreadful.

Jason was drinking when Zhao Hai pointed towards the old noble. When he saw the old man, he couldn’t help but spew out the liquid in his mouth. He choked again and again while Zhao Hai laughed at the side.

Terry looked at Jason and Zhao Hai’s scene and couldn’t help but feel disdain. At the same time, he couldn’t understand what Megan found in Zhao Hai. To Terry, there was nothing good about this man.

After quite some time, Jason recovered, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “This fellow, he was just quite an ordinary man before, how can he be…”

Zhao Hai looked at him and said, “Secretly perverted, right?”

When he heard what Zhao Hai said, Jason’s eyes went bright as he said, “Right, right, secretly perverted, hahaha, you really know your stuff. I guess you’re quite knowledgeable about yourself.”

Zhao Hai scowled and said, “Get lost, and take your smelly mouth along with you, I can’t bear hearing anything from it anymore. Right, while waiting for God’s Grace Day, do you have any plans? Will you join the daily banquets in the capital? What do you plan to do? How about going to the sea with me while enjoying the view.”

Jason didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have such a proposal. He stared, at the same time, he felt strange. He only knew Zhao Hai for a bit less than two hours, but it felt like he knew him for dozens of years. Jason has never met anyone this rude to him. This made him really surprised.

But he immediately replied, “Good, then I’ll go with you to the sea. I’ll take this chance to see how you do your business so that I can overthrow you in the future.”

Zhao Hai frowned at him and said, “Go on, if you have the ability then I’d be happy. Alright, when it’s time to go, I’ll have someone inform you. At that time, you must not decline.”

Jason actually knit his brows and he said, “That may be hard to say, you know my status, I’m not as free as you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, but if you have time, do tell me, I’ll take you out. If you don’t have any, then forget it. I want to find someone to play with, you’re quite fortunate that I haven’t found one yet.”

Jason also knew Zhao Hai’s situation, he just smiled bitterly and didn’t say anything. At this moment, Zhao Hai noticed the Crown Prince and Charlie heading towards the backyard, probably to discuss something.

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brows, but he didn’t say anything. Instead, he ordered Cai’er in his mind to pay attention to their situation.

Zhao Hai also paid attention to Laura and the others, who were still with Lizzy. They were all beautiful women, so they were very noticeable inside the hall. Many men passed by, asking them to dance, only to be disappointed when they got refused.

After a while, a servant came by their side and spoke a few words to Lizzy. Lizzy stood up and said a few words to Laura and the others before leaving.

Zhao Hai wasn’t interested in Lizzy, he already had three fiance’s, he was already satisfied. He also thought that Lizzy’s status wasn’t something that he could handle.

At this moment, Zhao Hai was really hating himself for not knowing how to dance. Otherwise, he would have invited Laura and the others. Unfortunately, the past Adam wasn’t very good at dancing. Because of this, nobody asked him to dance during parties. And adding on to the fact that he didn’t like to practice dancing, this made dancing even more foreign to him.

There was nothing else to say about Zhao Hai. Back on Earth, he was just a nerd. At the same time, there was almost nobody who practiced traditional dance. If he went up to people while jumping around, he would certainly get strange looks.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but regretfully sigh. He thought that he was a bit unfair to Laura and the others. Girls generally want to attend the dances in a banquet. They liked showing off their graceful side. But it was a pity that Zhao Hai didn’t know how to dance, so they can only sit on the sides.

Jason noticed Zhao Hai’s appearance. He smiled faintly and said, “What’s the matter? You want to dance with your fiance’s? Then why don’t you go over and invite them?”

Zhao Hai looked at him with and blank look, “You don’t need to mind my business. If I don’t want to dance, then I won’t dance. I quit dancing a long time ago.”

Jason looked at Zhao Hai with a shocked face, “You won’t dance? Or is it that you can’t dance? Isn’t that the most basic lesson that is taught to all nobles? Why can’t you do it?”

Zhao Hai snorted and said, “The one who my family asked to teach me was an old man. I like pretty girls at that time, and wasn’t interested in the old man. Because of that, I had the old man chased away. From then on, nobody dared to teach me how to dance.”

When Jason heard Zhao Hai’s response, he couldn’t help but laugh and said, “Brother, you’re very good. I didn’t think of that, it’s a great idea. Chasing the teacher away, I’ll try that next time.”

Zhao Hai rolled his eyes and shifted his attention towards the men and women who were dancing in the middle. This Jason really brings you bad influence.

At this time, a servant arrived at Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Mister, His Highness is waiting in the backyard. He has sent for you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said to Jason, “I’ll have to go.” Then he turned to Terry and said, “Brother Terry, I’ll be leaving for a moment.”

Terry smiled and said, “Go, go, we will wait for you here.” Maybe it was just in Zhao Hai’s mind, but Terry actually sounded overly enthusiastic. This confused Zhao Hai, at the same time, he also raised his guards up.

Zhao Hai walked towards the backyard along with the servant. The servant took two turns and three more before they arrived at a small room. After Zhao Hai sat down, the servant poured him a cup of tea before saying, “Please wait here, mister. His Majesty will first escort the Crown Prince away before he will come here.”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at the servant and said, “The Crown Prince is leaving?”

The servant nodded and said, “He is, since his Highness the Crown Prince is leaving, His Highness the Third Prince is going to escort him. I’ll have to ask mister to wait a bit.”

Zhao Hai deeply looked at the servant’s eyes. After serving him tea, the servant immediately withdrew from the room. The reason why Zhao Hai stared at the servant was because the servant was lying. Cai’er just told him that Charlie was still chatting with the Crown Prince. This meant that the Crown Prince was still not leaving.

Why did he lie? What does he want to do? Zhao Hai was full of questions in his heart. If it wasn’t for the servant being familiar with Charlie’s mansion, Zhao Hai would’ve thought that the man was the Crown Prince’s subordinate. But seeing how the servant led him as well as his familiarity with serving the mansion’s tea, Zhao Hai was even more confused.

At this time, Cai’er suddenly told Zhao Hai that the servant didn’t walk away. Instead, he just hid in the corner of the courtyard, making sure that nobody would notice him.

Zhao Hai now understood why the servant didn’t close the door. This was in order to see his situation. Zhao Hai was now even more skeptical about the identity of the servant. What was he planning to do?

Chapter 462: Hallucinogen

While Zhao Hai was confused, Cai’er gave another report. She said that the servant looked quite anxious, moreover he kept staring at the cup of tea on the table.

Zhao Hai stared, he looked at the cup on the table. After he arrived at the room, he didn’t receive any attacks, there weren’t any disturbances nor are there any other actions. The other party couldn’t just call him to the room and just do nothing, there should be something here, the only thing left was the cup of tea.

Zhao Hai lifted the cup and took a small sip. He want to see whether there was something strange with this cup of tea. He wanted to know if the tea was the method that the enemy has thought to deal with him.

When the liquid entered his mouth, a prompt from the Space was heard, “Relatively strong Hallucinogen detected. Can heavily affect a human body, may even cause memory loss afterwards. Extracting poison qualities, strengthening insecticide. Curing the host’s poison.”

Zhao Hai was shocked, he didn’t think that the servant would be giving him a cup of hallucination drugs. Although there was no specific description from the Space, he knew quite well that this was a cup also has some hint of aphrodisiac. And it seems like it had a strong potency.

Zhao Hai placed the cup down slowly. He really didn’t know why the other party would do this. Do they want to smear his image?

However, Zhao Hai wanted to see the entire play completely. He wanted to see how the opposite party would deal with him. Therefore, after he drank from the cup, he pretended to have a dizzy appearance. He kept shaking his head and then leaned on the wall after a moment, pretending to have fainted.

At this time, the servant appeared, he looked at Zhao Hai and pulled out a short sword from his body. He pointed it towards Zhao Hai’s leg, checking to see if Zhao Hai really fainted.

However, this servant didn’t use any Battle Qi. Although the clothes that Zhao Hai wore were from the Calci Family, he also used the armor that Laura gave him underneath. Naturally, ordinary attacks wouldn’t be able to pass through, halting the advance of the servant’s short sword.

Although it had been blocked by the armor, it was still very painful, even then, Zhao Hai still feigned unconscious. The servant was stunned, but he immediately knew that Zhao Hai must have worn protective clothing. He couldn’t help but whisper, “Attending a banquet while wearing protective armor, what a coward.” Then he shook Zhao Hai.

No matter how much he shook Zhao Hai, the body was still very unconscious. Seeing this the servant said, “He should be awake right now. Did he overdose?”

Zhao Hai already knew that the drugs that the other party used wasn’t a sleeping pill. However, the dose that was presented was indeed too much. Cai’er already calculated when he will wake up, she would certainly tell Zhao Hai when the time arrives.

While Zhao Hai was waiting, the servant carried Zhao Hai and walked for a while. At this time, Zhao Hai moved slightly and opened his dizzy eyes. He looked very unfocused, just like when someone sleepwalked. Additionally, his breathing was also very heavy while his face was red.

Naturally, these conditions were achieved thanks to Cai’er’s help. He wasn’t an actor, if he only depended on his own acting, he wouldn’t be able to achieve such an effect.

The servant looked at Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but whisper, “It seems like I put a bit more of the drug. This drug is really powerful. You’re lucky you even woke up.”

Then Zhao Hai reached in front of a room’s door, after which he was pushed in. Then the servant closed the door, making the people inside the room unable to see him.

Zhao Hai stared, but he knew that the servant must be listening outside. While pretending to still be under the effects of the drug, Zhao Hai quickly scanned the room.

It was a very ordinary guest room. At first glance, one could see that this was where Charlie assigned his guests who he didn’t deem that important. The room was divided into two parts, the bedroom and the small living room. While standing in the living room, one could see the bedroom, there was only a screen separating the two. Looking at the bedroom, Zhao Hai was certain that there was another person lying inside.

The person’s breath was very smooth, was probably already asleep. Zhao Hai understood a bit now, the other party wanted to lead him to this room after giving him the hallucinogen. And with the added aphrodisiac, they would wait until Zhao Hai does something to the person in the bedroom before coming in while he was doing the deed.

Now he understood why Terry stuck with him the entire time, he was afraid that Zhao Hai would do something out of his calculations. He also understood why Terry seemed happy when he was called over by the servant, it was actually because of this.

He can imagine that if he really was affected by the drug, after some time, Terry would bring Megan here to see the situation.

Thinking about this, Zhao Hai’s anger couldn’t help but flare up. The other person really wanted to ruin him. However, he was still curious. He was sure that the other person on the bedroom must have fainted. Otherwise, there was no way for the person to not wake up with how much ruckus he has made.

Zhao Hai was now curious about what sort of woman the other party prepared for him. If the woman’s quality was poor, then Zhao Hai was sure that Megan and the others would surely know that it has been faked with just a glance.

Thinking about this, Zhao Hai staggered towards the edge of the bed and looked into who was in it. The woman in the bed was still wearing her gown, and the bed’s blanket was arranged in such a way that only her eyes can be seen. What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that the person lying on the bed was actually awake!

Zhao Hai was startled, he carefully looked at the eyes of the opposite party, her eyes clearly expressed a panicked expression. Even with that, she still lied there motionless.

Zhao Hai was able to confirm that the other party was indeed under medication as well. But the medicine given was different, it should be the Paralyzing Drug. The type of medicine that makes one’s body unable to move while still being conscious.

Zhao Hai really wished that he could immediately kill Terry right now. But he knew that this shouldn’t only be the idea of Terry alone, the Crown Prince certainly had a hand in it as well. Otherwise, the Crown Prince wouldn’t chat with Charlie privately right now.

Zhao Hai raised the blanket gently. But what Zhao Hai saw made him freeze, this was because the person on the bed was none other than Princess Lizzy!

Zhao Hai felt his scalp become numb. The hairs on his body were all standing up. He finally understood that the other party’s aim this time was not only him, but Charlie as well.

Consider this, if the other party’s plans were to be executed perfectly, having Charlie’s subordinate, one he placed extreme importance on, *** the princess, not only will Zhao Hai be ended, Charlie will be ended as well, including Princess Lizzy. One arrow, three birds, this move was really ruthless!

Princess Lizzy was panicking when she saw Zhao Hai. She was called over by a servant, telling her that Charlie has something to ask her. Lizzy didn’t doubt the servant and immediately followed him. Then the servant led her to a small living room while serving her a cup of tea. After giving her the tea, the servant told her to wait for Charlie since he still has to escort the Crown Prince.

Because Lizzy had drank some liquor at the banquet, she immediately took the cup and drank the tea. But she didn’t expect her body to become unresponsive, she felt as though her body didn’t belong to her anymore. She couldn’t even move a single finger, the only saving grace was the fact that she was still conscious.

Then the man brought her to the bed and covered him with the blanket. The man who held him wore black clothes, so she wasn’t able to recognize him.

When the person left, Lizzy became more and more frightened as time passed by. She didn’t know what would happen to her. While lying on the bed, she felt like minutes had turned into years.

All of a sudden, she could hear footsteps. Then a person entered the room, he entered the room and came into Lizzy’s sight. Surprisingly, the person was actually Zhao Hai.

But Lizzy also recognized the state that Zhao Hai was in. He looked very strange, his facial expression was not right, his face was also flushed. Lizzy knew that he had been drugged as well.

Lizzy was not stupid, she was the ninth princess. She knew that she had no chance of inheriting the throne, so she made sure to care less about the battle for succession.

However, among her several elder brothers, her relationship with Charlie was the best. When she saw Zhao Hai appearance, she instantly knew what was going on. But even if she has thought everything out, her heart still felt very uncomfortable, knowing that she had been used by her elder brother.

When Zhao Hai saw Lizzy, he also understood what was going on. He looked at Lizzy, and then he suddenly moved forward. He didn’t stop before he bumped into a screen. Then it became displaced, enough to cover the view towards the bedroom.

Seeing that the bedroom was now blocked, Zhao Hai’s appearance changed. He no longer had his intoxicated face. He went to Lizzy’s side and smiled faintly, he gave a bow before he whispered, “I’ve troubled her highness, please wait for a moment, I will immediately get you an antidote.” Then he waved his hand as a bottle appeared. Inside the bottle was a transparent liquid, he immediately guided Lizzy’s body to drink the antidote.

After feeding Lizzy some Spatial Water, Zhao Hai then told her in a low voice, “Princess, when the effects disappear, I must ask you to not shout. Don’t make any noise, cooperate with me in performing a play.”

Upon finishing the bottle, Zhao Hai put it away. Then he turned around and placed his hands over a piece of cloth. With a bit of effort, he tore the cloth and then pretended to breath heavily and with escalating intensity. He also made an effort to make the tearing of the cloth much louder.

While he tore a few cloths and breathed heavier and heavier, Zhao Hai also kept shaking the bed that Lizzy lied on. The bed issued a sound of being rocked up and down. At the same time, Zhao Hai also had Cai’er monitor the servant outside.

True enough, when the servant heard Zhao Hai’s noise, he gave a nod before walking away. Seeing that the servant has gone, Zhao Hai retrieved the cloths that he tore before looking at Lizzy and said, “Princess, please get up quickly, you must get away.”

* * *

:/ really? We can see it from miles away

Chapter 463: Drinking Liquor While Waiting

At this time, Lizzy was able to move. But she was somewhat embarrassed, when she heard Zhao Hai’s noises, she couldn’t help but lower her head while she blushed. She slowly sat up from the bed and then got up.

Although she can already move, her movements were still quite stiff. However, Zhao Hai believed that she can still manage.

When Lizzy stood up, Zhao Hai immediately went forward to hold her and had her sit down on a chair. When Zhao Hai’s hand touched Lizzy, her body couldn’t help but tremble gently. She quickly became calm while feeling a sense of security.[1]

Zhao Hai didn’t know about any of these, he turned to Lizzy and whispered, “Your Highness, when you recover your strength, you should immediately leave the room. You must do so before the other party arrives.” Then he took a step back before tidying up the bed.

At this time, Lizzy had already recovered, she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Will mister not go with me?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “When acting in a play, it was natural to see it to the end. As long as Your Highness is alright, then their moves are all useless. Your Highness should quickly leave. Moreover, the farther you are from here, the better. When the other party brings people over here later, you can follow them.”

Lizzy stared at Zhao Hai and then gave a bow, “Lizzy needs to thank Mister. Lizzy will certainly no forget this favor.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Highness is too polite. Your Highness, please.” Lizzy nodded, then she turned around to leave the room. Zhao Hai already checked, the servant had already left. Therefore, Lizzy was free to leave, nobody will be able to spot her. Now, Zhao Hai wanted to see what kind of reaction the other party would make when they see the present situation.

After the took care of the bed, Zhao Hai rearranged the screen of the bedroom before he sat down on the living room. He placed a bottle of liquor on the table along with several types of snacks. The only thing that people can see here was a man enjoying his liquor and snacks all by himself.

While he was enjoying himself, the servant who left when he heard Zhao Hai’s noises already left far away, afraid that somebody would see him on the scene.

He was currently waiting for time. The medicine that he gave Lizzy was something that would get weaker as time passes by. When the time that Lizzy recovers came, he would execute the next phase of the plan. This way, when the people arrive at the room, they would be seeing Lizzy struggling against the assault of Zhao Hai.

The servant was very confident in his plan. But he was still very careful about being spotted. Because of this, he stayed far away from the room where Zhao Hai was. He wasn’t aware that Lizzy has already left.

When the time that he calculated came, he felt that it was time to execute the next phase. So he shouted loudly, “Not good, not good! The Princess is missing!”

Although he couldn’t be seen, his voice still reached every single person inside the hall. Everyone stopped what they were doing and became startled.

When Laura and the others knew that Zhao Hai was called over by a servant, they immediately knew that something wasn’t right. This scene was obviously directed at Zhao Hai.

The complexion of Laura and the others couldn’t help but change. People stood up and walked away. Megan gave a glance at Terry and saw a smug look on his face. Megan immediately knew that this event was certainly Terry’s doing. Megan couldn’t help but bite her lip as she stared intensely at Terry. Then she followed Laura as the group headed out.[2]

Terry was too proud to not notice Megan’s look. If he did, nobody knew what he would be thinking

On the other hand, when Charlie heard the servan’ts voice, his face couldn’t help but drop. The servants in his mansion were well trained, even if Lizzy did indeed go missing, they would certainly refrain from shouting and causing such a ruckus. This shout certainly didn’t come from the people of his mansion. If it was indeed someone from his mansion, then the servant was certainly bought over by another person.

While thinking about this, Charlie couldn’t help but turn his head to the Crown Prince. The Crown Prince’s eyes flashed a smug look. But the Crown Prince still pretended to change his expression, he stood up and said, “Younger Sister? How can Younger sister have an accident?” Then he also walked outside.

Charlie’s face couldn’t help but express his anger. Then he became worried, he knew that he had been negligent. This was his residence, and he didn’t manage to see that a plan has been spun inside.

Charlie immediately followed the Crown Prince. At this time, the nobles who were in the hall were also heading towards the backyard. At this time, Terry was in the middle, talking to a servant.

Charlie and the Crown Prince arrived, when Terry saw the two of them arriving, he released the servant and then gave a bow. “Your Highness Crown Prince, Your Highness Third Prince, this servant just came in for a report.”

Charlie looked at the servant and couldn’t help but stare, the servant was actually from his residence. He had seen him before, but he didn’t think that this man was already owned by the Crown Prince.

At the same time, Charlie’s heart sank. He knew that for the Crown Prince to give up such an important piece, then an appropriate result must have been achieved. It seems that things wouldn’t be good after this day.

Charlie wanted to see who was being framed from the crowd. He believed that those who were involved shouldn’t be among these people. When he saw that Zhao Hai wasn’t in sight, Charlie’s heart couldn’t help but skip a beat.

Charlie’s heart sank even further. He didn’t care about any other person other than Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was too important for his future plans, he just couldn’t leave him behind.

At this time, the Crown Prince opened his mouth and asked, “What happened?”

Terry looked at the Third Prince and said, “The Princess told the servant that she was tired, so she thought of going back to take a rest. It was this servant who followed her, but he was surprised when he suddenly woke up in the backyard. It was at that time that he shouted.”

Charlie looked at the servant and said, “Is this true?”

The servant lowered his head and said, “When the Princess told me that she was tired, I lead her to the backyard in order to take a rest. But when we arrived, I was hit and fainted. After that, I had no further memories.”

Charlie coldly looked at the servant. He didn’t think of scolding him, it was already useless at this time. This scenario was certainly arranged by the Crown Prince’s group. Charlie had no choice but to see how it plays out.

The Crown Prince did give Charlie a chance to ask any more questions, he immediately commanded, “Immediately look around the mansion, see if the Princess is still inside.”

However, the nobles didn’t actually move. These matters aren’t something that they can meddle in. Moreover, this was Charlie’s mansion, they cannot just wander around here. They weren’t fools, therefore they stood in their original place and didn’t take a single step forward.

At this time, another servant suddenly yelled, “Your Highness, I just saw a person holding the Princess and headed somewhere.”

As if in coordination, the Crown Prince immediately asked, “Who is it? Who did you see?”

The servant looked at Charlie and pretended to be afraid, “He resembles someone. Probably mister Zhao Hai!”

Charlie looked at the servant and saw the he was his mansion servant as well. Not someone who just pretended to be one. This made his back sweat, he didn’t think that there would be this much traitors inside his mansion.

At the same time, when he heard the servant saying that Zhao Hai was holding Lizzy to go into a certain direction, his head couldn’t help but feel dizzy. He was very clear that Zhao Hai and Lizzy were certainly framed. Now, he understood the Crown Prince’s plan. And this plan had four birds as its targets.

The first bird was naturally Charlie. If Lizzy had an accident in his mansion, with Zhao Hai being the culprit, Charlie will certainly be ended. Don’t say the struggle for the throne, his status as a successor might even be revoked.

The second bird was Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s strength was well known. And the side that gains his help will certainly increase its strength. Because of this, the second target was naturally Zhao Hai.

The third bird was Lizzy. Although Lizzy was only a Princess and didn’t have a right of inheritance, she was the most favored offspring of the current emperor. If Lizzy suffers an accident, she would be shaming the entire Imperial Clan. With this, it would be impossible for her to obtain the affection of her father. This was equal to killing Lizzy, and after that, it would be impossible for Lizzie to help Charlie.

The fourth bird would be the Calci Family. Even if the Calci Family distanced themselves quite well. With Zhao Hai being involved in this mess, it would be impossible for them to not be implicated.

Charlie was quite talented in politics, that’s why he understood everything in a flash. He couldn’t help but turn to look at the Crown Prince. The Crown Prince’s usually does things without much enthusiasm. But when he made a move, the effects would be sky shattering.

Now Charlie understood why Terry and the Crown Prince came together. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be cooperating with this performance. When he looked at Jason, Charlie thought that he was surely not involved. Jason was standing amongst the crowd, and as soon as he heard Zhao Hai’s name being called out, his expression couldn’t help but sink. His expression didn’t fit with someone who was involved in the plan.

In the end, Charlie couldn’t do anything. He can only wish that Zhao Hai was doing well, that he wasn’t going according to the other party’s plan.

But Charlie also knew that the possibility of this happening was minimal. If the Crown Prince’s plan failed, then they wouldn’t be making such a huge commotion right now.

While Charlie was thinking about these, the Crown Prince already had the servant led them towards the room that Zhao Hai was in.

Although Zhao Hai was still sitting inside his room, he can still look at the situation through the monitor. He paid attention to everything that was happening. He also saw Lizzy’s figure following right behind the group, she currently had a smirk plastered on her face.

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, and then with a serious voice he said, “Cai’er, pay attention to those two servants. Do no make them escape, don’t make them commit suicide either. We need a potential informant, I must keep them to ask for their personal confession.” Cai’er nodded.

* * *

New gorl, get!

How “sinister”. Megan can even read everything through his expression.. wtf

Chapter 464: I Have to See

At this time, the Crown Prince has been led by the servant in front of a door. The servant gestured towards the door and said, “Your Highness, Zhao Hai went here.” There was no need for the servant to tell them, they already knew that someone was inside since the lamp was already lit.

Laura and the others followed the crowd with worried faces. While the people around them looked at the group with strange looks.

These people weren’t fools, they clearly knew that Zhao Hai was set up. Because of this, they weren’t that surprised by the situation. At this point, the crowd treated the situation as though they were watching a play. Most of these people even took pleasure in seeing another one’s misfortune.

Soon enough, the crowd has arrived in front of Zhao Hai’s room. The Crown Prince imitated a concerned voice, “Is Mister Zhao Hai inside?”

Zhao Hai, who was sitting on his table, just faintly smiled and took a sip of wine. He didn’t make a noise, he just waited to see the proud appearances of these people turn the opposite way.

When the Crown Prince heard nothing, he seemed to be sure that Zhao Hai was inside. Then he immediately issued a command, “Break in, let’s save Lizzy!”

Terry came in first and kicked the door open, he gave a shout as he rushed inside the room. When he looked at the scene, he couldn’t help but freeze when he saw Zhao Hai inside, drinking wine.

At this time, people had also kicked the walls of the room to break in. All of them looked dull at Zhao Hai’s scene. Zhao Hai was halfway to drinking his wine, he couldn’t help but stop and stare at those who arrived. He slowly placed his wine glass down and stood up, then he bowed to the stunned Princes and said, “Everyone, I’m just hiding in order to enjoy some snacks along with the wine. Why are all of you so anxious?”

When Zhao Hai said this, the first who responded was Laura, she couldn’t help but laugh. Seeing Zhao Hai’s appearance, she immediately knew that everything was under his control.

Charlie was happy to see Zhao Hai. Jason looked at Zhao Hai and then the Crown Prince, he couldn’t help but laugh out loud as he said, “Kid, you dare hide here and drink without inviting me? Oh, and you even have some snacks from snack street. Your Highness Third Prince, can I have some snacks as well?”

Charlie was ecstatic right now, he couldn’t help but laugh as well, “You don’t have to ask me about this, these are things that Little Hai brought. Little Hai, you may not like the food, but why do you have to drink alone here?”

At this point, the Crown Prince couldn’t take it anymore, “Enough, Zhao Hai, where is Lizzy? If something happens to her, you will be held accountable.”

Zhao Hai coldly looked at the Crown Prince and then calmly replied, “I don’t know what Your Highness is talking about. Princess Lizzy’s disappearance doesn’t have anything to do with me.”

The Crown Prince coldly replied, “Someone clearly saw you holding Lizzy, where is she?”

Zhao Hai was without expression, “Who saw it? Where are they?”

The Crown Prince turned his head and was surprised. The two servants from Charlie’s mansion who led them here actually vanished.

The Crown Prince stared, he already knew that this night was his defeat. At this time, Lizzy’s voice was heard from behind the crowd. “For Big Brother to care about my safety, this really makes me feel glad.”

Along with her voice, Lizzy also appeared as she slowly walked forward from behind the crowd. She looked at the Crown Prince with a frosty glare, she also looked at Terry before she calmly saud, “Some people came to look for me, saying that Third Brother wanted to see me. I went with them but I didn’t expect that I would be deceived by that servant. Third Brother, your mansion isn’t very peaceful, you may want to clean it up. Separate the cats from the dogs, otherwise your house will continue to be chaotic.”

When he heard Lizzy, the Crown Prince’s expression couldn’t help but turn complex. At this time Zhao Hai also gave his thoughts, “Third Prince, I also think that you should make some changes in this mansion. I was also called over by a servant, he told me that you are also looking for me, hehe.”

Charlie’s complexion sank as he said, “Little Hai, rest assured, I will certainly clean this place up. I’ve also noticed lately that the mansion hasn’t been that peaceful.”

The Crown Prince’s complexion was currently pale, he coldly snorted before turning around to leave. Looking at the Crown Prince leaving, Charlie didn’t move a single step. Since the other party didn’t consider his face, then there was no reason for him to be polite.

The guests who Charlie invited didn’t know what they needed to do. Some of them followed the Crown Prince in leaving, while some of them remained.

Charlie didn’t think that those who remained were people on his side. He was not naive, he knew that they only stayed because they were afraid of offending him.

But Charlie didn’t care, one can win against a thousand, and Zhao Hai was that one. If all these Nobles left, Charlie wouldn’t bat an eyelid.

However, he still needs to deal with this situation, so Charlie asked everyone return to the hall to eat and drink. The crowd returned to the hall, but with lesser enthusiasm in their faces.

Zhao Hai didn’t return with them, he just stayed in the room and drank liquor with Jason. Laura and the others didn’t go as well, they kept Zhao Hai company. Most surprisingly, Lizzy also stayed.

Zhao Hai and Jason sat in the table and drank while Laura and the others chatted on the side. Jason looked at the group of women and then to Lizzy before he leaned over to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, what happened? Did something really happen earlier? Why does Princess Lizzy keep looking at you strangely?”[1]

Zhao Hai looked at him and said, “Don’t talk nonsense, I almost got into an accident. If it really happened, I would be dead right now.” Naturally, he whispered as well.

After Jason heard him, he placed his wine glass in the table before looking at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, are you telling the truth? Did they really plot against you?”

Zhao Hai snorted, “I won’t deceive you in this matter. This matter has something to do with Terry. When I went to buy somethings with Megan a few days ago, he always gives me the wrong kind of gaze. I didn’t expect that he would act this fast. Hmph, I thought that he would hold back, I didn’t think that he would actually be so anxious. With this matter, I need to be more vigilant from now on, if I didn’t manage to deal with today’s incided. Not only me, but the Third Prince and Princess Lizzy would have been ended.”

Jason coldly snorted, “You’re thinking too simply. Not just the Third Prince and Princess Lizzy, the Calci Family would be implicated as well. Also, your Buda Clan would be finished. After that, your clan wouldn’t have any place to settle in the continent anymore.”

Zhao Hai snorted. Jason then seriously said, “I didn’t think that Terry would be this much of a sinister villain. But Little Hai, you should also know that you have offended the Crown Prince as well, you should prepare yourself.”

Zhao Hai sneered, “If not for today’s matter, will he still let me off? I’m now on the Third Prince’s side. I am already the Crown Prince’s enemy. Him letting me off would actually be more strange.”

Jason sighed, and then didn’t talk anymore. Zhao Hai also knew that Jason didn’t have anything to add on this matter. He then looked at Jason and with a serious voice, he said, “Jason, I’m telling you today that it wouldn’t be good for you if you stay close with their group. Be careful when you meet them next time.”

Jason nodded, and then continued to drink liquor with Zhao Hai. Laura and the others were still on the side and just chatted with each other. Before long, Charlie came in. The banquet was already over. Because the atmosphere has been ruined, he decided to end the banquet sooner than he planned.

Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and Jason as he smiled and said,” You two are getting too comfortable drinking here. Right, Little Hai, come over for a moment, I have something to tell you.” Zhao Hai nodded and then placed his wine glass down.

Jason placed his glass down as well as he turned to Charlie and said, “Your Highness, it’s already quite late, I’ll be heading back as well.”

Charlie didn’t stop him, he smiled to Jason and said, “Alright, if you have time, you can come back here and visit.”

Jason nodded, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, if you have time, go to my family’s fort and look for me. You should know that I don’t have much friends in Carson City, when the time comes, you should ask me for a drink.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then smiled, “Of course, you should prepare a nice wine to drink.”

Jason smiled, “No, no. My liquors wouldn’t compare to yours. You prepare the liquor while I handle the side dishes.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then prepare to hear my knock on your door. I’ll be bringing some good wines.” The two of them laughed before Jason proceeded to leave Charlie’s mansion.

Looking at the departing Jason, Charlie smiled and said, “Zhao Hai, I didn’t think that Carson City’s foul-mouthed Jason would actually find a friend in you. I didn’t expect you being able to handle his words.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “Honestly, I like his character. It’s just that there aren’t a lot of people who wanted to handle the truth, that’s why they cannot bear with him. Fortunately, I am the opposite. That’s why I can become friends with him.”

Lizzy, who was close by, couldn’t help but stare at Zhao Hai. Megan also spoke to her about Zhao Hai’s personality. When she heard what Zhao Hai said, she couldn’t help but turn to Megan and see her infatuated face watching Zhao Hai.

Charlie nodded and said, “Alright, let’s go somewhere else. Lizzy, you should go back.”

Lizzy actually shook her head and said, “No, I won’t head back. Third Brother, with today’s matter, I’m quite afraid of my safety. I must go with you.”

Charlie looked at Lizzy and thought deep inside that the root of the matter was still him. Because he implicated Lizzy, there was no reason for him to refuse her request. Charlie sighed and said, “Alright, come with me.” The group went on to head towards the courtyard living room.

John Yinmi and the others were also waiting for them there. Laura and the others didn’t leave, they went along with Zhao Hai and entered the room. Charlie didn’t stop them. After the group sat down, Charlie turned to Zhao Hai and Lizzy and asked, “Tell us what happened earlier.”

Zhao Hai and Lizzy then told Charlie and the others what happened to them. The more Charlie listened, the more ugly his expression became. He didn’t think that the Crown Prince would be this ruthless. If his plan succeeded, the consequences would be extremely dreadful. Charlie couldn’t help but appreciate Zhao Hai deep down.

After giving his report, Zhao Hai waved his hand as two people appeared. These people were naturally the two servants.

Charlie looked at the two servants and couldn’t help but stare. John and the others stared at Zhao Hai as well. They didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s space could actually store living beings.

But soon, they understood what was going on when Zhao Hai said, “Tell your identities to His Highness.” The two nodded and then continued to tell Charlie who they are.

They being the sons servants was true. However, their parents’ identities were something that the Crown Prince has arranged. Charlie’s head steward was already bought over by the Crown Prince, so he faked these servant’s identities. They weren’t actually the sons of Charlie’s servants, but the Crown Prince’s servants instead.

Charlie and the others already knew by now that these two have been made into Advanced Level Undead. They sighed at Zhao Hai’s viciousness, but at the same time, they also developed more confidence in Zhao Hai’s strength. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this skilled, being able to easily turn people into Advanced Level Undead.

After the servants revealed their background, Charlie became startled. The Stewards was actually someone that Charlie looked up to. He didn’t think that the person was actually a traitor.

Charlie coldly snorted and said, “I will take care of them slowly. Today’s matter was really close. Luckily, Little Hai had been extremely vigilant. Otherwise, the consequences would be terrifying. Little Hai, how did you know that the cup had hallucinogens in it?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “How? I am a Dark Mage. Dark Mages who didn’t use poisons are very rare. In front of an expert in poisons, their move was too easy to spot.”

Charlie couldn’t help but laugh, the others smiled at Zhao Hai as well. They didn’t know about the Space, but a Dark Mage’s reputation regarding poisons was something every person in the continent knew. Therefore, they didn’t express suspicion in Zhao Hai’s testament.

After laughing, Charlie turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, what do you think we should do next? Do we have to swallow this time’s humiliation?”

Zhao Hai sneered, “Suffer a loss without retaliation? How is that possible? From what I see, Terry going along with the Crown Prince was certainly something that they have planned all along. They are quite confident in dealing with us, but unfortunately for them, their good luck has finally run out. Since they made the first move, I won’t be polite anymore. Your Highness, you don’t need to worry about this matter, I will personally take care of it. Let’s see how strong this millenium-old Robert Family really is.”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Megan knew that Zhao Hai was now fully intent in exterminating the Robert Family. But Megan didn’t say anything. She was on Zhao Hai’s side, moreover, it was Terry who moved first. She will certainly not stop Zhao Hai from doing what he wants to do.

Lizzy and Charlie frowned, they were somewhat worried because the strength of an established Noble family wasn’t something that one could easily challenge. Millenium-old Clans in the continent were rarely destroyed completely. Most of these clans only fell from grace because of some sort of internal conflict. Zhao Hai wanting to deal with the entire Robert Family was something the two of them thought was impossible.

* * *

She got baited, Jason

Chapter 465: A Brother’s Thoughts

Zhao Hai looked at their faces and smiled faintly, “Your Highness, don’t worry, I will certainly take care. If we continue to let him do these things, more and more families will be joining the Crown Prince’s side. And then your hope of getting the throne would get smaller and smaller. I just want those who follows the Crown Prince to know that they won’t be safe even if they are a millennium-old clan.”

Zhao Hai’s words sounded crazy, it was something that he was intent on following through. Those who heard it would certainly feel shock, their hearts would be beating faster.

But this reaction wasn’t an exaggeration. It was because the people who Zhao Hai wanted to deal with belonged to a millenium-old family. These families were held on being the most powerful forces in the continent. Even Royale Clans wouldn’t dare to offend these families. This was because there are only a few Royal Clans in the continent, while there are a lot of millenium-old clans.

Zhao Hai expressing his intent on waging war with a millennium family made the hearts of those who were present burn with anticipation. Charlie looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Good, Little Hai, getting hit and not retaliating isn’t your style. Good, good.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Highness, you don’t need to worry about this matter. What is most important for you right now is cleaning up your mansion. Otherwise, you wouldn’t be able to rest freely.”

Charlie smiled, “Rest assured, nothing wrong will happen. But this wouldn’t be very simple to fix, however, since they are already exposed, I will slowly take care of these people.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s good. Your Highness, it’s already quite late. I need to go back, I’m afraid that I won’t be able to return in the next few days. I’m too busy.”

Charlie nodded and said, “Alright, we have no choice. But if you have some free time, don’t forget to come visit.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he stood up. Said his goodbyes to Lizzy and then proceeded to leave.

Seeing that Zhao Hai was going to leave, Lizzy immediately stood up and looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister Zhao Hai, will I meet you at the imperial banquet?”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t’t think that Lizzy would ask him about this. But he shook his head and said, “I don’t think so. With my status, I don’t have any qualifications to attend the banquet. Also, I really don’t like attending such gatherings.”

Charlie stared profoundly at Zhao Hai. Then he smiled faintly and said, “If you want to participate, there will be no problem, I can just take you there myself. What do you think? Will you come?”

Zhao Hai looked at Charlie and then to Lizzy, he still shook his head and said, “Consider this matter finished, I don’t know anyone there, I will just be bored. I also don’t like banquets.”

Charlie nodded and said, “Alright, if you don’t want to go I won’t force you. You go back first, come back here if you have time.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he led Laura and the others to leave.

Lizzy looked at Laura and the others who were following Zhao Hai, she couldn’t help but feel envy. Charlie looked at Lizzy’s expression, he sighed in his heart and murmured, “Little Hai is really too outstanding, it seems like he would have more wives in the future. He is the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, and his clan doesn’t have that much members. I’m certain that he will get many wives, to increase the family’s branches as much as possible.”

Charlie said this intentionally because since Zhao Hai rescued Lizzy, Lizzy might hold a special sentiment towards Zhao Hai inside her heart. Charlie knew that if this sentiment were to evolve, it would turn into love. He said this because he wanted Lizzy to lose heart. Charlie was very clear about how much pride Lizzy held inside her heart. She will certainly not agree to marry someone who had other women.

If Zhao Hai married before, then Lizzy wouldn’t have anything to say. However, if Zhao Hai wanted to marry others in the future, it was certain that Lizzy wouldn’t be able accept it. Charlie wanted Lizzy to understand that Zhao Hai will certainly have more wives in the future.

When she heard Charlie’s words, Lizzy’s complexion changes slightly before quickly recovering. However, Charlie knew that his words were already received.

Charlie didn’t say anything else on this topic, he turned to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, now that Big Brother has already erased his consideration for us, you need to be more careful. Right, I really didn’t want this to happen, but Big Brother actually included you in his plots, I apologize deeply for this.”

Lizzy shook her head and said, “No, Third Brother, this matter isn’t yours to blame. I just didn’t expect him to do such a thing. Third Brother, starting today, I will strongly support you.”

Charlie smiled bitterly, “Forget it, the reason why father likes you is because you never cared about these things. If you participate, I’m afraid that you won’t be able to keep your current status. It’s alright, no need to worry about your Third Brother. Nobody bullies your Third Brother and lives comfortably later.”

Lizzy stared at Charlie, she didn’t say anything more about this matter. She just gave a small salute before saying, “Third Brother, I will be heading back.” Then she turned around to leave.

In Rosen Empire, after a Prince has grown up, then he must construct his own palace outside. This rule didn’t apply to princesses, they would be staying inside the Imperial Palace before getting married. If she was favored, the Emperor would bestow her a residence in the palace, allowing her to stay in the palace along with her husband. If you aren’t favored, the princess can only leave the palace to live with her husband.

Zhao Hai still wasn’t married. Lizzy wasn’t engaged as well, because of this, she still lived inside the Imperial Palace. Seeing Lizzy leave, Charlie couldn’t help but sigh. He pained for Lizzy’s well-being. She’s a kindhearted woman and sensible as well, but she was also a bit arrogant and would never put an average man in her eyes.

Zhao Hai saving her today certainly left a big impact. Moreover, Zhao Hai’s beautiful handling of the situation made Lizzy change her thoughts about him.

The only issue about this was that Zhao Hai had already three fiancees, but it looks like it would be four. This is because Laura had Nier always right by her side. Due to this, Charlie cannot propose to Lizzy the matter of marrying Zhao Hai.

From Charlie’s point of view, Zhao Hai’s strength was worthy of Lizzy. If Zhao Hai didn’t have a lot of fiancees, then Charlie would be happy to see their marriage. In the end, he was an older brother who didn’t want someone to hurt his little sister. Charlie didn’t want to see her sister fighting with other women for the favor of his husband.

Zhao Hai didn’t think of any of these right now, he was currently sitting inside his carriage along with Laura and the others. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, how are planning to deal with Terry?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Bring the Robert Family down from their position as one of the top families in the continent. If they really wanted to deal with me, then I will exterminate them.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “Brother Hai, so how are we going to do it?”

Zhao Hai looked outside the window and then said, “Rest assured, no need to worry about it. I have already sent a Blood Hawk out, letting the Space map out the entire Rosen Empire. Then when we return, Megan, I will have to ask your family to map out all of the Robert Family’s businesses inside the Empire.”

Megan nodded, to be honest, if Zhao Hai wanted to deal with the Robert Family before this day, she would certainly try her best to stop him. The Robert and Calci Families always had a good relationship from generation to generation. But what Terry did today was excessive, Zhao Hai wanting to make an action against the Robert Family was quite normal.

Zhao Hai then said, “Also, tell father and grandfather about what happened earlier. Make them prepare. If the Robert Family really wants to fight with us, then the Calci Family must be ready to take over the Robert Family’s businesses.

Megan nodded and said, “Be careful Brother Hai. The Robert Family is a Millennium-old clan, they are not that easy to deal with.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t speak. Now that he has a plan, he certainly won’t make the Robert Family’s life any easier.

His carriage immediately returned to Dark Soldier Fort. Because it was already late, except for the guards and the servants who worked the night shift, everybody has already rested. Zhao Hai didn’t want to disturb anyone, he went directly to his courtyard before going into the Space to rest.

Tonight, Charlie invited the Calci Family to the banquet, but Randolph didn’t send anyone. This was to show the other people that the Calci Family wasn’t supporting Charlie yet. Zhao Hai and Charlie might be partners, but Zhao Hai’s matters have nothing to do with the Calci Family.

Another reason was because Megan was already planning to attend. Although Megan was engaged to Zhao Hai, the two still weren’t married. Therefore, Megan can act on behalf of the Calci Family, making sure that Charlie didn’t get offended while not making other people misunderstand.

The night went by without any issues. The next morning, Zhao Hai combed his hair and washed his face before having breakfast with the others. Just as he took a bite, Smith sent someone over to fetch him.

Zhao Hai also knew that Smith was already aware of yesterday’s matters. It seems like Smith still wanted to ask Zhao Hai about the details. Zhao Hai didn’t hesitate, he immediately went to the Rustling Tree Courtyard’s living room while being led by the servant. Smith wasn’t the only one present, Randolph came as well.

After the group gave each other greetings, Randolph had Zhao Hai sit down before asking, “Little Hai, carefully tell us about yesterday’s matters.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he told Randolph what happened yesterday evening. Zhao Hai’s serious voice said, “This matter was certainly orchestrated by the cooperation between Terry and the Crown Prince. Moreover, I’m afraid that the Robert Family had already thrown their lot with the Crown Prince. Even if the Robert Family didn’t, then Terry certainly did.”

After Randolph heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but frown and said, “It certainly isn’t just Terry allying with the Crown Prince. It seems like this action was decided by the Robert Family itself. Terry is their successor, him going to the Crown Prince’s side without the approval of the family would be very strange.”

Smith also nodded, “It seems to be like this. I didn’t think that the Robert Family would actually support the Crown Prince publicly. This is really a strange case. Father, do you think that we should fully support the Third Prince?”

Chapter 466: Going To Jason’s Home

Randolph shook his head and said, “Consider that matter finished. How the Robert Family wants to go with their matters is none of our business. We shall retain our stance with regards to the succession battle. Right Little Hai, how will you deal with the Robert Family?” Randolph knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t someone who would suffer without retaliating. With how Terry plotted against him, Zhao Hai will surely not forget this matter.

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said “In a few days, I will deal with the Robert Family. But if they continue to annoy me, then I would have no choice but to exterminate them.”

Randolph and Smith doesn’t know of Zhao Hai’s true strength. But when they heard what he said, they couldn’t help but knit their eyebrows. They thought that Zhao Hai’s words are too boastful.

Smith opened his mouth and said, “Little Hai, you need to be careful with millenium-old Clans, they aren’t that simple. You should know that 9th ranks experts can live more than a thousand years. Everybody knew that the Robert Family had five 9th rank experts. But we need to account for the hidden trump cards that they have, you need to act carefully.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I will take care. Uncle doesn’t need to worry.”

Smith also knew that Zhao Hai understood what he meant, so he didn’t warn him any longer. He just nodded and said, “What are you planning to do today?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “I had a great time with Jason yesterday evening, we have become friends. Today, I think I’ll head to the Crook Family and look for him. At the same time, I might as well give the family some gifts. If those foods go past God’s Grace Day, they would certainly taste different.”

Smith nodded and said, “Alright, that’s good. Even if the Crook Family isn’t a millennium-old clan, they are also quite a competent family in Rosen Empire. You should go meet them.”

Randolph nodded as well, “I really didn’t expect you to befriend that boy Jason. That boy’s foul mouth is very famous. He has managed to annoy a lot of people, aside from you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t say anything. Randolph looked at the sky and said, “You should head there early. I also have some matters to take care of. I’ll leave first.” Then he stood up and turned around to leave. Zhao Hai and Smith escorted him to the exit of the courtyard.

After seeing Randolph leave, Smith brought Zhao Hai back to the room. After they sat down, Smith asked, “Little Hai, tell me. Do you really have the strength and confidence to deal with the Robert Family?”

Zhao Hai didn’t mince words and directly said, “I’m very confident.”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and couldn’t help but frown, he didn’t believe Zhao Hai. He knew that one couldn’t just be confident in this matter, millenium-old families aren’t a joke. Zhao Hai being this confident made Smith think that Zhao Hai was too arrogant.

When he saw Smith’s expression, Zhao Hai knew what he was thinking. He added, “Uncle, rest assured, If I’m confident, then I can definitely do it. You don’t have to worry.”

Smith looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Consider this matter done. Whatever happens, me and father wouldn’t mind it. Do what you can, know that the Calci Family is behind you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Thank you uncle. If there’s nothing else, then I will leave first.”

Smith nodded and said, “Go.” Zhao Hai stood up, he gave a small salute and went to prepare for his trip to the Crook Family. He also prepared the seafood that he was going to gift them.

After returning to his place, Zhao Hai discussed his plan to head to the Crook Family with Laura and the others. The women didn’t oppose, they clearly saw how comfortable Zhao Hai was with Jason. With how the two clicked with each other, how can they possibly oppose.

Zhao Hai didn’t plan to take Laura and the others today. This time, he only meant to visit the family and give them a gift, so it wouldn’t be good if he brought the women along. He had Shue and Shun prepare his carriage before he slowly headed to the Crook Family’s residence.

The Crook Family’s Castle was also constructed outside Carson City. It wasn’t that far away from the Calci Family’s place, just a few hills away. It would take an hour of travel before arriving.

The small mountain that the Crook Family constructed their castle in was quite similar to the Calci Family, only a bit smaller. There weren’t many trees on the hill, and the fort was as large as the fort of the Calci Family. However, the fort looked a bit newer than the Dark Soldier Fort, and it had a very practical design.

There was also a small house at the foot of the hill, guarding the road that headed towards the fort. There was a bar on the road as well. When Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived, a servant went out of the small house. The servant first examined Zhao Hai’s emblem, he was stunned, this was because he hadn’t seen this emblem before.

However, this servant was well-trained. He recognized that the emblem belonged to a Count. Although it was insignificant compared to the Crook family, the servant still didn’t dare underestimate the person inside the carrise. Before long, the servant arrived at the carriage and gave Shun a bow before asking, “May I know who is the owner of this carriage?”

Shun, who was driving the carriage, returned the servant’s salute before answering, “Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Zhao Hai Buda. He came to visit Young Master Jason Crook.”

As soon as the servant heard that it was the Buda Clan, he stared for a moment. He has heard about the Buda Clan, moreover, the way Jason and Zhao Hai interacted last night was also relayed to him. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to visit today.

The servant immediately answered, “Mister, please.” He said before removing the roadblock. This servant knew that the Young Master of the family wasn’t someone who had a lot of noble friends. For him to befriend the Buda Clan’s Patriarch was surely a welcome surprise.

In a blink of an eye, the obstacles have been removed. The servant gave another bow as the carriage headed up the hill. At the same time, a Wind Falcon flew up the mountain.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived at the Crook Family’s Castle, Jason was already there waiting for him. As soon as he saw Zhao Hai getting off the carriage, Jason immediately welcomed him. He laughed and said, “Well, you really came very quickly.”

Zhao Hai stared at him and said, “What? Am I not welcome? If I’m not, then I might as well leave.”

Jason held Zhao Hai and said, “Leave? I greeted you in the front door, if you don’t leave behind some liquor then I won’t release you.” Then he pulled Zhao Hai towards the fort. They didn’t notice that the eyes of the guards and the servants were about to pop out of their sockets.

In Carson City, Jason was certainly a unique type of person. It was not only the other nobles who thought to, the Crook Family as well. He had a foul mouth, his temperament wasn’t good as well. Because of this, he didn’t have any friends even after all these years. Those who came to the fort always looked for Jason’s brothers, none bothered to visit him.

Although Jason was good to the family’s servants, those servants couldn’t be his friends, even if they have a good relationship with him. It was precisely because of this that the people present were quite surprised to see how Jason was very polite to another noble. Even the Princes wouldn’t receive such face from Jason.

After entering the fort, Zhao Hai noticed that even if the fort was as big as the the Calci Family’s fort, it lacked the ancient atmosphere. It felt like it’s history was quite insufficient. Since the fort was as large as Dark Soldier fort, naturally it also had a special carriage for visitors to ride in when they visit. However, their carriage wasn’t as luxurious as the Calci Family’s, it looked very simple.

After they entered three doors, they finally arrived at a courtyard. Jason brought Zhao Hai to the place that he was staying at. When the two had sat down, Zhao Hai noticed the fruit trees planted in the courtyard and smiled, “Interesting. Other people generally wouldn’t plant fruit trees inside their courtyards, only some ornamental plants. This is my first time seeing someone plant fruit trees in theirs.”

Jason snorted and said, “Why must I be the same with them. Hmph, I actually like planting fruit trees.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t comment anything more. Jason was really a different type of person much to his liking. Zhao Hai turned to Jason and said, “Right, is your father inside the fort?  I want to pay my respects.”

Jason looked at the time and said, “At this time, father and grandfather should be in the study handling official business. Alright, let’s go see them right now. While we head there, I’ll have someone prepare us some dishes. We’ll drink after we come back.” The he stood up and led Zhao Hai to leave the courtyard as they walked towards the main hall.

After they left Jason’s courtyard, they walked through the middle of the fort and before long, they arrived at the main area. This main area had the same function as the Calci Family’s main area. It was used for official work and not for anyone’s residence. Therefore, Jason’s father and grandfather should be here at this time, working.

When they arrived at the main area’s living room, Jason had Zhao Hai sit down before he turned his head towards a servant who served them tea and said, “Go inform father and grandfather that Zhao Hai, the Patriarch of the Buda Family has come to visit.” The servant issued a bow and then left.

Zhao Hai looked at Jason and smiled, “Your father and grandfather should be quite busy. Why are you so carefree? Do you not manage any affairs of the family?”

Jason smiled and said, “I’ve left it to my steward. Currently, I’m learning from father and grandfather. But since God’s Grace Day is arriving, the two of them had been very busy, they simply didn’t have the time to teach me, thus, explaining my free time.”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “I’m envious that you can be this relaxed. Not like me, who needed to depend on myself. With how tired I am, I’m no better than a deceased person.”

Jason gave Zhao Hai a look and said, “You have less worries, nobody monitors you. Unlike me, father and grandfather always watches over me, I actually have little freedom.”

Zhao Hai smiled and didn’t say anything. Jason was just like him when he was back on earth. He always complained that he was always watched and was not free at all. But he hasn’t thought that this constant watch was also a blessing. If nobody watched over him, he would certainly suffer some hardships.

But Zhao Hai also knew that even if he told this to Jason it will certainly pass through deaf ears. These types of people wouldn’t believe you no matter how many times you tell them. They needed to see it themselves before they agree.

Chapter 467: Having Such a Friend is a Blessing

Seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t respond, Jason didn’t care. He kept busily talking and drinking tea with Zhao Hai. At this time, sounds of footsteps can be heard from the living room. Before long, people appeared from the living room’s door.

Zhao Hai and Jason immediately stood up. Zhao Hai looked at the newcomers, the one at the lead was an old person, he looked quite old but his face was still healthy and full of life. He wore a very gorgeous noble clothing. Although the old man’s posture wasn’t that straight, his temperament along with his clothes made one unable to underestimate him.

Along with the old man was a middle aged man. The man looked much like Jason, but his face was serious and he also had clear eyes. He seemed like an astute person. At the back of the two was the servant who went to inform them.

Jason hastily bowed to the old man and the man, “Grandfather, Father, this is the Buda Clan’s Patriarch, Zhao Hai. Little Hai, this is my Grandfather, this is my Father.”

Zhao Hai immediately gave a bow and said, “Zhao Hai has met Grandfather and Uncle.”

Jason’s Grandfather and Father sized Zhao Hai up before Jason’s Grandfather smiled and said, “Good, little Jason doesn’t have any friends. You should come here often.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I will certainly visit if I have time. But I’m going everywhere all year round, I don’t have that much free time. I was only able to come this time because Megan asked me to visit the Capital. After this, I won’t be here most of the time. But Grandfather and Father can rest assured, I will be Jason’s friend forever.”

Jason’s Grandfather nodded, “Alright, I feel relieved by your words. But Little Hai, I’m just a bit curious, Little Jason talks very frankly, making people of the Rosen Empire quite uncomfortable. How did you become friends with him instead? Can you bear his mouth?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I just like talking with him, I don’t see anything wrong with Jason. Although he has a frank attitude, saying everything he thinks about, he is a good person, a good friend. There aren’t a lot of people that can handle the truth in these times.”

Jason’s Grandfather stared, if those words were said by someone with the same age as him, then it wouldn’t have been strange. But the one who said it was actually the same age as Jason. One cannot just have those kinds of thoughts at that age.

Jason’s Father haven’t said anything since coming in the living room. He was just observing Zhao Hai, when Zhao Hai said those words, he couldn’t help but stare at the young man.

Jason’s Grandfather nodded, “Right, nicely said, it’s good that you became friends with Jason. Don’t go home at noon, let’s go drink together.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, I’ll go drink with Grandfather and Uncle later. Right, little nephew bought some gifts. I’ll take them out outside so you can have a servant take them away.” Then he went towards the door and released the seafood that he prepared for the Crook Family.

Seafood were rare in the continent, but for a Great Noble Clan like the Crook Family, those things aren’t foreign. However, the seafood that Zhao Hai took out are much better in quality compared to the ones they have consumed before.

After he took out his gift, Zhao Hai turned to Jason and said, “Jason, make someone take these away. I have no other good stuff to give, I can only give these seafood to your family.”

Jason laughed and said, “Good, good, these are quite delicious, you really do have the best things on hand. Hahaha.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t waste anymore time, go get these to the kitchen immediately. Right, I’ve also brought some nice liquor.” Then he also retrieved a several big leather bags, all filled with Milk Wine.

Seeing Zhao Hai and Jason chatting and laughing, Jason’s grandfather said, “Little Jason finally found himself a good friend. He even brought some gifts.”

Jason’s father nodded, “I actually didn’t think that Little Jason would have a friend given that he has that foul mouth of his. I’ve been worried for this boy.”

Jason’s Grandfather smiled, “This Zhao Hai child is very good, hahaha. Not many people can handle the truth. Good, good.”

Then Jason’s grandfather continued, “I’ve doubted Little Hai before. But now that I see him, he seemed like a good man. To make such a friend, Little Jason is surely blessed in his life.”

Jason’s father nodded and sighed, “A good friend is quite a hard to come by. Especially for someone of our status, Jason’s luck is really good.”

At this time, servants came and carried Zhao Hai’s gifts towards the storehouse. Zhao Hai and Jason returned to the living room along with Jason’s grandfather and father, the two looking at Zhao Hai with gentle gazes.

Jason’s grandfather looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, think of this place like your house. If you want to come, just come, you don’t need to be polite.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Certainly, Grandfather can rest assured.”

Then Jason’s grandfather stood up and said, “Alright, you young men go play around. Also, remember to not drink too much, you still need to accompany me later at noon. If you don’t, I will be all alone later.”

Zhao Hai nodded with a smile. Looking at the two men leaving, Jason turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Let’g head to my courtyard. I have a few snacks there. Let’s go have some cups, we don’t need to drink much anyway.”

After pouring two cups of liquor, Jason looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, do you consider yesterday’s matter finished? Don’t you want to deal with Terry and the Crown Prince?”

Zhao Hai smiled at Jason and said, “What? You want to help me? Can you do it? You know the Crook Family’s standing, it wouldn’t be good if you involve yourself in this matter. Don’t act carelessly.”

Jason snorted and said, “I become angry everytime I think about what happened last night. Not only did they plot against you, they somewhat included me as well. That thought really makes me angry.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Rest assured, I’m not the type of person that would suffer a loss without fighting back.”

When Jason heard Zhao Hai, his eyes couldn’t help but light up as he said, “Really? Do you really intend to deal with them? What are you planning to do?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and replied, “I didn’t expect that you would have such enmity with them. I don’t have a solid plan right now, but rest assured, I certainly won’t make them live their lives peacefully. But we must wait for a good time to start.”

Jason nodded and said, “Alright, but you must consider me. If you need my help, don’t hesitate to tell me. Otherwise, don’t blame me for being impolite.”

Zhao Hai asked Jason, “Why are you so anxious? Let’s be clear, if you really want in on my plans, do you really think that your family will agree? This action would also be seen as joining the battle for succession. Even if you represent yourself, you still have your family behind you. If you really want to join, you need to ask your father and grandfather first.”

Jason sighed and lifted his glass of wine and took a sip. He turned to Zhao Hai, “You really are in a better position. Whatever you do, nobody would restrict you. You have more freedom.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “While I may be free, I rarely have time to relax. I have to consider my family in all of my actions, I always worry about them wherever I go. Since nobody still has any idea of our location, I can freely act against anyone I want. But if they do find out, I will have more troubles coming my way. Moreover, I also don’t want to implicate the Calci Family in my matters. Megan is already engaged to me, I don’t want to be unfair to her. If I manage to bring trouble to the Calci Family, I will certainly feel sorry.”

Jason looked at Zhao Hai, then he suddenly smiled and said, “Now that you say it, you really are quite good. To be honest, I saw how Princess Lizzy looked at you last night. What would you do if she wants to marry you?”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “Don’t talk nonsense, why would she want to marry me? As you can see, I’m only a count, and not even a count of the Rosen Empire. You think Princess Lizzy would marry me? Don’t joke around.”

Jason smiled and said, “That may be possible. Megan’s status isn’t that low compared to Princess Lizzy, yet she became engaged to you. You must be more confident in yourself.”

Zhao Hai ridiculed him, “Get lost. Why would I not have confidence in myself. If Princess Lizzy indeed wanted to marry me, then would His Highness the Emperor agree? A princess getting snatched by a man with several women, in the eyes of the Emperor, this would certainly look bad.”

Jason nodded, “Indeed, even if Princess Lizzy is willing, his majesty surely wouldn’t agree. Princess Lizzy is his most loved daughter, and her well being is related to the Royal Clan’s face.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It’s fine if I don’t wed Princess Lizzy. After all, I already have three fiance’s. Meg grew up with me, her grandfather is Spirit Wind Green, someone who I treat like a real grandfather. Moreover, they are also very loyal to my Buda Clan. Without Grandpa Green, I wouldn’t be able to survive to this day. Laura, for the sake of me, sacrificed her years of work and even fell out with her Markey Family. Megan doesn’t care about my low family background, she was determined to marry me. Having three such fiance’s already made me satisfied.”

Jason looked at Zhao Hai and sighed, “Your luck is indeed really good. You also have good luck with females, being able to find such good women. I really envy you to death.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and didn’t talk back. He agreed with Jason, for him to obtain the approval of Laura and the others was certainly his good luck.

Because they needed to drink with Jason’s grandfather at noon, the two didn’t drink too much liquor. They only drank a small cup as well as eating a few snacks before taking a rest.

At lunchtime, the place was very lively. Jason’s grandfather not only invited the well-known members of the family, they also introduced each one of them to Zhao Hai. This gave Zhao Hai a big sense of respect for the family.

However, in such an occasion, it was impossible for one to both drink and eat too much. Almost everyone was there to chat, and pretend to be polite. Such occasions weren’t to the liking of Jason and Zhao Hai. But since this event was made for Zhao Hai, the two of them couldn’t just escape midway. They could only stay here, this made Zhao Hai quite impatient.

After having lunch, Zhao Hai chatted with Jason for quite a while before saying his goodbyes. Jason escorted Zhao Hai outside the fort and waved him farewell.

When Zhao Hai returned to Dark Soldier Fort, the skies were already turning dark. Upon returning to his courtyard, he immediately told Laura and the others about what happened back at Jason’s family. The group talked until the skies turned completely black.

There were a lot of cards that came, inviting Zhao Hai to various banquets. But since Zhao Hai found them quite bothersome, he didn’t participate in any of them.

The next day was the Day of Rare Purity, although people still send some gifts, most of them were fully preparing for tomorrow’s God’s Grace Day. At this time, nobody attended any banquets. Also, it was the Imperial Banquet tomorrow, no noble family held any banquets in these two days.

On this day, the entire Dark Soldier Fort was also very busy. Everyone was preparing for tomorrow. For a Great Clan like the Calci Family, they were very particular in performing the festival and following tradition. Everybody received an itinerary about what to do tomorrow. This was to prevent anyone from being out of the loop.

When Zhao Hai’s group received their itinerary, they couldn’t help but gasp. The day was indeed quite strict. Upon waking up, they would have a particular time to eat their meals before they need to wear appropriate clothing and then proceed to worshipping the ancestors. What to wear as well as to which ancestor they would go first was clearly written. It was as though the family was afraid that anyone might make a mistake.

For a Clan like the Calci Family, worshipping the ancestors was a grand matter. If a mistake was made in worshipping the ancestors, that person would receive huge fines and have their status in the family affected.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t a person of the Calci Family, he was still placed under Smith’s umbrella. If he makes a mistake, Smith would be penalized. Therefore, Zhao Hai had no choice but to prepare well for tomorrow.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also made Cai’er monitor the entirety of Dark Soldier Fort. If somebody was thinking of causing trouble with him, he made sure that Cai’er would report to him. He was really afraid that Juwan and Third Grandfather might bring him trouble when he goes to worship the ancestor.

Fortunately, Juwan and Third Grandfather also placed great importance to the ceremony. They don’t wish to smear the faces of the ancestors, it would not only be unfair to the ancestors, it might also bring the family bad luck for the following year. Because of this, they didn’t make any plans against Zhao Hai. This made Zhao Hai very relieved.

Chapter 468: Goodbye To Yesterday, Hello To A Better Tomorrow

Zhao Hai’s mind was now somewhat confused about the people of the Ark Continent. These people act like westerners on Earth, however, they perform oriental traditions such as worshipping the ancestors.

Worshipping the ancestors is an integral part in Eastern Culture. This was because in the East, they believed that after death, their family member’s souls will remain and guard the family. Because of this, those who are still alive give their respects to the ancestors, asking them to continue protecting the family.

To be honest, people already knew that it was impossible for their ancestors to protect their families. If one turned into a soul, they would have no means of protecting their loved ones. These thoughts aren’t only present within Great Clans, even the Imperial Clans think of this. Therefore, recently this thought of protection slowly faded away.

However, worshipping the ancestors still survived to this day. This was done in order to commemorate one’s ancestor, telling them of all the achievements that you’ve done. It wasn’t done in order to request for protection anymore.

For a Great Clan like the Calci Family, this wasn’t the only thing that made this event significant. Worshipping the ancestors also brings a type of cohesion among the family. This will help the Family prosper in the future.

The entire ceremony was prepared in a strict manner, there shouldn’t be any mistakes, everything needs to be perfect. Zhao Hai went along with Smith during the event.

The way the Ark Continent worshipped their ancestors was a little different from China. Chinese tradition generally forbade women from attending the ceremony. But in Ark Continent, there wasn’t such a rule. The event took up half a day before everything was over.

In the evening, Randolph led Peter and the others to attend the Imperial Banquet. To be honest, Nobles during God’s Grace Day were usually bored. Aside from attending their family banquets, they would also drink and chat with their family members. The atmosphere was not very good as well, which made Zhao Hai dislike the scene.

After attending the family banquet that the Calci Family has held, Zhao Hai immediately led Laura and the others back to Iron Mountain Fort. Compared to the Calci Family, Iron Mountain Fort was Zhao Hai’s genuine family. Therefore, he must attend the fort’s evening banquet.

At this time, the banquet in Iron Mountain Fort still hasn’t started. Green and the others were waiting for Zhao Hai. They were currently inside the fort’s main square. The square was filled with bonfires. Suspended on the side of them were Argalis and Raging Bulls. There were also Blue-Eyed Rabbits everywhere.

Additionally, there was also an entire Blade-Scale Whale on the side along with the other seafood. Once could say that Green really took out all the good things that they had.

Beside each bonfire were big wooden barrels. One could smell the sweet smell of Milk Wine from the barrels. No matter Beastman nor Human, all of them wore new clothes while gathering around the bonfires. Nobody touched the food as well as the liquor, all of them were waiting for Zhao Hai.

When Zhao Hai came out of the Space and saw this situation, his heart couldn’t help but turn warm. Laura and the others were also touched. When Zhao Hai scanned the square, he saw some people missing. So he immediately teleported to Jade Water City and retrieved Mu’en’s family and brought them back to the fort. At this point, as long as the place was mapped on the monitor, Zhao Hai can immediately go there, making teleportation much much easier.

When Zhao Hai got Mu’en, Green immediately had the people place the animals on the bonfire. He also had the Blade Scale Whale processed.

Dealing with the Blade Scale Whale took a lot of thought. The scales of the whale were taken off, these scales can be used later to store water. They were sharp and sturdy as well.

Green already made a few cuts on the body of the fish, he placed seasonings all over them after having its internal organs removed. Burning stones were placed inside the body of the whale. Because of the size of the fish, one could enter its mouth in order to take the stones and reheat them on the bonfires outside. In this way, the whale would be evenly cooked. Before long, the whale was roasted and was ready for eating.

As for the argali and raging bulls, they didn’t need to think much about them. These animals were a staple food for the Beastmen. Because of this, cooking them became quite easy.

Shortly after, the entire square of Iron Mountain Fort was filled with the aromatic fragrance of roasted meat. When the meats were ready to be eaten, Merine also had the food they cooked themselves taken out and shared them with everyone.

This was also the proposition of Zhao Hai. He knew that the situation of the Buda Clan was different from the others. Other families have servants to handle these types of things while the Buda Clan didn’t. To not turn this evening into a barbecue party, Zhao Hai requested Merine to have people help make 1 or 2 additional dishes that they were adept in cooking. When everyone eats on the eve of God’s Grace Day, these dishes would be taken out and shared to everyone. They didn’t need to worry about the ingredients of their dishes, Zhao Hai already had everything covered.

Merine didn’t want to bother the others about this matter. But she didn’t expect them to be excited when she told them about it. Merine didn’t even need to cook anything. The people returned to their homes and prepared their best recipes to have everyone taste it.

One couldn’t blame these people for their excitement. The initial 100 slaves that they bought in the beginning were no longer slaves. They already settled down and had their own homes in their own land. Everyone’s days were flourishing, and it was also the first time that they would experience God’s Grace Day since they weren’t able to do so before. So it was natural that they would be overly excited. They wanted to return the favor to the Buda Clan in some manner, and this time’s task of cooking food was a great opportunity, so they immediately agreed.

Beastmen were experts on all kinds of meat dishes while the human slaves were experts in vegetables. This made Zhao Hai speechless for a while. However, this was good, it was God’s Grace Day, and everyone was going to be happy in eating their food.

Seeing that everything was already prepared, Green slowly walked to the middle of the square and watched the crowd before talking loudly, “Everyone, please calm down!”

Green’s words were very effective. The square immediately quieted down, even the children were looking at Green, they didn’t make any noise nor did they move around randomly.

Iron Mountain Fort has always been under Green’s management. For those slaves, Green was like their leader, it was natural that they would listen to his order. To them, Zhao Hai was a god-like existence, he awed them everytime they see him.

Seeing that the square has become peaceful, Green said, “Everybody, one year ago, we arrived here at Iron Mountain Fort. At that time, the fort was an old worn out castle. It didn’t have anything, we were desperately clinging for our lives. One passed by in a blink of an eye, in the past year, we have created a lot using our two hands. We have managed to change our lives, we turned heaven and earth upside down. But everything was given to us by one person, do you know who that person is?”

In almost the same time, everybody said, “The Young Master!” Zhao Hai had his people call him Young Master. Because of this, the people yelled out ‘Young Master’. They didn’t call Zhao Hai by his name nor did they call him Patriarch. For them, ‘Young Master’ was Zhao Hai’s special title.

Green nodded and said, “Right, today is God’s Grace Day. I know that this is the first time for many of you. I ask the Young Master to give us a few words.” Then he slowly drew back.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that Green would make him say a few words. But this place is his domain, he didn’t back down. He smiled and stood up before walking to the middle of the square. Before he started to speak, the crowd gave him an applause.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone and said, “One year ago, you all have different identities, now you are all the people of the Buda Clan. I promised a year ago that you will be able to eat meat every single day, and I managed to fulfill it. However, I didn’t do this alone, you’ve all used your own hands and worked hard every single day in order to achieve this. In behalf of the Buda Clan, this Zhao Hai will express his gratitude.” Then he bowed towards the crowd.

This move from Zhao Hai scared them. No matter if they were a Beastman or a Human, all of them started to kneel. Several elderly beastmen even said loudly, “Young Master, you should get up quickly. You don’t owe us anything. Without you, we would never reach this day. You are our great benefactor, as well as the benefactor for our succeeding generations.”

At this time, Zhao Hai returned to standing straight. When he looked at the people kneeling down, he smiled and said, “Everyone get up! This is a special day, you don’t need to kneel. Quickly get up.”

Then the crowd stood up. Zhao Hai looked into their eyes and said, “This year, the Buda Clan has been reborn, I’ve been reborn as well, and so are all of you. This day marks a significant moment in our lives. We shall celebrate a new holiday today, which would be the Festival Of Rebirth. Everyone, raise you glasses of wine. Let’s drink together, let’s say goodbye to yesterday and say hello to a good tomorrow! Drink!”

The crowd followed his instructions and raised their glasses before drinking together with Zhao Hai. The wine tasted especially good. Just like Zhao Hai said, this glass of wine was a farewell to the yesterday as well as a welcome to the new tomorrow. When the liquid warmed their stomachs, the people’s eyes couldn’t help but moisten.

They were different from Laura and the others. When Laura and the others were growing up, they didn’t need to worry about food and clothing. As for meat, they didn’t even need to think about them. Everyday, they get to eat good food, for them, meat was no big deal.

However, to these slaves, having clothes to put on as well as having meat to eat was akin to living in Heaven. They didn’t expect that they would actually experience such a thing.

Some of these slaves were sons and daughters of slaves. They knew that their fathers and mothers, even their grandfathers and grandmothers might not have eaten meat their entire lives, maybe they were even unable to drink liquor. This was a dream for all of them, they didn’t think that this dream would actually come true.

Chapter 469: Alibi

Laura and the others looked at Zhao Hai with infatuated gazes. They felt that this Zhao Hai who was standing in the middle of the square was most attractive. Zhao Hai was so dazzling at this moment. Even if he didn’t have a very outstanding appearance, his charm was in a different aspect.

Laura and the others didn’t settle on Zhao Hai because of his appearance, there were people who courted them that were much more handsome than Zhao Hai. What they saw Zhao Hai was his unique temperament, this attitude somewhat attracted them.

Zhao Hai temperament was different from those who live in the Ark Continent. There was an inseparable relationship between a person’s temperament and the place where they were living in. People who lived in the slums for many generations simply cannot have the same temperament as the nobles. Zhao Hai’s difference certainly stemmed from the fact that he was from Earth. Earth didn’t have Magic and Battle Qi, instead, scientific and technological developments was present there. His concept of society was also from Earth. This made Zhao Hai have a different mindset than those from the continent. This made him unique, which gave him a certain kind of charm.

In Ark Continent, one who had the closest type to Zhao Hai’s temperament was Jason. But this temperament was only acquired because of Jason’s rebellious tendencies, not really a mindset that a person from Earth would have. Even still, with his temperament, Jason was seen as an oddity in Rosen Empire, not to mention Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai’s temperament was different from that of Jason. Zhao Hai’s temper was relatively mild, he also worked hard in order to adapt to everything in Ark Continent. He also had Adam’s memory within him, equivalent to him being half a native of the continent. These two different personalities fused together to become what he is today.

The entire population of Iron Mountain Fort has gotten drunk this evening. Both men and women were drunk. The expressions of these people were varied, some were laughing while standing, some were sitting and smiling, while others were crying.

Zhao Hai, along with Green and the others were sitting on one side. They had not become drunk. They looked at the drunken beastmen and slaves and couldn’t help but feel bad. There was no need to say that compared to their present life, their previous life was a living hell. It was no different to these beastmen, they were only a small tribe, and were easily exploited. During winter, they would suffer extremely, some wouldn’t even survive till the next season.

Zhao Hai provided them with a different life, enabling them to laugh like they did today, weep bitterly like they did today, eat meat like they did today, and drink wine like they did today. In their minds, all of these were given by Zhao Hai. All of them were very grateful to Zhao Hai.

In Zhao Hai’s heart, he felt that he held a huge responsibility over them. All of them were people of the Buda Clan. He had the obligation to make these people’s lives better. This was a mission he set for himself.

Laura and the others were very emotional as well when they saw these slaves crying and laughing. They felt choked up in their hearts. Megan was very tearful, she looked at the people present with a gaze of warmth.

After all of the people were asleep, Zhao Hai let out some undead to bring them to their residences. At the same time, he also had the undead clean the square.

Seeing the square being cleaned, it was only then that Zhao Hai realized how these guys can really eat. Not only was the huge blade-scaled whale eaten, all of the dishes were also cleaned up. Even the argali and bulls weren’t saved. This made Zhao Hai very surprised, these guys can really eat.

After making the undead continue on with their cleaning, Zhao Hai returned to the fort’s living room and sat down. After the group settled in, Zhao Hai said two matters to Green; One was about Terry’s enmity with him while the other one was his intention to retaliate against Terry’s family.

After listening to Zhao Hai’s words, Green didn’t respond immediately, after a while, he nodded and said, “Young Master, how are you planning to deal with the Robert Family? Do you want to eliminate them?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, no. If I were to directly exterminate them, I would certainly alert the entirety of the Rosen Empire. Such development would be detrimental to our future actions. I simply cannot do that. Over the years, the Robert Family has amassed a few enemies. All we need is to cripple them, their enemies will finish the job. Even if they were to recover, they won’t be going to live well.”

Kun nodded and said, “This method is good. Cripple them and have their enemies see their situation. In the face of the Robert Family’s resources, those people would surely burn with greed. We don’t need to do anything at all, someone else would clean the family up for us. But Little Hai, you need to be swift. If you are dealing with a Great Clan like the Robert Family, even a crippled one can still bring you trouble.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I know that. This is why I didn’t make a move immediately. At this time, I had a hawk map out the entire Rosen Empire. As long as I have the entire empire mapped, I can then begin my move. In one evening, I plan to destroy every shop that the Robert family has, save for the one inside Carson City.”

The Space’s ability has since been upgraded. So Kun and the others’ trust in Zhao Hai was well founded. What Zhao Hai said didn’t surprise them, they knew that this matter can easily be accomplished.

After quite some time, Green nodded and said, “It’s feasible. It’s the God’s Grace Day season, nobody would suspect that anyone would make such a bold move this time. We will certainly be able to do it.”

Kun also nodded and said, “But it’s best if we do our moves secretly, we shouldn’t let anybody know that we did it. If they knew, we would be similarly marked. We must let them know that we have an enmity with the Robert Family while making them feel that we aren’t overwhelmingly strong. Right, Little Hai, during the day of the operation you should have other people along with you. Spend time with them, make them think that you had no hand in this.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew that the Buda Clan’s identity was quite rocky at this moment. If they were to make other people vigilant, they wouldn’t have much freedom in the future.

Kun’s proposition was quite good. Killing the people of the Robert Family and destroying their shops without letting anybody know who did it. Even if they suspect Zhao Hai, he would have an alibi by that time. People would feel fear and suspicion, but they wouldn’t associate the Buda Clan as being a huge threat. They would only dread the Clan a little bit, which was what the clan needed right now.

Green looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, after God’s Grace day, I’m afraid that you would have to head to the Prairie. Your matters in the Prairie has not yet been completely taken care of. Although the Herculean Bulls have defeated the Fighting Bulls, their status inside the Cow-headed race is still threatened. In order for us to have a good relationship with the Prairie in the future, you need to help secure the Herculean Bull’s position.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, I’ve also thought about trading with the sea dwellers this time. But I think I need to set a specific time for our transactions in the future, it may be once a month or several times in a year. After all, we can’t always go and do business with the merfolk. If we do so, sooner or later people would pay attention.”

Green nodded and said,” Young Master, how about taking a look at the Elven and Dwarven races? When do you plan to look for them? They also have a lot of special animals and plants. Their collections should be good for upgrading the Space.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then sighed, “I’m afraid I would have to move that to a later time, I have a lot of matters to take care of in the following days. We must first take a firm root in the continent, making its residents accept our Buda Clan. Only then can we think about extra matters.”

Green nodded, “Alright, let’s wait. The Space’s current strength is very good anyway. We don’t need to worry upgrading it at this time.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I really don’t want to wait because when the Space reached level 50, it might be able to plant high level plants, making your progress to 9th rank much easier. But now it looks like we don’t have any other choice but to wait.”

Green laughed and said, “No need to worry about that. We old people wouldn’t die tomorrow, there’s no need to be anxious. Take your time, I’m already satisfied with our clan’s current state. Young Master doesn’t need to take this matter to heart.”

Zhao Hai nodded, it seems like it can only be like this. He had already looked up the materials that the Processing Machine would need in making a potion for 9th rank promotion. Not only did the ingredients contain plants, there were also some animal blood, bones and all other things. Naturally, these beasts’ levels were also quite high.

Also, from the Space’s current level, Zhao Hai cannot make that potion right now. Zhao Hai also looked into the products in the Space’s store. He could see how high the levels of the plants and beasts could get. The highest level was surprisingly level 100, both for beasts and plants. This made Zhao Hai think of working hard to upgrade the Space.

After the group chatted for a while, Zhao Hai turned to leave. He was now living in Dark Soldier Fort after all. Even if they don’t live in the courtyard there, they still need to stay in the Space. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be able to respond should something happen inside the fort.

Laura and the others also returned to their rooms. They had been very tired the entire day. Just from the ancestor worshipping ceremony, the girls were already quite exhausted. Although Laura and Meg cannot attend the ceremony, they also need to wait at the side until the ceremony ends, otherwise they would be seen as disrespectful.

And then they also went to the celebration in Iron Mountain fort. Even if they were happy, they were also quite tired out from all the celebrations inside. At the end of the day, they could even swear that their bones ached as well.

Chapter 470: Three-Dimensional Map

Early next morning, Zhao Hai and the others went out of the Space. After a good evening’s rest, all of their exhaustion has vanished. All of them were now very full of energy.

Upon coming out of the Space, Zhao Hai breathed the chilly air outside. Suddenly, he had the urge to smile, this was because he felt that Ark Continent’s God’s Grace Day is pretty much like the Chinese New Year. It’s a celebration that celebrates the past year as well as the fortunes of the upcoming year.

He had experienced a lot of things in this one year. But to be honest, when Zhao Hai thought about all he has done in this past year, all of it seemed to be like a dream. He still couldn’t fathom how he turned from an unemployed nerd to a noble youth of a falling noble clan. How did he turn from being unable to kill a chicken to someone who can kill a thousand people without even batting an eye? How did he turn from someone who blushes just from being looked at by a woman to a man with three fiance’s. All of these felt pretty much like a dream, but this dream was indeed true.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai who was just standing there. She walked over and gently told him, “What are you thinking about? It’s very cold outside, you should go indoors.”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura’s charming face. This kind of face would never interact with him back on earth. They were like heaven and earth. But in Ark Continent, he actually had a girl as a fiance’.

Seeing Zhao Hai staring at her, Laura’s face couldn’t help but turn red, her heartbeat going faster. But she still looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “What are you looking at?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I see a beautiful woman. For a beautiful woman to be with someone like me surely gives me a lot pressure.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and then turned to look behind her. There, she saw Nier chuckling while covering her mouth. Laura’s face couldn’t help but get redder, but her heart was actually touched. However, she still looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Talk fewer nonsense, people might treat you as a joke. Come inside quickly.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and then entered the room. They got up earlier today, the Calci Family slept quite late last night, therefore, Smith might possibly wake up late. Because of this, he had no way of inviting Zhao Hai to breakfast.

Just as Zhao Hai entered the room, Meg came in carrying milk. Drinking milk upon waking up each morning had become Zhao Hai and the others’ routine. However, Zhao Hai didn’t really like drinking milk, what he liked was soybean milk. But making soybean milk is very tedious, and there wasn’t any machine present to process soybeans. Grinding them manually would take a lot of time so Zhao Hai didn’t bother.

Additionally, this milk was made by the cows that they raised, so there aren’t any synthetic components within in them. Therefore, Zhao Hai can drink them without any worries no matter how much milk he drank.[1]

Zhao Hai was now used to drinking milk along with everyone. Not only his group, every person in Iron Mountain Fort drank milk everyday. Zhao Hai hoped that his people would develop strong bodies.

After drinking the milk, Zhao Hai looked at the weather and then turned his head to Megan and smiled, “It seems like uncle wouldn’t be able to get up early today. Right, these days I’ll have to ask your family to mark the businesses of the Robert family on the map. After a few more days, we shall act against them.”

Megan nodded and said, “Alright, but it might take quite some time. A millennium-old family like the Robert Family has hidden businesses. Businesses who didn’t bear the banner of the Robert Family. We must include these in order to deal an actual blow to the Robert Family. Otherwise, we wouldn’t be hurting their core.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, we must find them as well. We shall deal with them from the bottom then we go to the top. We cannot just face them head on, or else they would retaliate.”

Megan nodded, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, I’m afraid that there will be more banquets happening in the capital. Will you participate in any of them?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I’ll leave this matter to you, you know much more about the nobles in Carson City. You go receive the invitations and tell me which one is good to join, I’ll be going to those ones.”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and then she faintly smiled, “Right, when will you bring me to the Prairie? I would also like to see Brother Wales.”

Zhao Hai looked at the skies and said, “Soon, the Prairie is much colder than here. You’ve been used to staying here so you might get sick if we go there this time. Right, you must practice well so that you’ll reach 8th rank. When we go to the Prairie, I will have Brother Wales deliver those 100 thousand slaves, I’ll have them go to Iron Mountain Fort.”

Megan also knew about this, but she wasn’t expecting the Beastmen to give 100 thousand slaves, which was something impossible for a Human. This made Megan want to go to the Prairie even more.

When she heard Zhao Hai, Megan nodded and said, “Alright, rest assured, I will certainly practice hard and reach 8th rank soon. When that time comes, you can bring me to the Prairie.”

Seeing Megan, Laura cannot help but smile and said, “Why do you want to go to the Prairie that much? There’s nothing to see there, it’s much better to play in the Space than the Prairie. It isn’t as beautiful as one can imagine, winds are ever present there, the sunburns doesn’t help either.”

Megan smiled and said, “Even so, I still want to see it. I haven’t gone to the Prairie yet.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, let’s wait until you finish cultivating then I will certainly lead you to the Prairie.” At this time, a servant came, asking Zhao Hai to eat.

…

In the next days, Zhao Hai lightly attended the banquets. Those banquets that Zhao Hai visited were all taken care of by the Calci Family. Only in the Crook Family banquet did Zhao Hai go personally.

There was no other way to do this. Zhao Hai’s fame wasn’t the same as the Calci Family. When they send invitations, they would send the cards to the Calci Family. But for these banquets, it was quite rare for two people to attend. Because of this, everytime Zhao Hai brings Megan along, people would feel envious in their hearts.

Zhao Hai didn’t only attend the banquets outside, he also attended the one that the Calci Family hosted. Great Nobles hosting banquets this time of the year was quite a common practice. It was quite normal to have multiple banquets in one evening. Families could also choose to attend all of them, separating their members in order to attend the banquets.

Aside from attending banquets, Zhao Hai was also waiting. Megan and Smith had been working hard in marking the Robert Family stores for Zhao Hai. At the same time, Zhao Hai also marked everything in the Space monitor’s map.

Also, the Blood Hawk has also finished mapping the entirety of the Rosen Empire after five days of flying around. It was because of this that Zhao Hai was able to mark the Robert Family businesses. Zhao Hai took his time, he wanted to make the Robert Family suffer as much as possible.

After completing everything, Zhao Hai started to prepare, he had Cai’er look into these shops and investigate who were inside of them, and if ever they had some experts inside.

Cai’er’s work was very quick. In two days, all of the manpower of the Robert Family had been accounted for and were reported to Zhao Hai.

Looking at the numbers, Zhao Hai finally discovered how formidable millenium-old families were. Apart from the Robert Family’s shop in Carson City, their shops in both large and small cities reached more than 1300 shops altogether. Of these shops, 630 publicly waved the banner of the Robert Family while 700 weren’t. Even if it looked like small Nobles were managing these shops, they were actually owned by the Robert Family.

Most importantly, on 1000 of these shops, there was at least one 8th rank expert. Some major shops not only have 8th rank experts, there were also 7th and 6th rank experts present. All in all, there were more than 2,000 8th rank experts in all 1300 stores. This number really surprised Zhao Hai.

In the past, the Buda Clan only had Green and Merine as their 8th rank expert. Even so, the Clan was able to be popular in Aksu Empire. But the Robert Family actually had 2000 8th ranks on their various shops outside of the capital. This difference in strength was too great.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t know, but the reason why the Buda Clan was able to be popular was because they had the good graces of the Old Monarch. It wasn’t the Buda Clan that the people showed respect to, but the Old King.

As long as nobles settle inside major Empires, they surely need to have a 9th rank expert in them. If they don’t, then they won’t be able to survive. If you don’t have any 9th rank experts, then you would need to attach yourself to those big Nobles. Your clan would then be regarded as a vassal to that Noble family.

After Zhao Hai took these into account, he was quite surprised to discover that there were a lot more human 9th ranks than those present inside the Carrion Swamp. Even if 9th rank Magic Beasts are much stronger than Human experts, they still cannot defeat the collective might of the Human Race. It was only because of Cai’er’s presence in the swamp as well as the poison mist inside did the Magic Beasts have the chance to hold the Humans off all this time. Because of this, the Human 9th ranks made an agreement with the 9th rank Magic Beasts.

When he found out the strength of these old clans, Zhao Hai’s buried his pride deep inside. Now, he was thinking about the strength of the Radiant Church.

The Calci Family and the Robert Family were both millenium-old clans. As such, the Calci Family’s strength shouldn’t be that much weaker than the Robert Family. But even if so, they were still suppressed by the Radiant Church. This fact surely cemented the idea that the Radiant Church was much more formidable than these old noble families. This made Zhao Hai even more cautious in his actions.

But Zhao Hai didn’t think too much into it, the Magic Beasts of the Carrion Swamp aren’t very easy to deal with either. In addition to their environment, their physiques were much better than the Human experts. In addition, the human 9th ranks were all separated into many families. It would be very difficult to unite all of them. If they can really unite, they would still have to conquer the Carrion Swamp.

Just when Zhao Hai was waiting for the opportune moment to attack, the chance suddenly came when Zhao Hai was sitting on the living room, looking at the monitor. The projection on the monitor wasn’t an ordinary map. This map was three-dimensional, just like those maps that sci-fi movies back on Earth have. With a wave of his hand, Zhao Hai can enlarge or shrink the projection. This was something that Cai’er had told him, it was a new ability of the Space.

Showed on the map was a holographic projection of the Rosen Empire. There were a lot of dots showed on several parts of the map. These dots were all Zhao Hai’s targets, the shops of the Robert Family as well as the locations of those small nobles. These nobles were the vassals of the Robert Family. At this point, Zhao Hai was still undecided about whether he would also erase these small noble families.

Laura and the others were also with Zhao Hai, looking at the three-dimensional projection. Even if they had already seen this in the past few days, they were still very amazed everytime they see it. There are really a lot of surprises in the Space, such as this map.

The way the Ark Continent does it sbattles is very primitive. They hardly had complex things such as the Art of War. They generally have three avenues in battles, scouting and assassinations by the assassins, long distance warfare using magical cannons and ballistas, and lastly, large scale infantry battles. Everything depended on raw strength.

Because of this, the armies don’t have the need to have sand tables. In a war, a flat map was enough to handle command. Sand table discussions and battle plans were rarely done. Moreover, there was a miniscule amount of staff officers in each army, most of them were all military officers.

With rarity of sand tables, it was no surprise that Laura and the others would be surprised about the three dimensional map. This was because they simply didn’t have any idea about this three-dimensional map.

At this time, Megan came in from the outside. Megan was going to her father every day now. First reason was because of the matter about the shops, and the second reason was to see the invitations that were sent over and see if there are any banquets that Zhao Hai can attend.

Looking at Megan’s appearance, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “What happened? You look glad, is there something to be happy about?”

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, guess which family invitation just came in.”

Zhao Hai stared, seeing Megan’s faint smile, he suddenly thought of a person. He looked into Megan’s eyes and said, “Is it the Robert Family?”

Megan scowled at Zhao Hai, “Big Brother Hai, can guess wrong just one time? It’s very annoying, you don’t let me have a sense of achievement.”

Zhao Hai stared, “Is it really the Robert Family?” Then he opened the card and read the contents. He stared, it was because the name that was written inside was actually his, Zhao Hai Buda!

* * *

Maybe this has something to do with Chinese not trusting the milk that their country produces.

Chapter 471: Singing

Zhao Hai had seen a lot of written invitations, but he had only seen two of them who specifically mentioned his name. One of them was from Charlie, before God’s Grace Day, and another was from Jason, sent the day before yesterday, this was the third.

The first two invitations that were given to Zhao Hai were expected, but this one came out of the blue.

He placed the invitation down and looked at Megan, “Megan, what do you think Terry wants to do? Or the Robert Family in that matter?”

Megan snorted and said, “I don’t know about the Robert Family, but what Terry wants to do was actually step on your reputation, shaming you. Makes you look ugly to me. Big Brother Hai, you need to be careful tomorrow. Otherwise, their plans would affect you.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll be fine. I’m also trying to deal with him. If I were to attend the Robert Family’s banquet tomorrow and all of their businesses get attacked at the same time, how could they possibly place the blame on me?”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Megan and the others smiled. They really wanted to know what response Terry and his family show when they receive the news that all of their businesses outside of the capital have been erased.

Laura smiled and said, “Right, I agree with Brother Hai. If we execute our plans, there shouldn’t be any loose ends.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Now I really want to see how they plan to deal with me. It looks like they don’t intend to use force, my reputation as an 8th rank mage is already widespread. Their previous plan was good, I didn’t see that one coming. What methods can they use this time? Does it have to do with literature?”

Laura and Megan nodded, the two of them grew up in noble households since childhood, so they were quite familiar with how nobles act. Therefore, they thought Zhao Hai’s words were quite acceptable.

Laura nodded and said, “If you can’t deal with someone using force, then one can embarrass them in front of a crowd. One could make their enemy do a dance, recite a poem, or play some musical instruments. Brother Hai cannot dance, and I haven’t seen you play an instrument, poem? I think that may be a bit difficult. Brother Hai’s weakness really has to do with performances.”

Laura didn’t deliberately ignore this shortcoming of Zhao Hai. In Laura’s view, there are no such thing as a perfect person. Zhao Hai cannot write poetry, cannot dance, cannot play instruments, but all of these doesn’t overshadow Zhao Hai’s brilliance. For a recently fallen family like the Buda Clan, poems, dances, and musical instruments aren’t the talents that they currently need for a leader. They need someone who is tolerant, low-key, and decisive in his actions. And Zhao Hai was the latter.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “They really know my weak spot. Alright, I’ll sing. Is singing fine?”

When they heard Zhao Hai, Laura and Megan’s eyes turned bright. They looked at each other before Megan said, “Big Brother Hai, will you really sing? Are you good?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly, he knew that if he was allowed to sing, he could survive this situation. But he didn’t lie, although he cannot play any musical instruments, he was quite confident in his singing. This was because back on Earth, he only had three hobbies; singing, drinking, and reading books.

What Zhao Hai liked were pop songs, so it was natural that he would sing along. For drinking, he generally wouldn’t drink much, but he enjoyed doing it along with his friends. As for writing, there was no need to mention it, it was Zhao Hai’s most loved hobby.

To be honest, Zhao Hai was good at signing. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have proposed doing it. However, since he came to Ark Continent, he didn’t have any mood to do so, he had too many matters to think about.

One could say that if he was forced to write a poem, he can plagiarize one or two. But Zhao Hai didn’t want that. But if he really was pushed to doing it, then he wouldn’t be polite.

Man can lose face, but not in two occasions. The first one is in front of a love rival, and the other, in front of an enemy. Because if you do so, you would be losing your dignity.

When Laura said that Nobles would generally make a poem, dance, or play a musical instrument, Zhao Hai frowned. This was because these are not things that he was skilled in. So he proposed that he would sing. He wanted to know whether singing was allowed because he would prefer doing so. Naturally, if he said that he can sing, Megan and the others would certainly ask him to do so. And as expected, they did.

Laura became interested in what Zhao Hai said, “Brother Hai, you can actually sing? How come I don’t know about it? Sing one song for us quickly.”

Zhao Hai looked at their face and smiled bitterly, “Alright, I’ll go sing one for you. Hmm, what to sing, Alright, I’ll go sing ‘Bed of Chrysanthemums’”

Your tears glisten with pain in their fragility

The pale crescent hooks the past

The endless night has crystallised into frost

Who is it in the loft, destitute with cold hopelessness?

* * *

The rain slowly patters on the vermilion window

My life is a tattered page battered by the winds

Far-off dreams fading into mist

Your image has been dissipated by the wind

* * *

Wilted chrysanthemums are spread across the floor; even your smile has turned faintly yellow

The falling flowers induce sadness, and my thoughts languish

In the passing of the north wind and the dusk, your shadow lingers on

And standing by the lake, I only have my own reflection for company

* * *

Responding to the dusk, the flowers shed their brilliant shine

They wilter on life’s path, meeting a tragic fate

Don’t cross the river in melancholy

You may spend a lifetime drifting, never reaching the shore

* * *

Whose empire is it now? The sound of horse hoofs thunders in the distance.

My resplendent armour decays with the hounds of time

Your soft sigh heralds the first ray of dawn

The conclusion to another restless night

* * *

Wilted chrysanthemums are spread across the floor; even your smile has turned faintly yellow

The falling flowers induce sadness, and my thoughts languish

In the passing of the north wind and the dusk, your shadow lingers on

And standing by the lake, I only have my own reflection for company…” [1][2]

This song wasn’t unfamiliar to average people. Jay Chou’s song has a very unique charm, and Zhao Hai really liked his works. What he liked in songs were the lyrics and the artistic style in how they were arranged.

This type of song was naturally not present in Ark Continent. What people generally listened to were songs that were like those sang in the opera. Pop songs were non-existed here.

Zhao Hai knew about this matter, but he cannot sing opera, only pop songs. He accepted Laura’s request because he wanted to see how they’ll receive this style of song. If the song was acceptable, then Zhao Hai can use this to deal with Terry’s plan. If they can’t accept it, Zhao Hai can only think of something else.

While Zhao Hai sang, Laura and Megan both wore very dumbfounded faces. From the moment he started to the end, the two’s expression didn’t change. This made Zhao Hai extremely worried.

After quite some time, the two somewhat recovered and stared at Zhao Hai strangely. Seeing how the two looked at him, Zhao Hai asked, “What? What’s wrong?”

Laura and Megan, now fully recovered, looked at each other before running outside. Zhao Hai didn’t know what was going on. He was very confident in Jay Chou’s song, this song had a lot of thought put into it, and Zhao Hai also sang it very well. Was it that bad? Why did they need to run away?

With a puzzled expression, Zhao Hai turned to Meg. Meg was strangely looking at Zhao Hai as well, then she said, “Young Master, how come I didn’t know that you could actually sing? When did you learn? Did you use this to attract other girls to your room?”

When Zhao Hai heard the first part of Meg’s response, he couldn’t help but have a cold sweat. He thought that Meg would get skeptical about his identity. But when he heard the second part, he became relieved, Meg wasn’t suspicious of him.

In fact, Zhao Hai was completely overly concerned. Not only Meg, even Green didn’t doubt Zhao Hai. This was because Zhao Hai replaced Adam’s soul, not his body. From the time when he drank the Water of Nothingness to when he woke up, he never left Green’s sight. In this case, how could they doubt his identity?

Zhao Hai relaxed, and at the same time, he turned to Meg and said, “Don’t talk nonsense. This is your young master’s talent, I made it myself. It’s good right? So tell me what those two were planning on doing.”

Meg smiled and said, “You’ll know in a moment.” Making Zhao Hai wait in anticipation.

Before long, Laura and Megan came back. Nier was also following behind them. Carried in their hands were musical instruments.

Zhao Hai stared, then immediately understood what they want to do. They actually wanted to play the ‘Bed of Chrysanthemums”, very interesting.

Zhao Hai looked at the four instruments, there was something that looked like a harp, one was a violin, one was a cello, and the last one was a horizontal flute.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, your song is very nice to hear. We haven’t had such a song in the Continent. We know how to play instruments, when you sing, we’ll  will be giving you a musical background.”

Such an opportunity was rare, so Zhao Hai didn’t decline. He nodded and said, “Alright, let’s practice the song. If Terry wanted me to perform, then you will accompany me.”

Laura smiled and said, “Alright, go sing it again.” Zhao Hai nodded and then sang ‘Bed of Chrysanthemums’ again from beginning to end.

Including this time, Laura and the others have already heard the song twice, but they still had difficulties in playing along. But this obstacle didn’t stump them, they have all grown up in noble families, they learned these instruments from childhood. For Noble families, it wasn’t surprising for their descendants to learn one of two instruments, even for Adam who didn’t learn anything.

* * *

Sauce – https://lyricstranslate.com/en/%E8%8F%8A%E8%8A%B1%E5%8F%B0-bed-chrysanthemums.html

Also, easiest chapter of my life xD

Chapter 472: Savage Wolf and a Malnourished Horse

Afraid that people may hear them in the courtyard, Zhao Hai immediately relocated their practice into the Space. Laura and the others were very excited, this was a new and odd style.

The day slowly passed as they practiced non-stop. However, their efforts weren’t wasted. Now, when Zhao Hai sang, Laura and the others can already keep up with their tunes.

When the skies slowly turned dark, the group started to groom themselves. In the banquets that Zhao Hai attended in the past few days, aside from Jason’s banquet, Zhao Hai didn’t bring Laura and the others, only Megan. He was afraid the Megan would get shamed if he were to bring his other fiances.

One must know that noble women were not so polite. Megan was always placed beside Lizzy, being one of the Twin Flowers of the Capital. Because of this, there were a lot of women who were very jealous of her. If Zhao Hai brought Laura and the others to the banquets, those women might act on Laura and the others in order to embarrass Megan. Zhao Hai didn’t want such a matter to happen, so when he went to such banquets, he didn’t bring Laura and the others.

Naturally, Zhao Hai not bringing them doesn’t mean that he left them behind in the Calci Family. Laura and the others were inside the Space whenever he went out, not accompanying Zhao Hai while at the same time not appearing in the banquet.

But in today’s banquet, all of them were going to appear together. Zhao Hai had no choice, it was clear that Terry wanted him to bring Laura and the others along so that Zhao Hai can lose face in front of them as well.

Zhao Hai still used his bull-pulled carriage. His carriage may look good elsewhere, but not here. This was the Rosen Empire’s Capital, in here, Zhao Hai’s carriage was quite common.

However, it doesn’t matter if his carriage looked good or bad, it was still Zhao Hai’s own carriage. He was already very used to sitting on this one, being uncomfortable on other carriages would be no good.

The carriage slowly headed to the Robert Family’s castle. The Robert Family’s castle was a short distance away from the Calci Family. If one were to walk, it would take four hours; two hours if you walk fast.

When Zhao Hai left, he let the carriage slowly head forward while he went to the Space to observe the situation outside. At the same time, he was also preparing their action tonight.

Zhao Hai cannot personally take charge of tonight’s operation, so he can only delegate the task over to Cai’er, making her take charge of Zhao Hai’s Advanced Level Undead. Since these undead were created by the Space, there was no problem in transferring their control over to someone else.

In fact, there was no need to take command on all these undead. Zhao Hai had already found all of the Robert Family’s shops. He can just transfer a group over to finish the job quickly before withdrawing. If a problem arises, Zhao Wen and Cai’er can just support them anytime. Zhao Hai’s plan was to finish everything in one hour, after that period, everyone must retreat. Moreover, they should make their actions as silent as possible, not making any large commotions.

As for those vassal nobles of the Robert Family, Zhao Hai decided to not include them in his plans. In the end, those nobles are nobles of the Rosen Empire. If he decides to touch them, he might incur the anger of the whole empire’s nobles. When that happens, their gains wouldn’t justify their losses. One must know that the collective strength of Rosen Empire’s nobles was very strong.

To further ensure the success of the operation, Zhao Hai went to Iron Mountain Fort to ask Green and Kun to supervise. With them and Cai’er er taking charge of the undead, there was no way for this plan to fail.

Zhao Hai had to ensure this plan’s success. He had to get rid of all the family’s shops without leaving anybody alive. This was to make sure that nobody finds out that the shops were attacked by the undead, leaving the Robert Family with no way to suspect Zhao Hai.

After discussing everything with Green and Kun, the two elders couldn’t help but stare strangely at Zhao Hai. They didn’t believe that Zhao Hai could really sing. Seeing the look on their faces, Zhao Hai knew that they were thinking about him wanting to sing. This made him smile bitterly, how can his singing become a wonder in this world? If all those who loved karaoke in Earth were to be transported to the continent, their numbers would be enough to establish an independent country.

Green looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, can you really sing? Is it a good idea for you to sing?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I can sing a little. I don’t know any other thing aside from singing. There was no way for me to practice an instrument in one or two days. If Terry really wanted to embarrass me tonight, then I have no choice but to sing.”

Green smiled and said, “I really didn’t expect that Young Master can actually sing. Haha, good. Right, I must talk with Merine later. When Young Master comes next time, we’ll have you study an instrument as well as work on your dancing.”

Zhao Hai felt quite down, he wasn’t really interested in those things. If they really wanted him to learn, then he didn’t know whether he can last very long.

Kun agreed as he nodded, “You should study, study. A noble that can’t dance is quite a loss of face. Hmm, I think it would be better if we have Laura and the others teach him.”

Upon hearing Kun’s suggestion, Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but turn bright. Although Zhao Hai was very polite and really loved Laura and the others, this didn’t mean that he didn’t have any thoughts about them. In the past, his health wasn’t very good, but now, he was already very healthy. He’s an 8th rank expert, he can kill an elephant in one, naturally, his basic instincts were much stronger as well.

But since he didn’t want to destroy Laura and the others’ impression of him, he didn’t make any excessive actions. Ark Continent wasn’t the same as Earth. On Earth, if you were with a girl and didn’t make any moves after several days of dating, people would judge you as incompetent. But Zhao Hai was in the Ark Continent now, if one was too anxious, then they wouldn’t have any good reputation among the people.

Because of this, Zhao Hai did his best to practice self-control. He tried his best to suppress these evil thoughts.

At this time, the bull-pulled carriage had already arrived at the base of the Robert Family’s hill. The emblem of the Robert Family was a wolf with only one eye. Their family’s badge was named the Savage Wolf emblem.

Everybody knows that a savage beast is the most difficult one to fight. This was because a savage  beast was more ruthless. The Robert Family choosing this emblem has this reason behind it.[1]

Savage  Wolf, Savage  Wolf Fort, Savage  Wolf emblem, all of these symbolize the Robert Family. Moreover, Zhao Hai had also heard that the Robert Family ancestors always advocated their descendants act as thought they were savage  wolves at all times.

Savage  wolves are ferocious, but they were sly as well. Someone who had that temperament was very scary. And each and every one of the Robert Family members practice this kind of mindset. Even if generations of the Robert Family had good relations with the Calci family, the two families were always on guard against each other.

And you have to realize that with the Robert Family always acting like sly wolves, they were still able to arrive at their current height today.

When Zhao Hai’s carriage arrived at the foot of the hill, he was greeted by the servant in charge of the roadblock and upon inspecting the invitation, allowed Zhao Hai passage. The styles of the castles around Carson City were really similar, there were no special trait to any of them.

Zhao Hai knew that people from the Ark Continent didn’t like to pursue beauty, they were leaning towards having things that are practical. Looking at the long history of the continent, Zhao Hai knew that humans aren’t the only people waging wars with each other, there were also battles between humans and Magic Beasts. Now that the human population in the continent was increasing, the population of Magic Beasts in the mountains was increasing as well. When humans start to expand their territories again, they would be getting in contact with those Magic Beasts, which would lead to war. And in wars, beautiful castles have no use, thus, practical structures were deemed more important.

When Zhao Hai looked at the Calci Family’s fort before, he saw that the castle was constructed quite well, it was well suited for battles. Moreover, after years of modifications and additions, this type of has reached its peak potential, making it the most suitable place for the humans to fight in. This was the reason why forts looked very much the same, they were already designed to have the most effective defensive and offensive capabilities.

The bull-pulled carriage slowly arrived at the front door of the Savage Wolf Fort. There, two servants were present to greet the guests. Seeing Zhao Hai’s carriage, the two servants surprisingly didn’t come forward. But Zhao Hai didn’t care, when he disembarked along with Laura and the others, only then did the two servants give a bow, “We welcome Count Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai stared, he had attended a lot of these banquets, there weren’t a lot of people who call him by his title, most of them referred to him as ‘Mister Zhao Hai’.

But Zhao Hai recovered quickly, he knew that this was a ruse that Terry had planned. Terry wanted to borrow his title to embarrass him, reminding Zhao Hai frequently that he was only a count, so there was no reason for him to be proud.

Zhao Hai’s eyes flashed a cold light, but he didn’t say anything. Now is not the time to cause a scene, he needed to endure. So instead of being angry, he decided to behave, the more behaved and calm he was, the more Terry would get annoyed. Because of this, Zhao Hai just smiled faintly at the servant and said, “Thank you.”

The servants certainly didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have that response, they stared slightly before one of said, “We invite Sir Count.” Then he lead Zhao Hai towards the castle.

There was a carriage waiting for Zhao Hai and the others inside, but evidently, this was in a way worse situation than what was normally used. This carriage was very small, the horse pulling it was also very malnourished.

When Megan and the other women saw this, they looked very angry. Megan was about to reprimand the servant before Zhao Hai stopped her. He just smiled faintly and got on the carriage.

* * *

The character used in this one is 残 which has both the meanings of savage  and injured.

Chapter 473: Endure!

While sitting on he carriage, Megan snorted and said, “Big Brother Hai, why do we need to endure? See this carriage, what kind of carriage is this? This is a carriage that servants ride on, why did you ride it?”

Looking at Megan’s appearance, Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “It’s fine, don’t be too angry. You must have heard the servant calling me by my title, reminding me of my status. If we get angry, we would get Terry his satisfaction.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Megan became calm. She turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Big Brother Hai, are you really not angry?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “What’s the use of being angry? Even if we get unlucky today, think about the faces of the Robert Family tomorrow when they find out what just happened.”

Megan smiled when she heard Zhao Hai, she said, “Alright, we’ll endure. We still have something to do later.” As she said that, the carriage stopped.

Zhao Hai stared outside when he got off the carriage. He stared not because the carriage stopped in front of the banquet hall, he stared because there were many people standing outside. Several of them looked at Zhao Hai with a ridiculing smile on their face.

Terry stood in front of these people, looking at Zhao Hai with a faint smile. Seeing that Zhao Hai’s group had already got down from the carriage, Terry smiled and said, “Count Buda, are you comfortable with the carriage we’ve arranged you? There are no other carriages available for the count, our Robert Family only has this carriage left.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine, I thank Mister Terry for the concern. I didn’t think that there was such a malnourished horse in the Robert Family. It seems like the Robert Family isn’t doing well lately. I’ll have someone come to your family tomorrow and deliver ten Fire Horses that I use to pull my carriages. It really hurts the Robert Family’s face if they use a thin horse just like that one.”

When Terry heard Zhao Hai, his complexion couldn’t help but change. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to say such things.

He wanted to insult Zhao Hai with this method, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have that response. He actually made the Robert Family look poor.

Terry coldly snorted and said, “What kind of people is our Robert Family for us to treat our guests like that? Our treatment of Count Buda this time is quite acceptable.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It seems like the Robert Family deemed me to be unbearable, so why would they take the effort to send me an invite? Is the family not afraid of someone like me defiling your castle? If that’s the case, then Mister Terry might as well break this castle tomorrow since I’ve already polluted the place.”

Although Zhao Hai seemed like he was demeaning himself, saying such things about himself, the people present weren’t fools. These people knew what Terry did in the past. Because of this nobody dared approach Megan. Seeing that Zhao Hai and Terry going head to head with each other, these people felt interested and excited.

Terry’s complexion paled, he coldly snorted and then turned towards the crowd, “Everybody, please enter the hall for the feast.” Then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “I’m inviting Count Buda in as well.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled and said, “I thank Mister Terry. For Mister Terry to personally invite a lowly person like myself really gives me great honor.” Then he led Megan and the others towards the hall, leaving the black faced Terry behind.

Those who came out with Terry wanted to watch something fun, and they weren’t disappointed. They didn’t reveal too much in their expressions, but seeing how Terry and Zhao Hai interacted with each other, they knew that something interesting was going to happen inside the hall.

After going inside, Zhao Hai separated with Laura and the others as Jason went by his side. Jason patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “You really are very good with your mouth. What’s happening? I didn’t expect that you would be present here today.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Why wouldn’t I come? I want to see his expression today and what kind of attitude Terry uses when dealing with me. To be honest, I’m quite let down. If the heirs of the Robert Family are all like this, then I couldn’t help but feel disappointed.”

Jason smiled, “You should be careful with your words, Terry is not simple. With how he treated you today, I’m very sure that he has something planned. You should have went back earlier.”

Zhao Hai looked at Jason, he knew that Jason’s concern was sincere. Jason didn’t want Zhao Hai humiliated here. Zhao Hai smiled a little and looked around, then he went closer to Jason before whispering, “No, I can’t go back today. I need to appear here so that everyone can see me.”

Jason is a smart person, as soon as he heard Zhao Hai, he immediately understood. He turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Tonight?”

Zhao Hai nodded and then didn’t speak anything more. Jason snorted and said, “Why didn’t you tell me? If I didn’t ask you, then you won’t tell me?”

Zhao Hai looked all around, then he whispered to Jason, “Don’t be angry, the less people know the better. If everyone knew, then I’ll be in trouble. People shouldn’t know that I did it to avoid suspicion. Don’t tell anyone about this, even your family.”

Jason snorted, then he drank his liquor. Even if he didn’t reply to Zhao Hai, Zhao Hai knew that Jason understood him. Jason is a genuine friend, Zhao Hai wouldn’t doubt him, he knew that he certainly would tell.

The banquet went smoothly. During the event, there were no other people who went to talk to Zhao Hai aside from Jason. One could say that Zhao Hai was isolated.

Zhao Hai sat down with Jason at the side. Jason looked coldly at the people present and said, “These people present here are all descendants of families that are in good relations with Terry’s family. Right, Terry actually invited my second brother but I replaced him. It seems like the people wouldn’t be friendly tonight.

Zhao Hai just smiled and said, “It’s alright, be relieved. What’s wrong with being unfriendly? Their attitudes cannot affect me, don’t worry.”

The situation with Laura and the others were very different from Zhao Hai’s. They were surrounded by people and naturally their attention was fully set on Megan, ignoring Laura and the others. Moreover they were talking strangely to Megan, they kept speaking bad things about Zhao Hai while occasionally inserting some good words for Terry.

Regarding Terry’s method, Laura and the others couldn’t help but sneer. Such a method couldn only be described as weak, there was nothing special about it.

At this moment, Terry suddenly walked towards the orchestra and rang the cup on his hand. He smiled at everyone and said, “I’m very happy to see everyone today. But it seems like the atmosphere has become quite bland, how about we share a performances for everyone? What do you think?”

Zhao Hai almost spat out the liquor in his mouth. Jason looked at him and said, “What happened? Is there something wrong?”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled to Jason and said, “There’s a problem, big problem, I can’t play instruments, dance, and make poems. Haha, Laura and the others already saw this coming. Terry would actually do this method to deal with me.”

When Jason heard Zhao Hai, he couldn’t help but get anxious. He quickly asked Zhao Hai, “You really can’t write poems? Can’t dance? Can’t play musical instrument? Didn’t the people of your family teach you?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “They taught me, but unfortunately I just cannot learn.”

Seeing Zhao Hai’s nonchalant expression, Jason couldn’t help but get even more anxious, “Then what are you planning to do? If you cannot give a performance, they you would get disgraced. In the future, nobody would want you in their circle.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s alright, rest assured that I’m going to be fine. I have also thought about this point and naturally have a way to get around it. You don’t need to be worried.”

At this time, several Nobles have already given their performances. They didn’t do anything else other than reciting poems and playing musical instruments.

When Jason looked at Terry, his heart couldn’t help but beat faster. He knew that Terry would deal with Zhao Hai today. When a man playing an instrument was finished, Jason went forward and said, “I will go next.” Then he went to the band and played a harp.

Zhao Hai knew that Jason was stalling for time. The time Jason took while playing was very long. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, Jason is really caring.

However, it was impossible for Jason to perform for the entirety of the banquet. Although he had delayed, he still had to stop playing. At this moment, Terry’s gaze rotated towards Zhao Hai.

But Zhao Hai didn’t notice it, he was currently communicating with Cai’er. He decided that their operation needed to start upon seeing Jason playing.

Zhao Hai gave them a time limit of one hour. Jason’s performance lasted for 20 minutes, almost 50% of the time has passed by.

At this time, there have already been groups who had finished their job. Zhao Hai’s estimate was very accurate, the information that Cai’er has collected came in useful. The undead he sent out went in to kill, ensuring that they finish quickly. Even if they have one hour to finish, it was best to finish early.

What surprised Zhao Hai was the time it took for the fastest team to finish; the group took ten minutes to finish everything. This group was made up of undead assassins, their actions were very swift.

In ten minutes, they dealt with everything, Cai’er also had the inventory of the shop stored into the Space before the team burned the shop down.

Just as Zhao Hai took his mind off the operation, Jason’s performance was also on the verge of finishing. The applause given by the crowd completely woke Zhao Hai up.

Zhao Hai looked at Jason who was currently walking down the stage. Although Jason’s performance was very successful, he didn’t have a happy expression on his face. He just coldly looked at Terry as he slowly returned to his seat.

Terry didn’t notice Jason’s look since his eyes were aimed at Zhao Hai. Then he went up the stage and said, “Everybody’s performance today was very fantastic. How about we invite Count Buda to show us something too?”

The crowd was naturally very supportive of Terry. Zhao Hai had already expected this to happen. He didn’t say anything as he handed his wine glass over to a servant and slowly went up the stage.

Terry was in the stage looking at Zhao Hai with a ridiculing gaze. Before he started to deal with Zhao Hai, he had investigated him well. He knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t weak. He was a Dark Mage and although Terry didn’t know how he attained his strength, he can just think of it as Zhao Hai having a fortuitous encounter. However, when it came to performances, Terry was well confident that Zhao Hai was going to be very terrible in it.

Terry already checked and knew that Adam was a playboy, although Zhao Hai had been quite exceptional recently, he had neither learning nor skill when he was a child. Magic can be improved by potions, but talent in performing? Terry doesn’t think so. He had not heard about a potion that improves one’s talent in dancing, poem, and instruments.

Because he had thought of this point, Terry arranged this day to enact on his plan. He must make Zhao Hai lose face, he wanted Zhao Hai to be forever excluded from the circles of Rosen Empire’s nobles.

Zhao Hai stood on the stage and looked at the proud face of Terry. He then smiled and said, “I suddenly find myself to be quite ashamed right now, it seems like this banquet is specifically held for me. For someone of my status, it was impossible for me to get such a treatment. Since Mister Terry has invited me over to perform, then it would be impolite for me to decline. The previous performances were very good, It made me deeply admire the younger generation of the Rosen Empire. Since everyone wants to see me perform, then I can only apologize in advance if I make any mistakes. But me performing along wouldn’t be very special, I want to ask my fiancees over to accompany me. I wonder If everybody can agree to it?”

Zhao Hai being self deprecating made everyone present feel that there wasn’t anything wrong. Knowing that Laura and the others, very beautiful women, were going to perform, the people present naturally gave a loud applause. Terry, on the other hand, had a very ugly expression.

When he heard Zhao Hai, he immediately knew that Zhao Hai had already prepared for this moment. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have asked Laura and the others to accompany him on stage. This made Terry very disappointed. However, he still wanted to see Zhao Hai perform. He didn’t believe that someone who had no artistic talent could give a very good performance.

Chapter 474: Change in Attitude

Jason looked at Zhao Hai’s appearance on the stage and smiled, he suddenly didn’t worry. Although he didn’t know Zhao Hai for a long time, he understood that Zhao Hai wasn’t the kind of person that would suffer without hitting back. He was not the type to come unprepared as well. Seeing him so calm meant that he was prepared, it seems like Jason’s worries were all in vain.

Thinking about this, Jason couldn’t help but alternately look between Zhao Hai and Terry. The corners of Jason’s mouth slowly lifted, showing a smiling expression. He was really in anticipation for tomorrow, he wanted to see how Zhao Hai retaliated.

At the very least, Jason was sure that ZHao Hai would make the Robert Family suffer. But all of these have nothing to do with Jason, he wouldn’t be affected by the Robert Family’s bad luck.

At this time, Laura and the others were already standing up the stage. These beautiful women standing on the stage naturally attracted everybody’s attention. In turn, Zhao Hai who stood in front looked very insignificant.

Seeing the crowd being attracted to Laura and the others, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel uncomfortable. He was a man and the women behind him were his fiancees. With these people’s eyes going green in front of him certainly made him feel strange.

Zhao Hai coughed lightly, then turned towards Laura and the others and gave a signal. The women nodded and turned towards the orchestra and discussed something. The musicians didn’t decline the women and immediately gave them four types of musical instruments.

Laura took the harp, Megan took the cello, Meg had the horizontal flute, and Nier held the violin. Seeing that the group was prepared, Zhao Hai turned to the crowd and said, “I don’t know how to dance, play musical instruments as well as making poems. Because of this, I have to choice but to sing. I hope that everyone present won’t be offended by my performance.” Then he turned to Laura and the others and nodded.

The people facing the stage didn’t expect Zhao Hai to sing. Singing wasn’t generally something that nobles study. This was because it was very difficult to learn it. Songs in Ark Continent usually referred to operas. If you don’t practice it for a long time, there was not a way to present themselves in public. Most importantly, studying opera meant that you need to condition your vocal chords every day, for Nobles, this was very laborious, explaining the lack of people who studied it.

When the crowd heard Zhao Hai sing, they were shocked, all of them stared blankly at Zhao Hai. The gentle music was very soothing, it was as though it was touching their very hearts. However, the song had a touch of tragedy in it, making the crowd feel as though their hearts were being constricted, their entire bodies slowly being surrounded by a sad atmosphere.

The song ‘Bed of Chrysanthemums’ was actually not suited to the present situation because the song itself was played in a movie. How could people who hadn’t seen a chrysanthemum think about the emotion that one presented. It’s strange, but sometimes, song lyrics didn’t need to be understood in order to receive its soul. Back on Earth, Michael Jackson had many fans who didn’t understand English at all.

‘Bed of Chrysanthemums’ might not be able to contend against Michael Jackson’s songs, but for the people of the Ark Continent, the song still made their minds blank. This was because this form of singing didn’t exist in the continent before. Also, chrysanthemum seemed to be a foreign word.

There are times when foreign words bring advantages. Everytime one appears, it always feels novel and intriguing.

Before long, Zhao Hai finished singing ‘Bed of Chrysanthemums’, Even after he closed his mouth, there was still no sound that’s heard inside the hall. It may be because the crowd was still immersed in this out of the ordinary song.

Suddenly, an applause was heard in the hall, the crowd who were still staring couldn’t’ help but turn around and look for its source.

Zhao Hai also looked for the source of the applause, then he saw that the one clapping was none other than Jason. This fellow was the first to recover, therefore he applauded first.

When the crowd saw Jason, they immediately recovered. Then a thunderous applause broke out almost instantly. Zhao Hai and the others stood in a row and bowed to the crowd before walking down the stage.

These young people became lively. All of them were invited by Terry, and all of them didn’t have a status that was much worse than him. However, all of them had a good relationship with Terry’s family. Therefore, when Terry asked them to help him humiliate Zhao Hai, they were all very glad to play along.

But when they heard Zhao Hai sing, they suddenly forgot about Terry’s request. When Zhao Hai got off the stage, they immediately surrounded him. They asked Zhao Hai about the song, for them, this song was very attractive.

Zhao Hai chatted and laughed with these people as well. For the questions about how he learned to sing, he just responded that he really liked to sing when he was alone. But he knew that this kind of song cannot be sung in an opera, so he didn’t bother to reveal it.

Terry’s face was pale while he stood there looking at Zhao Hai. He requested these people to help him humiliate Zhao Hai. Naturally he didn’t only want to embarrass Zhao Hai, he also wanted to drive a wedge between Zhao Hai and these people.

If two people met and left a bad impression on each other, it would be very difficult for the two of them to become friends later. First impressions are very important.

Terry knew about this, so his plan was very simple, he would make Zhao Hai look bad in front of these young nobles. In the future, they would feel awkward towards Zhao Hai, exempting him from their circles, making becoming friends with him much more difficult.

But he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually be patient and even ridiculed himself, not offending these young nobles. And then afterwards, with his new and odd song, he made those nobles approach him and even chat with him. It was very clear that Terry’s plan completely failed.

Jason didn’t join the other nobles in surrounding Zhao Hai. His relationship with Zhao Hai was very different than these people. He can see what Zhao Hai was doing with them. So as a true friend, he will not interfere, he also thought that his help was unnecessary.

On the other hand, Jason was paying attention to Terry. Jason lived in Carson City since he was a child, so he knew the temperaments of the young nobles in the city. He understood more than Megan how sinister Terry was. He was afraid that Terry might have another method to deal with Zhao Hai.

Terry looked at Zhao Hai, his eyes filled with intense anger. He couldn’t accept it, he couldn’t accept that Zhao Hai managed to evade his plan to humiliate him.

With this thought, Terry’s eyes immediately hid his expression. He then headed up the stage and gently tapped the glass on his hand. Everyone immediately looked at him, feeling confused.

At this point, the crowd also remembered Terry’s request and thought about how nobody cared about it right now.They are now looking at Terry’s mildly annoyed expression.

These people aren’t fools, they understood why Terry was obviously targeting Zhao Hai. Although Terry told them bad things about Zhao Hai, after listening to Zhao Hai’s performance at the banquet, all of these nobles felt appreciative of him, they also felt much better towards Zhao Hai. In fact, they quite liked Zhao Hai more than they respected Terry. Terry was very arrogant and always wanted to have his whims accomplished. This fact gave these nobles an unfavorable impression towards Terry.

Now that they saw up the stage again, these people knew that Terry must be scared of Zhao Hai, which made them even more disgusted. Everyone knew that Zhao Hai didn’t offend Terry. The cause of the hatred between them was Megan.

Everyone also knew that Terry grew up with Megan, but after all these time, Megan’s treatment of Terry was always neither warm nor cold. But Terry still made it clear that nobody would get to approach Megan. Now that Megan was married, he still actually made a move on Zhao Hai. This made him lose style, this was not a method befitting of a Great Noble.

Terry didn’t care about any of these, what he was thinking right now was how to crush Zhao Hai. Therefore, when he stood up on the stage he smiled and said, “Count Buda’s performance was really too splendid. Everyone please give him a round of applause.”

When the crowd heard him mention Zhao Hai’s title, they became even much more disgusted. There were also some people here who held the title of count. When they wanted to embarrass Zhao Hai, they didn’t care about this. But now, Terry mentioning the title made them feel how harsh Terry was. However, they were still in the Robert Family’s castle, they still needed to give the family face. Therefore, all of them clapped but not the kind that showed enthusiasm.

Terry counted two seconds before he waved his hand, making the applause slowly fade. When he heard that the clapping has stopped, Terry continued, “From the applause, I believe I share the same sentiment as everyone when they heard Count Buda singing. There seems to be a sense of incompleteness. I want to ask Count Buda to come on stage again, but since singing was too boring, Count Buda needs to do something else.”

Those under the stage weren’t fools. When they heard Terry’s words, they understood what Terry intends to do. It seems like Terry wanted to humiliate Zhao Hai no matter what.

Doing this, Terry didn’t express his brilliance, on the contrary, it showed how small-minded he was. He looked like someone very desperate, this made the crowd disdain him.

Terry didn’t care about any of these, he proudly stood on top of the stage and said, “I invite Count Buda again.”

Zhao Hai looked at Terry and then faintly smiled. He knew that Terry was now at a loss, he already didn’t know how to proceed with this night’s events.

Zhao Hai slowly climbed on the stage. This made Laura and the others worried. They knew that Zhao Hai was with them the entire day, practicing their song. This time, they didn’t know how Zhao Hai would perform, will he really lose face today?

Zhao Hai stood on the stage and looked at the crowd, he showed a faint smile and said, “It’s a pity that Mister Terry didn’t allow me to sing, otherwise I would’ve made this night into my concert.” The crows laughed.

Zhao Hai then continued, “It’s already quite late. I still have some matters back at the family. Therefore, I shall give this small performance. However, I need to apologize first to the people below, I also need to apologize to Mister Terry.”

Chapter 475: Huge Harvests

Zhao Hai saying that he would be leaving wasn’t a surprise. They knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t want to keep on participating in Terry’s ruse any longer. To be honest, for Zhao Hai to endure until now made them admire him even more.

Although Terry was unwilling with Zhao Hai announcing his departure, it wouldn’t be good if he was to stop him. He can only lift his wine glass to Zhao Hai and agree.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then bowed towards the people down the stage before saying, “Since Mister Terry didn’t want me to sing, then I won’t be singing. When I went to the sea some time ago, I accidentally wrote two verses. I ask everyone here to please  appraise it.”

When everyone heard Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but be disappointed. Only two verses, how can this be considered to be poetry? Everyone at the crowd understood that Zhao Hai was going to be embarrassed this evening.

The expression of Laura and the others were not good either. Only Terry wore a smug face, he believed that he had won.

Zhao Hai looked at the expressions of the crowd and couldn’t help but smile faintly. “When I went to the sea in the past, I managed to get some Marine Magic Beasts to bring back to the continent in preparation for God’s Grace Day. This poem had these magic beasts as an inspiration. I only managed to write a few words, but I think that you would be able to get its message, moreover, its intent is very profound.”

The people below the stage looked worriedly at Zhao Hai. They didn’t know how Zhao Hai can deliver a message with such a short poem.

Zhao Hai looked at the crowd and smiled faintly, “I think that there are a lot of you who were able to eat crabs. This poem is about them, I ask the crowd to please appraise it.” Then he cleared his throat, scanned the crowd before stopping his gaze on the proud looking Terry. Zhao Hai slowly opened his mouth and said, “I often look coldly at crabs, but I always see them looking so proud!”

Then there was a static silence, the place was even more silent than the time after he sang.

Hahaha, Hahaha. A huge laughter was suddenly heard, breaking the silence. Zhao Hai didn’t need to look for the person who laughed, he was certain that it was Jason.

Jason’s loud laughter provoked a chain-reaction. The crowd in the hall were all laughing at this point. People understood who Zhao Hai’s poem was pertaining to.

These young nobles came to find themselves liking Zhao Hai more and more. If Zhao Hai continued to endure after all this time, then they wouldn’t like him. This was because they would see Zhao Hai as someone who didn’t have courage. Even if he did counterattack at a later time, they would then think that Zhao Hai was a sinister villain as well.

However, when Zhao Hai delivered his two lines, they immediately knew what Zhao Hai meant. Zhao Hai was clearly scolding someone, he even made a gesture towards the person. But most importantly, the crowd knew that Terry cannot say anything. If Terry makes a commotion, not only would he lose face, he would also be claiming that he was the butt of the joke. This move was wonderful, very wonderful.

Zhao Hai stood on the stage and then bowed to the crowd before saying, “Everybody, since I still have family matters so attend to, I shall be leaving first. I want to thank Mister Terry for the entertainment, I give my utmost gratitude to you.” then he bowed again before walking towards the exit.

There were some young nobles who followed Zhao Hai when he left, as if showing their support for him. Terry was standing there, pale faced. He knew that he would certainly be a laughing stock among the noble circles in Rosen Empire tomorrow.

Laura and the others also followed Zhao Hai out, all with smiles on their faces. When he reached the door, Zhao Hai turned back and gave a last bow to the nobles before he left the premises.

Although these nobles liked Zhao Hai, they still need to give the Robert Family face, so they didn’t immediately leave after Zhao Hai. However, each and every one of them looked between Zhao Hai and Terry with a strange expression.

Jason didn’t care about face, so he just left with Zhao Hai. The servants didn’t know what just happened inside the hall, but they already received an order from Terry beforehand. When Zhao Hai exits, they would still give him the carriage with the malnourished horse. However, even if Jason’s Crook Family wasn’t a millennium-old clan, their family still cannot be neglected. So in addition to Zhao Hai’s malnourished horse carriage, the servants brought a separate carriage as well.

Jason didn’t care about the other carriage, he just went forward and rode Zhao Hai’s carriage. Laura and the others followed them up. After the group sat down, Jason laughed and said, “Nice, Little Hai. You did good, hahaha. Did you see Terry’s face after hearing your poem? Hahaha, it’s all black, I’m afraid he might even vomit blood.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You’re exaggerating. But if he didn’t vomit blood today, he will certainly do so tomorrow. Hehe.”

Naturally, Zhao Hai’s voice was said while under soundproofing magic. He did that because he was afraid that they would be heard by the servants outside. Laura and the others just sat there smiling, they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would have a poem that would leave Terry speechless.

The carriage quickly arrived outside Savage Wolf fort. Zhao Hai and Jason disembarked from their carriage and then said farewell to each other. They got on their own carriages and then slowly went down the hill.

After boarding his carriage, Zhao Hai immediately returned to the Space. Just as he left the hall, the one hour limit for the operation just passed. Zhao Hai wanted to see what happened this time.

Just as he arrived inside the Space, he was received by Green and Kun’s smiling face. Looking at their expressions, Zhao Hai relaxed, it seems like the operation flawlessly succeeded.

Seeing Zhao Hai and the others arrive, Green and Kun immediately had them sit down before Green reported, “Young Master, the operation went by successfully without accidents. Not only did we get rid of the Robert Family’s people, we also looted their inventories. Even the bricks and wood inside weren’t let go. Even if they saved the fire in their shops, they wouldn’t be able to rebuild it. And most importantly, this time we got over 10 million tons of living supplies. We also received 10 million gold coins, 20 million silver coins, and 100 million copper coins. The bricks and wood could build 500 buildings. We have gained greatly this time!”

Zhao Hai didn’t think that they would get so much this time. He looked at Green and asked, “How did we get so much?”

Green smiled and said, “God’s Grace Day has just passed. At that time, various shops in the continent kept a lot of goods in stock. During the days leading up to God’s Grace Day, the shops would sell a lot of stuff. Because of this, the shops needed to be able to restock after God’s Grace Day passed by, explaining the amount of goods they have stocked up. Additionally, they also had the profits they just made a few days before. So it was natural that we got so much this time.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “How about the staff? Are they dead? Are the managers dealt with?”

Green nodded and said, “Young Master can feel relieved, according to Cai’er, all of the staff have been taken care of. No witnesses should have survived. Moreover, we also made sure to leave no evidence when we ransacked the place. Additionally, we also used Dark Magic before starting the operations, ensuring that nobody can see what was happening inside. All those who saw the magic were killed as well.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s good, let’s see how the Robert Family handles this. Moreover, when the beastmen come, we won’t worry about their food and clothing. Hahaha.”

Green smiled as well, millenium-old clans were truly extraordinary. If they didn’t attack the Robert Family, then they wouldn’t have gotten these goods. With these things, settling 100 thousand people wouldn’t be a problem. Moreover, they can also used their plundered goods to trade with the Merfold and the Beastmen. And most importantly, they had obtained a lot of silver and copper coins, enabling them to establish a currency system within Iron Mountain Fort. They can now say goodbye to bartering, as well as the awkward situation of giving salary.

Although Iron Mountain fort has some sort of currency system, the amount of silver and copper coins circulating was pitifully small. Gold coins were the most common type of coin present. So people can still technically acquire coins when they trade their products in Zhao Hai’s shop.

But this was not convenient, this system can only work because there was still a small amount of people in Zhao Hai’s domain. When their numbers increase in the future, confusion would surely appear. But now that the silver and copper coins were taken care of, the circulation of currency in the fort wouldn’t have any more problems.

Kun smiled and said, “The operation went as smooth as it can possibly be, there shouldn’t be any flaws in its execution. In order for people to not find out that we used Dark Magic, we used Light Magic in order to remove all traces of Dark Magic in the area. Now, traces of Light Magic were the only things left in the scene, masking all of our traces. Maybe people might even associate this matter with the Radiant Church, which would be very good for us.”

When he heard Kun, Zhao Hai stared, then he asked, “Grandpa Kun, whose idea was this? Why haven’t I thought about this before?”

In the past, Zhao Hai was only thinking about not being recognized, he didn’t think of using light magic to destroy the scene that he left behind. It seems like this old man still had his formidable wit.

Kun smiled and said, “It’s great that even you didn’t think about this. Right, all of us are quite tired, we should rest early. Tomorrow, we have to construct buildings in the Black Wasteland in preparation for the incoming Beastmen slaves this spring.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Greed didn’t immediately go to rest, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Young Master, how was the banquet?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s very good, it went by smoothly.”

Laura and the others actually chuckled. Then they told Green and Kun about what happened back at Terry’s banquet. When they heard about what happened, Green and Kun couldn’t help but laugh. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to take this opportunity to scold Terry, moreover, Zhao Hai scolded him in front of his face.

While the group chatted inside the Space, the bull-pulled carriage continued to travel slowly towards Calci Family’s fort. Shue and Shun sat on the driver’s seat with bored expressions. They knew that there was an operation tonight, it was very unfortunate that they weren’t able to participate.

Chapter 476: Antimagic Powder

Seeing that there was nothing to look at, Shue told Shun, “Shun, what do you think about tonight’s operation? Do you that it’ll succeed?”

Shun faintly smiled and said, “It’ll definitely succeed, with Cai’er as well as the undead, it would be impossible to fail. Right, Young Master said that if he manages to find the right plants to cultivate, he can give us potions in order to upgrade our strengths to 8th rank.”

Shue smiled and said, “There are already a lot of powerful experts on young master’s side. Even if we arrive at 8th rank, we wouldn’t be a big help to the Young Master, unless we reach 9th rank.”

Shun sighed and said, “If only reaching 9th rank can be so easy. If it was that easy, Grandfather Green, Grandmother Merine, and Grandfather Kun would have reached 9th rank already.” Suddenly, his face changed, he lowered his voice and told Shue, “Shue, be alert, I just sensed killing intent.”

Shue nodded, “I also felt it, I’ll immediately go and inform the Young Master.” Then with an intention, a shadow appeared and knocked three times on the doors of the vehicle.

This was a code, as long as Shue knocks three times, Cai’er would know that something just happened and then she would immediately inform Zhao Hai.

Upon hearing Shue’s knocks, Cai’er immediately appeared on the villa’s living room and told Zhao Hai, “Young Master, Shue just knocked on the door, something probably happened.”

Zhao Hai, who was chatting with Green, stared, then he immediately said, “What happened? Immediately open the monitor.” Cai’er complied and then opened the monitor.

The range of the monitor was much larger than original ten li. Looking at the monitor, Zhao Hai saw a lot of red dots appearing.

There red points were obviously not them, but an ambush on the both sides of the road. At this time, the carriage had already arrived in the middle of their encirclement. Looking at their numbers, Zhao Hai estimated them to be about 500 people. Moreover, they were all experts, most are 6th and 7th ranks, and then a couple dozen 8th ranks. These people were all in full body armor, and had various weapons in their hands. Most importantly, these people had 20 ballistas as well.

Ballistas are impossible to use without proper installation. It seems like these people had prepared these ballistas quite early, they should be in ambush for at least a couple of hours.

Zhao Hai appeared in the carriage and told Shue and Shun about what he saw, making them prepare. The two men immediately went down on the ground and didn’t move. The remaining matters would be left to him.

Naturally, the two didn’t object to Zhao Haim since both of them knew about Zhao Hai’s strength. So they didn’t say anything and just concentrated on the situation.

Zhao Hai didn’t return to the Space and just sat in the carriage while observing the scene on the monitor. Among these people, he can see a fully bearded man that seemed to be their commander. He was standing nearby a ballista, looking intently at the carriage without blinking an eye. He can also see that the ammo used on the ballistas were all whistling arrows.

Upon seeing the whistling arrow, Zhao Hai immediately changed his vision towards the other ballistas and saw the same thing. Upon looking closely, he noticed black jars being tied up on the arrows. He had no idea what they were trying to do.

If this was ancient Earth, ZHao Hai might have guessed that the other party were using explosives. But this was Ark Continent, there aren’t explosives here. Zhao Hai was very curious about the black jars.

But Zhao Hai certainly knew that those jars aren’t good for him. At this time, he saw the bearded man issue an order, Zhao Hai immediately called out and said, “Get ready!’ as the man’s voice came down.

The bearded man swung his hand down and said, “Release!” Then the more than 20 ballistas immediately shot their ammunition. Zhao Hai waved his hand as he took Shue and Shun to the Space as the arrows smashed the carriage into pieces.

Zhao Hai didn’t delay and immediately released a large number of undead. He had some of them surround the ambushers while some surrounded his carriage.

Zhao Hai just sat in the Space and looked at the bearded man. He knew that the bearded man was their leader. Zhao Hai just had his forces stay still and prepare on dealing with the enemy,

When he observed the bearded man, Zhao Hai saw something interesting. When he released his undead, the bearded man looked very silly. The man murmured, “Impossible, this is impossible. We used Antimagic Powder. How can he still use magic?”

Zhao Hai stared before his complexion changed. This was because the bearded man seemed to indicate the presence of a potion that was widely known in the continent, the Antimagic powder. This powder can debilitate Mages in large scales.

Antimagic Powder, just as its name suggests, is a kind of powder that can inhibit magic. This powder had no effect on ordinary people nor do they affect Warrior. This powder only targets Mages.

Sprinkling this powder around a Mage will make their magic spells cost exponentially more. When one was surrounded by Antimagic Powder, spells would take ten times as much as they normally did. In the past, people used this powder in dealing with Mages.

This Antimagic Powder was made by a Grandmaster Alchemist. Generally, Alchemists are Mages that wanted to branch out in their profession. But this Grandmaster wasn’t a Mage, not only was he not a Mage, he also had a huge hatred towards the profession.

When the Alchemist was young, he really wanted to study Magic. But when he went to get tested, he found out that he had no talent. Additionally, that night, the Mage who tested him went to his family and killed everyone. He was only able to survive because he went to a secret passage and ran away.

After several years of investigation, he managed to find out that he wasn’t untalented in Magic at all, on the contrary, he was very gifted. An enemy clan paid the Mage to fake his result and see to it that he was tested as having to talent. Afterwards, the Mage felt greedy and decided to attack the Alchemist’s family, murdering everyone and robbing their reserves. The Alchemist’s family only had small fame, they were a Merchant family with no background. Without an expert to guard them, the Mage went unhindered in eliminating the clan.

For revenge, the Alchemist didn’t study Magic, on the contrary, he even thought that Mages were a danger to humanity. He thinks that the profession must not exist, he wants to eliminate all Mages. Because of this he learned Alchemy and before long, he became a Grandmaster.

After 30 years of unyielding effort, the Alchemist managed to successfully make Antimagic Powder. The powder separates a Mage from the elements surrounding him, making a small space where he can barely use any spells. With the powder, there was no way for a Mage to use powerful spells.

Everyone on the continent knew that Mages specialize in spiritual force, through practicing it, they can communicate with the elements around them. Then, with the help of the elements, they could execute formidable magic spells. With this image, one can compare a Mage to a general commanding his soldiers. But with this Antimagic Powder, a Mage’s connection to the elements would be cut off. Making a Mage fully rely on his spiritual force. In this way, the Mage can only use a small amount of Magic he has in his body to cast spells. When his spiritual force runs out, the Mage can only wait for death.

This powder immediately caught the attention of all the Mages in the Continent. Every Major power also began to treat this as an important matter. Clans were even starting to use this powder to deal with Mages. Before long, all the Mages in the continent felt panic.

Because of the Antimagic Powder, all of the Mages in the continent made an alliance and started to chase the Alchemist down. In the end, the Alchemist was killed off. After that, the Mage Alliance went and exerted pressure on all Nobles and Major Forces of the continent, making them ban the future usage of the powder. Additionally, all Mages swore that if they find out that someone was still using the powder, they would get eliminated immediately.

Zhao Hai saw this story in a book discussing the history of the Continent. This matter happened 3000 years ago, and from then on, there was no other heard instance where Antimagic Powder was used.

He didn’t expect that today, he would actually hear someone mention this Antimagic Powder. This would certainly be a huge matter if it reaches the ears of the people of the continent.

The people who wanted to deal with Zhao Hai didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s magic was different. His magic was provided by the Space and wasn’t affected by the Antimagic Powder.

Those who attacked Zhao Hai surely didn’t expect that he wouldn’t be affected by Antimagic Powder. Zhao Hai didn’t allow them time to escape, he immediately made his Undead rush towards the enemy. In less than half an hour, all of the ambushers were killed off completely.

Zhao Hai used Wind Magic to collect the scattered Antimagic Powder. After doing that, he prepared to head back and tell Randolph about this matter, making them deal with it.

Zhao Hai clearly knew that the appearance of the powder today was a huge event in the continent. This matter doesn’t only affect Dark Mages, but all of the Mages in the Continent as well. Zhao Hai’s status was too small to handle this matter, only through Randolph and the Calci Family can this problem be dealt with.

After collecting the Antimagic Powder, Zhao Hai immediately turned all those who attacked him into undead. The also made the leader into an Advance Undead. From the man’s mouth, Zhao Hai discovered that the one who sent for the ambush was the Robert Family. As for where the Robert Family got the Antimagic Powder, the man didn’t know.

Now that Zhao Hai’s bull-pulled carriage was destroyed, Zhao Hai had no choice but to release Alien as he headed back to Dark Soldier Fort. Compared to the giant-horned bull, Alien was much quicker, therefore, Zhao Hai arrived at the fort much faster. In order to avoid misunderstandings, Zhao Hai went out when he was a small distance away from the roadblock. After which, he walked forward towards the small house.

After talking to the servant at the roadblock, Zhao Hai went back inside Alien and then headed towards the fort. Waiting for Zhao Hai outside the fort were Randolph and Smith.

When he saw the two, Zhao Hai immediately went out and gave them a salute. Randolph nodded and looked at Zhao Hai before asking, “Are you alright?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’m fine. I made Grandfather worried, let’s talk inside the fort.” Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and immediately understood that Zhao Hai had something important to say. He immediately nodded and led Zhao Hai to enter the fort and sat down in the main lobby. Sitting beside Smith were notable members of the Family, only Juwan was not present.

After the group sat down, Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, did some people attack you?”

Zhao Hai nodded and responds, “Yes, grandfather, people from the Robert Family ambushed me, there were about 500 of them. My carriage was destroyed because of that.”

When Randolph heard that it was the Robert Family, he snorted. Zhao Hai looked at him and then held up a leather back. He placed the bag on the ground next to Randolph and said, “Grandfather, in dealing with me, the Robert Family used Antimagic Powder. I’ve collected some of them in this bag.”

Just as Zhao Hai expected, when the people heard that the bag was filled with Antimagic powder, all of them became startled. They couldn’t help but unconsciously take two steps back. They looked at the bag as though it held a savage magic beast inside.

.The Calci Family was known as a Dark Mage clan. Naturally, most of their members studied Magic, if they didn’t practice Dark Magic, then they would practice other elements. Therefore, regarding the Antimagic Powder, it was no wonder that everyone in the room treated it as a fatal threat.

Randolph expression also changed, but he was the Family’s head, so when he heard about the powder, he didn’t take a step back. But his expression was still ugly, he looked at the bag and said, “Is there really Antimagic Powder in this bag?”

Zhao Hao nodded and said, “There is, in addition to the Antimagic Powder, I also had the commander of the attackers turned into Advanced Level Undead. From his own mouth, i learned that they are all people of the Robert Family. There shouldn’t be anything wrong about his testimony.”

Chapter 477: Acting Out of Desperation

Randolph’s face showed a serious expression, he clearly knew how huge the matter regarding Antimagic Powder was. This was something that was taken seriously by the continent. A lot of Mages suffered because of this powder.

Also, he didn’t believe that Zhao Hai would deceive him. Although Zhao Hai had some problems with the Calci Family in the past, Randolph can see that Zhao Hai really liked Megan. This Antimagic Powder held a very significant place in the hearts of all the Mages in the Continent. It didn’t matter whether they were Dark Mages or Light Mages, every single one of them were extremely concerned about this item.

Randolph nodded and said, “What are you planning to do now?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I reckon the Robert Family is finished. This night, except for their shop in Carson City, all of their shops in the continent will be attacked, they wouldn’t even get a single cent from them. In the future, their troubles would only get bigger. If Grandfather is swift, the Calci Family might even take over Robert Family’s businesses.”

After Zhao Hai talked, Third Grandfather pointed towards the bag of Antimagic Powder and said, “Wait, if they really used Antimagic Powder, then how did you survive?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Antimagic Powder doesn’t affect me.”

Third Grandfather snorted, “That just shows that this powder is fake, how could it be ineffective.”

Zhao Hai just smiled, “Is it really fake? You’ll know when you try it, Third Grandfather. Remember, if my toxin from the Water of Nothingness didn’t get cured, I wouldn’t be here today.”

When Zhao Hai said this, Third Grandfather didn’t know how to respond. At this time, Randolph was still very cautious, he immediately turned to Smith and said, “Smith, you get a person to try it, see if this thing is real. If it isn’t fake, then even god cannot save the Robert Family.”

Zhao Hai added, “Grandfather, i think we should send someone to monitor the Robert Family right now. They failed their operation this time, exposing the fact that they possess Antimagic Powder. It would be a big problem if they run away.”

Randolph stared, then he immediately nodded and said, “Right, do just as what Little Hai said. First, immediately go send some assassins over to the Robert Family, make sure to keep a close eye on their movements.”

Peter complied, he turned away to find someone to send. At this time, Smith returned, along with him, a family’s foreign elder came. He was an 8th rank Dark Mage, although he doesn’t have any authority, he can be trusted.

After the person came, he gave a salute to Randolph. Randolph had the man stand in an area as Smith started to spread the powder all around him. When Smith opened the bag, he immediately knew that the contents were real. This was because he felt the movement of the elements going sluggish. This was something he didn’t experience before.

However, to test the powder’s might, Smith continued to spread the powder around the person. When the person used magic, Randolph and the others carefully observed him. Even if the person was successful in casting his Dark Magic, they could clearly see that it took him a significant amount of effort to succeed. When the man casted the second time, nothing came out, the man’s face couldn’t help but turn white.

When Randolph and the others saw this scene, their doubts about the authenticity of the powder disappeared. At this time, Zhao Hai carefully collected all of the powder. After Zhao Hai was done, all the people in the room finally relaxed.

However, Randolph’s face turned very ugly. He turned to Smith and said, “Second, immediately inform the family to prepare for battle, we should be on guard just in case the Robert Family goes to act in desperation.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think about this point. When the Robert Family decided to use Antimagic Powder, they should’ve been acting because they see that they have an advantage. After all, they still didn’t know about the fact that all of their shops outside the capital were now destroyed.

Even if they don’t know, it was still possible for them to act out of desperation. This was because they might be be afraid that the Calci Family would spread the fact that the Robert Family had Antimagic Powder in their possession.

As long as the information about the existence of Antimagic Powder spreads, not to mention a mere Robert Family, even the Rosen Empire wouldn’t survive the backlash. Think about it, how many Mages were currently in the continent? For their own safety, all of the Mages would unite and kill all of those who possess Antimagic Powder. There isn’t a single power in the continent that could guard against an alliance of such scale.

The status of Mages in the continent was naturally high because of their formidable attacking strength. If people were to suddenly use a type of item like the Antimagic Powder, making their capabilities weaker, their status would definitely decline. In this case, in order to maintain their interests, Mages would surely make a counter-attack. The cumulative strength of all Mages in the continent was simply terrifying. There won’t be any 9th rank experts that would not want to interfere, this was because there were also a lot of 9th rank experts among the Mages.

Listening to the old patriarch, Smith immediately prepared to exit. But at this time, an explosive sound can be heard. Then, a giant firework fired off into the sky.

Upon hearing this, everyone in the hall immediately went out to see. The only ones left behind were Randolph and Zhao Hai, Smith left much earlier.

When he saw the people’s perplexed expression, Zhao Hai was confused. Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and faintly smiled, “That was just an early warning signal released by a magic cannon. That signal meant that our Calci Family is getting ready for attack. As long as that warning shot is heard, all the members of the Calci Family would prepare themselves for battle at the shortest time possible. Making themselves mentally ready for a life and death fight together with the family.”

Zhao Hai nodded, Randolph’s attitude towards him was now very good. Randolph looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Well, no need to think much about it. Come with me, let’s go towards the walls.”

Zhao Hai agreed, then went out of the room along with Randolph. While they were heading to the walls, they could see the members of the Calci Family redying themselves. There were people moving here and there, there were also Warriors wearing their full body armor, along with a weapon in their hands. Mages can be seen holding their magic staffs as well.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also noticed that the children of the family were being led away by some men. They were going to be lead outside the castle using a secret passage. Megan and the others didn’t join them, the group just stayed there instead.

People from the Calci Family knew that Dark Soldier Fort was their family’s fort. Their fighting power was strongest here. For someone to dare attack this place meant that someone was confident in dealing with the family. This made them more careful in preparing themselves.

Before long, Megan and the others arrived by Zhao Hai’s side. Megan already told Laura and the others about what was currently happening. However, they didn’t worry, they knew that inside Zhao Hai’s Space, 40 9th ranks were present. In the face of that quantity of 9th ranks, there was no point in worrying.

When Randolph saw Megan, he couldn’t help but frown and said, “Megan, why haven’t you left? Just in case something went wrong, you should make yourself safe.”

Megan smiled and said, “Grandfather, it’s fine. With Big Brother Hai here, there’s no need to worry. Right, let’s quickly go to the walls, let’s see who dared to attack us this time.”

Zhao Hai didn’t tell them about him being attacked with Antimagic Powder. In his mind, this matter was not necessary, this information wouldn’t have any influence on them.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he walked towards the walls along with Megan and the others. Randolph couldn’t help but shake his head, he didn’t expect that Megan would trust Zhao Hai this much.

The group quickly arrived at the walls. There were a lot of people on the walls as well. Moreover, magic cannons and ballistas were already prepared there.

Although the walls of Dark Soldier Fort weren’t very high, with all of their preparations, defending it wouldn’t be a problem. Most importantly, the Calci Family was a family of Dark Mages. There were a lot of Mages, especially Dark Mages, in the family, their fighting prowess wasn’t something to scoff at.

Standing on the walls were these Mages. Even a 100 thousand strong army wouldn’t be able to occupy Dark Soldier Fort. Attacking it wasn’t a good idea.

However, at this time. Zhao Hai complexion changed. He smiled bitterly and then turned to Randolph and said, “Grandfather, make those Mages in the walls leave, they wouldn’t be able to help. The opposite party has already spread Antimagic Powder on the surrounding forest.

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Randolph’s expression changed, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Really?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “They spread it out immediately. Moreover, the Robert Family had set out ten thousand people, all of them Warriors. Their ranks aren’t low either.”

Randolph stared, he decided to believe Zhao Hai as he nodded. Then he issued a command that was received by the people. Before long, all the Mages on the walls went back inside the fort.

From what he saw in the monitor, Zhao Hai knew that the other party was well prepared. The Warriors already had their weapons prepared. Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he wanted to see how the other party wishes to proceed.

At the same time, he increased the range of the monitor and saw a group of people scaling up Dark Mountain. This people might be the ones preparing to assault the fort.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then in the dim night, he released his undead and made them encircle the attackers. When he makes a move on the attackers later, he wanted to make sure that nobody gets to escape.

Right now, Randolph had a very serious expression, he didn’t expect the other party to place this much capital on this one attack. For them to use this much Antimagic powder meant that they were preparing to exterminate the Calci Family.

In any time of the year, eradicating the Calci Family wouldn’t be easy. However, God’s Grace Day has just passed, all of the important members of the family were currently present inside Dark Soldier Fort. If the fort gets attacked this time, the Calci Family would really be ended.